Chapter 240: Discussion Among Golden Immortals

One day, several years later, in a majestic palace somewhere in the Blaze Dragon Dao.

The ceiling of the palace was extremely tall, while the interior was vast and spacious. There were eight thick pillars supporting the ceiling, and each pillar had a giant dragon engaged in a different activity engraved upon it, with some roaring to the heavens, some soaring through the sky, and some locked in fierce battle.

Every single one of those dragons were extremely life-like, as if they could spring to life and fly out of the pillars at any moment.

There was a giant plaque hanging in the hall that read "Dragon God Palace", and beneath the plaque was a massive statue depicting another dragon that was roaring to the heavens.

In contrast with the extremely intricate craftsmanship of the dragons engraved onto the eight pillars, this dragon statue had been carved out in a far less sophisticated fashion. In fact, many of the scales on its body hadn't even been carved out, and it resembles the creation of a complete amateur.

Despite the fact that the statue was a little rough around the edges, there was an indescribable sense of mystique about it. It was as if there were another pair of eyes within the statue's crudely carved out eyes, looking down upon all of the insignificant ants of the world like an almighty dragon god.

The giant statue cast a huge shadow within the hall, striking the beholder with a sense fo awe and veneration.

Furthermore, there was a huge altar in front of the statue, which was laden with incense and offerings.

At this moment, there were three people standing in the hall, at the center of which was a purple-robed middle-aged man with an authoritative expression. It was none other than Ouyang Kuishan.

The second person was Bai Suyuan's seductive and stunningly beautiful mistress, Dao Lord Yun, and the third person was the golden-robed Deputy Dao Lord Xiong, who was standing around 10 feet away in a respectful manner.

The three of them were all silent, and they seemed to have been waiting for something.

Moments later, the sound of footsteps rang out, and three more figures made their way into the hall.

They were led by a gray-robed old man with a red nose, and if Han Li were here, he would be surprised to find that it was none other than Elder Hu Yan.

Beside him was a woman in a black dress with black veil over her face, concealing all of her features with the exception of a pair of cold eyes. However, she appeared to have been quite young, and her fingernails were a peculiar dark purple color, while also giving off a faint sheen.

The final figure in the trio was a black-robed young man who appeared to have only been in his twenties. He was quite handsome, with a head of long golden hair, and his face was also slightly golden in color, while a golden wheel was sitting on his back.

"You're finally here, fellow daoists. The five of us are finally all gathered in one place," Ouyang Kuishan said as he approached the three figures with a smile on his face.

A faint smile had also appeared on Dao Lord Yun's face, and even though three people had entered the hall, her gaze had remained fixed exclusively on Elder Hu Yan with a barely detectable hint of displeasure in her eyes.

The respectful look on Xiong Shan's face became even more pronounced as he extended a salute toward the three new arrivals.

The trio paid no heed to Xiong Shan, extending a collective salute toward the giant dragon statue instead before turning to Ouyang Kuishan and the others.

In the face of Dao Lord Yun's scrutiny, Elder Hu Yan was clearly feeling a little awkward, and he looked directly at Ouyang Kuishan as he said, "Fellow Daoist Ouyang, seeing as you're currently in charge of the sect, you can take care of the sect's internal affairs as you see fit. For what reason have you decided to call this meeting?"

The woman in the black dress and the golden-haired young man also turned to Ouyang Kuishan, waiting for an answer.

"Believe me, I wouldn't have interrupted your cultivation had there been an alternative. A while back, an incident took place in the Profound Ice Mountain Range while the core disciples were undergoing their trial. This matter has the potential to be quite significant, and that's why I must discuss it with you all," Ouyang Kuishan said as a serious look appeared on his face.

Elder Hu Yan was already aware of the incident, so he wasn't surprised to hear this.

As for the two people behind him, the golden-haired young man seemed to have also already heard about this, while the woman in the black dress appeared slightly perplexed, seemingly only having just been made aware of the incident.

After a brief pause, Ouyang Kuishan gave everyone a detailed recount of the incident that took place in the Profound Ice Mountain Range.

"... Thankfully, the two elders overseeing the trial were able to intervene in time to destroy the infiltrator's physical body, and only his nascent soul managed to escape. As for the disciples undertaking the trial, all of them also survived, so overall, there were no significant consequences," Ouyang Kuishan concluded.

"No significant consequences? Prior to coming here, I heard that four of the disciples had their physical bodies destroyed. Those four were all bright talents of the inner sect with exceptional aptitude.

“Now that their physical bodies have been destroyed, even if they can find new bodies to possess, their aptitude will be significantly compromised. Those two elders must be severely punished for their failure to protect the disciples!" the golden-haired young man said in a cold voice.

The 13 dao lords of the Blaze Dragon Dao were also split up into the native and itinerant factions.

The golden-haired young man was a native dao lord, and the four inner sect disciples who had lost their physical bodies during the trial were all native disciples, while all of the itinerant cultivators remained completely unharmed.

The seniors of the four disciples were furious upon hearing this, and they were all of the opinion that the two elders had favored the itinerant cultivators over the native ones.

Even if Ouyang Kuishan hadn't called for this meeting, the golden-haired young man was planning to pursue this matter further anyway.

"I'll have to disagree, Fellow Daoist Yuan. We've already familiarized ourselves with the sequence of events, and the two elders are not at fault. That True Immortal Stage intruder was extremely cunning and also quite powerful.

“Additionally, he had set up multiple arrays ahead of time, and it's already quite commendable that the two elders were able to destroy his physical body while keeping the disciples safe, so I think we should reward them instead," Dao Lord Yun retorted as she turned to take a glance at the golden-haired young man.

Dao Lord Yun was an itinerant cultivator before joining the sect, and the same applied to Ouyang Kuishan as well.

"How could you say that, Fellow Daoist Yun? They took on the mission to protect the disciples, and that made them responsible for all unforeseen mishaps. How can you say that they're not at fault when the physical bodies of those four disciples were destroyed?" the golden-haired young man countered in a justified manner.

"I think we all know whether you're actually discussing this matter objectively, or trying to take advantage of this opportunity to further your own agenda," Dao Lord Yun said with a cold smile.

"What did you say?!"

An enraged look appeared on the golden-haired young man's face but before he could say anything else, Elder Hu Yan gave him a stern glare, as he interjected, "That's enough, Yuan Bushao! Fellow Daoist Ouyang is the one in charge of the sect right now, so he's the one that gets to decide the verdict on this matter. I'm sure he'll make a decision that's satisfactory for all of us."

"Of course. You can rest assured on that, Fellow Daoist Hu Yan," Ouyang Kuishan assured with a smile.

Yuan Bushao clearly wanted to argue the point further, but he refrained from saying anything in the end.

A cold smile appeared on Dao Lord Yun's face, and she also remained silent.

"After the trial, I had in-depth conversations with both of the elders and the disciples that undertook the trial, and this is the information I've managed to gather on that True Immortal Stage intruder. All three of you are more knowledgeable and experienced than I am, so I invited you here to see if you can identify him," Ouyang Kuishan said as he pulled out three jade slips and handed them out.

The trio accepted the jade slips, then injected their spiritual sense into them.

"Deputy Dao Lord Xiong, your input is quite valuable as well, so you should take a look as well," Ouyang Kuishan said as he offered a jade slip to Xiong Shan as well.

Xiong Shan extended a respectful bow as he accepted the jade slip, then injected his spiritual sense into it as well.

The initial part of the content in the jade slip was a piece of footage, and it recorded the entire process from when the elderly man began conversing with Bai Suyuan and the other disciples, all the way to the point when he was defeated by Han Li and fled the scene.

Xiong Shan's expression changed slightly as he heard the elderly man mention Bai Fengyi.

After that came some text and images, denoting the items that the elderly man had been carrying.

"Who recorded the footage? It's very detailed, and it's very remarkable that one of the disciples was able to have the presence of mind to record this footage while in the heat of battle," Elder Hu Yan asked.

"It was Dao Lord Yun's disciple, Bai Suyuan," Ouyang Kuishan replied.

Elder Hu Yan took a glance at Dao Lord Yun before immediately withdrawing his gaze. "I see. Not only does she possess exceptional aptitude, it seems her mental qualities are just as stellar."

"I have an eye for people, so my disciples are naturally all outstanding. I'm not blind like a certain someone," Dao Lord Yun scoffed with a meaningful look in her eyes.

Elder Hu Yan sheepishly rubbed his own nose and offered no response.

The atmosphere had suddenly become a little awkward, and Ouyang Kuishan cleared his throat as he asked, "Does anyone have any ideas on who this person could be?"

"All of the items in his possession are quite ordinary, and there's nothing that we can use to identify him. However, judging from the cultivation arts that he used, it seems like he may be from the Upper Ah Continent," the woman in the black dress remarked in a slightly raspy voice.

"That golden-armored puppet looks a lot like the Wise King Puppets of the Infernal Frost Continent's Holy Puppet Sect," Yuan Bushao chimed in.

"That does indeed appear to be a Wise King Puppet. However, the Wise King Puppets of the Holy Puppet Sect are indeed quite precious, but they can still be purchased for a price, so it's impossible to identify him from the puppet," Elder Hu Yan said.

Ouyang Kuishan turned to Xiong Shan as he asked, "Is there anything you can enlighten us with, Deputy Dao Lord Xiong?"

"I wouldn't dare to say enlighten. I am far less knowledgeable and experienced than all of you, but I did notice that the sword array that he unleashed is a little similar to the Seven Deaths Sword Array of the Boundless Sword Sect," Xiong Shan replied in a humble manner.

"I've heard of the Seven Deaths Sword Array, it's an extremely renowned sword array from the Boundless Sword Sect, but how is it so pitifully weak? Not only was that elder with the Li surname able to destroy it with ease, he even managed to destroy those five flying swords as well," Yuan Bushao scoffed, clearly unconvinced by Xiong Shan's statement.

"I'm not sure of it myself, I just feel like it looks a little similar," Xiong Shan said as he lowered his head.

"Deputy Dao Lord Xiong is very proficient in the way of the sword, and I heard that he once obtained a lost inheritance of the Boundless Sword Sect, so I'm sure he's correct here. The reason why Elder Li was able to destroy the sword array so easily isn't because the array is too weak. Instead, it's because his attacks were sufficiently powerful to do so.

“It looks like the Mantra Treasured Axis that he refined contains heavy water that is imbued with the power of water laws, and that's quite a unique path, producing a very powerful treasure. If it wasn't for him, I'd say it wouldn't have just been a matter of four disciples having their physical bodies destroyed. If you ask me, you should reward him handsomely, Fellow Daoist Ouyang," Elder Hu Yan said.

Everyone else was rather taken aback to hear this.

It was very difficult to clearly assess the situation from the footage, so they could only speculate about what had taken place during the battle, but it appeared that Elder Hu Yan was very confident in his assessment of the battle, and no one was going to rebuke him.

"Indeed, Fellow Daoist Hu Yan. I'll make sure to have that arranged, but back to the subject at hand, it appears that the intruder won't be so easy to identify," Ouyang Kuishan mused.

Yuan Bushao wanted to say something further, but he held his tongue in the end after taking a glance at Elder Hu Yan.

Dao Lord Yun took a glance at everyone else, and there was a slightly concerned look on her face.

That man had attempted to abduct Bai Suyuan, so in her eyes, it was of the utmost importance for him to be tracked down and dealt with.

After a brief hesitation, Ouyang Kuishan said, "There's also something else that needs to be noted. That man mentioned Bai Fengyi, and it seems like there's some type of connection between the two."

Contemplative looks appeared on everyone's faces upon hearing this.

"Speaking of Bai Fengyi, it's quite a pity what happened to him. If it wasn't for what happened back then, given his aptitude, perhaps our Blaze Dragon Dao would've had 14 Golden Immortal Stage dao lords by now," Elder Hu Yan sighed.

A slightly dejected look appeared in Dao Lord Yun's eyes upon hearing this.

"I'm afraid we're also unable to identify the intruder, so just take care of this matter as you see fit, Fellow Daoist Ouyang," Elder Huyan said, then turned to depart.

"Why are you in such a hurry to leave, Fellow Daoist Hu Yan?"

In the blink of an eye, Dao Lord Yun appeared in front of Elder Hu Yan, blocking his path.

"Haven't you always been an avid wine enthusiast? I happened to get my hands on a few jars of fine immortal wine a while back, would you like to come over and have a taste? I also have questions about cultivation that I'd like to ask you as well," Dao Lord Yun said.

Chapter 241: Message from Qilin 9

"Er... I've been so busy recently that I've been getting dizzy and lightheaded, so I'll have to refuse your kind offer," Elder Hu Yan replied as he waved his hands in response.

"Dizzy and lightheaded? That's no good. Come sleep for a night on my 10,000-year-old Profound Ice Bed and you'll be sure to wake up feeling much better," Dao Lord Yun said.

"Ah, I just remembered that I still have a cauldron full of pills sitting on the fire, and it's about time that they're ready! My apologies, but I have to go now."

Sweat was beginning to bead up on Elder Hu Yan's forehead as he spoke, and he exploded into countless specks of blue light, vanishing on the spot.

Dao Lord Yun placed her hand over her own mouth as she giggled in amusement.

Meanwhile, Yuan Bushao and the woman in the black dress paid no heed to the interaction between Elder Hu Yan and Dao Lord Yun, departing from the hall in silence.

Xiong Shan also took his leave before promptly departing, and before long, Dao Lord Yun and Ouyang Kuishan were the only two people left in the hall.

A serious look appeared on Dao Lord Yun's face as she asked, "What do you plan on doing with those two elders?"

Ouyang Kuishan remained silent, seemingly still yet to make a decision.

"Let me make this clear: it's all thanks to that Li Feiyu that Yuan'er wasn't abducted during the trial, so I'm not just going to stand by and watch as others try to frame him to further their own agendas," Dao Lord Yun said in a meaningful voice.

"As the leader of the sect, I can't be biased. Otherwise, conflicts could easily arise, leading to catastrophic consequences. Li Feiyu did indeed do quite well in this situation, but at the same time, he failed to perform his duty as one of the guardian elders, so he should be let off the hook, but not rewarded beyond that.

“As for Su Tongxiao, the blame for the incident should definitely fall on him, but given the circumstances, I'll only administer a light punishment upon him. Additionally, seeing as Fellow Daoist Hu Yan expressly stated that Li Feiyu should be rewarded, you can issue him a reward on your own behalf," Ouyang Kuishan said.

Dao Lord Yun nodded in response, then flew away as a streak of white light.

Moments later, she appeared on another mountain summit.

There was a white palace that was over 100 feet tall situated on this mountain, and it looked as if it had been carved out of a single enormous block of white jade.

It was an unknown jade-like material that was giving off a gentle glow that resembled moonlight, and the entire palace was filled with a strong glacial aura.

As soon as Dao Lord Yun entered the palace, she was immediately met with a burst of glacial qi, but it was kept at bay by a burst of invisible force that was emanating from her body.

At the center of the palace was a crescent-shaped pond that appeared to have been formed naturally, and it was so deep that it was impossible to see its bottom. There was a translucent round plate that was about 10 feet in size floating on the surface of the pond with countless tiny transparent runes engraved upon it, and it was giving off a white glow, as if it were entirely crafted from a block of ice.

The glacial aura here was 10 times more pronounced than outside, and it was coming directly from that pond.

A woman in a white dress was seated with her legs crossed on the plate, and it was non other than Bai Suyuan.

Her entire body was enveloped within a layer of gentle white light as she constantly absorbed the glacial qi from the pond. Her aura had advanced significantly compared with during the trial, and she was approaching the late-Spatial Tempering Stage.

Dao Lord Yun nodded in approval upon seeing this.

Bai Suyuan seemed to have heard Dao Lord Yun's arrival, and her eyelashes fluttered momentarily before she opened her eyes.

A smile then appeared on her face as she rose up from the plate before landing next to Dao Lord Yun.

"You're becoming more beautiful by the day, Yuan'er. I wonder which lucky boy is going to make you his wife," Dao Lord Yun chuckled as she gently stroked Bai Suyuan's hair.

A slight blush appeared on Bai Suyuan's face upon hearing this, and she complained, "What are you saying, Mistress? I'm not going to marry anyone as long as you don't!"

"What does this have to do with me?"

Dao Lord Yun was very amused to hear this. As one of the 13 Golden Immortals of the Blaze Dragon Dao, she possessed unfathomable power, but she was like a doting mother whenever she was around her favorite disciple.

She led Bai Suyuan to the side before sitting down as she said, "Yuan'er, it's good that you're so diligent in your cultivation, but don't rush it. This Glacial Moon Pond contains extremely potent glacial qi, which will reciprocate your Moonlight Immortal Physique, but at the same time, it'll also harm your body in excessive quantities, so you have to be patient and progress slowly."

"Yes, Mistress," Bai Suyuan replied.

After that, Dao Lord Yuan answered a few questions that Bai Suyuan had on cultivation, and given her aptitude and intelligence, she was immediately able to figure things out.

The smile on Dao Lord Yun's face became even more pronounced upon seeing how gifted a learner her disciple was.

"By the way, why did you come here today, Mistress?" Bai Suyuan asked.

"Why? I can't come to visit you?" Dao Lord Yun asked as she put on an angry expression.

"That's not what I meant, Mistress," Bai Suyuan said as she swayed Dao Lord Yun's arm from side to side like a small child.

"Alright, I won't tease you any longer. I discussed what happened during the trial with a few of the other dao lords today," Dao Lord Yun said with a serious expression.

Bai Suyuan's expression changed slightly as she released Dao Lord Yun's arm, and a serious look appeared on her face as well.

"Even after some discussion, we were still unable to identify the intruder," Dao Lord Yun sighed.

Bai Suyuan's face fell slightly upon hearing this, and she replied, "The Northern Glacial Immortal Region is extremely vast and is home to countless powerful cultivators, so there's no way our Blaze Dragon Dao can know them all."

"Seeing as we've been unable to identify him or track him down, I think you should stay in the sect as much as possible. I'll continue to investigate the matter, and we'll be sure to capture him," Dao Lord Yun said.

Bai Suyuan nodded in response, following which a thought occurred to her, and after a brief hesitation, she asked, "During the trial, four of the disciples had their physical bodies destroyed. What have you and the other dao lords decided to do with Elder Li and Elder Su?"

A meaningful smile appeared on Dao Lord Yun's face upon hearing this.

"You seem to be very concerned about that Li Feiyu. I've never seen you pay so much attention to any of the male disciples. Could it be..."

"What are you saying, Mistress? Elder Li saved our Bai Clan and brought me to the Blaze Dragon Dao, and this time, he saved me from being abducted in the trial. I owe him a great debt, and that's the only reason why I asked about him," Bai Suyuan hurriedly explained.

"Is that right?" Dao Lord Yun asked with an amused look in her eyes.

For some reason, Bai Suyuan didn't dare to meet Dao Lord Yun's gaze as she replied, "Of course! There's no way I'd take a liking to someone like him!"

Dao Lord Yun merely began to giggle in response, while Bai Suyuan kept her head lowered as a faint blush appeared on her face.

……

Meanwhile, in a lush mountain range that was abundant with spiritual qi countless kilometers away from the Blaze Dragon Dao.

A young man who was dressed like a lumberjack was seated in a secluded cave with his legs crossed. There was a layer of dense white light around him that was expanding and shrinking with each cycle of inhalation and exhalation.

A long while later, the man opened his eyes as he murmured to himself, "This body has decent aptitude. I've already recovered around a tenth of my former cultivation base."

A look of intense resentment then appeared in his eyes as he spat through gritted teeth, "Li Feiyu, I'll get you back for destroying my physical body sooner or later!"

After that, he rose to his feet and exited the cave before flying away into the distance as a streak of white light.

……

Over 10 years passed by in the blink of an eye, and Han Li had been focused on completing Transient Guild missions this entire time.

Due to the fact that he had to take care of the Dao Warrior and all of the spirit plants planted in his fields, all of the missions that he took on were ones near the Ancient Cloud Continent.

Due to the frequency at which he took on missions, many of the other Transient Guild members situated on the Ancient Cloud Continent gradually came to know the name of Wyrm 15, a powerful madman who was sweeping through missions like the wind.

As a result, many people were led to the false assumption that he had to have been at the late-True Immortal Stage.

As Wyrm 15's reputation continued to build, many of the Transient Guild members near the Ancient Cloud Continent were keen to have him as an ally during their own missions, and there were even some people directly contacting him with requests to complete certain missions.

In contrast with how renowned he had become in the Transient Guild, Han Li had maintained a low profile in the Blaze Dragon Dao.

After completing his three regular elder missions, he had refrained from interacting with anyone else in the sect under the guise of cultivating in seclusion.

During this period, he was summoned once by Dao Lord Ouyang and Dao Lord Yun, and the former had enquired him about the incident concerning the trial, while the latter had rewarded him 1,000 merit points without saying anything, only warning him not to speak of this matter to anyone else.

He wasn't the type to go blabbering about something like this anyway, and he was certainly more than happy to accept the 1,000 merit points.

He wasn't all that renowned in the sect to begin with, and after so many years out of the limelight, he had become even lesser known in the sect, and that was exactly what he wanted.

One day, Han Li was standing in front of his medicine garden in his cave abode, nodding to himself with approval at the sight of the vibrant spirit medicines laid out before him.

During these past years, he had been constantly undertaking all types of missions, accumulating a large sum of spirit stones in the process. Additionally, he had managed to nurture a batch of 50,000-year-old Blaze Tuber Herbs with the spirit liquid from his Heaven Controlling Vial, so it was now time for him to focus on cultivating for a while.

There was a rather spacious and barren area in the southwestern corner of the garden, standing out like a sore thumb compared with the rest of the lush and vibrant garden.

That was exactly where the primary bean had been planted.

Over the years, he had watered it with the spirit liquid on many occasions, but the primary bean still showed no signs of germinating at all.

According to the book of Dao Warrior planting insights given to him by Elder Hu Yan, there was a massive range of factors that could impact the germination period of a Dao Warrior, and it was quite normal for a bean to be nurtured for centuries without germinating.

Right at this moment, Han Li's brows suddenly furrowed slightly as he returned to the secret chamber in his cave abode.

As soon as he entered the secret chamber, he flipped a hand over to produce his Transient Guild mask, which he promptly put on.

The runes on the mask began to glow brightly as it released a beam of azure light, which formed a projection of an azure figure.

The figure was rather tall and imposing, wearing a cloak-like robe and an azure deer mask. He was standing with his hands clasped behind his back, giving off an authoritative aura.

"Why have you suddenly contacted me, Fellow Daoist Qilin 9?" Han Li asked.

Qilin 9 was none other than the late-True Immortal Stage Transient Guild member that Han Li suspected to have been Xiong Shan.

Chapter 242: Smelting Sword Refinement

"No need to be alarmed, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15. I contacted you today because there's a special mission that I'd like to invite you to complete with me," the azure figure said.

"If my memory serves me correctly, we haven't had many past interactions, so why have you come specifically to invite me?" Han Li asked.

"You've been forging quite a reputation for yourself recently, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15. We've only worked together once in the past, but you left a very deep impression on me. I know that your reputation is very much deserved, and that's why I came to invite you to undertake this mission with me."

Qilin 9 was praising Han Li, but the tone of his voice was very neutral, as if he were merely stating facts rather than trying to flatter Han Li.

"My reputation is nowhere near as resounding as yours, Fellow Daoist Qilin 9. Seeing as this is a mission that's caught your eye, I'm assuming it's not going to be an easy one to complete, right?" Han Li asked with a smile.

"My apologies, but this mission is indeed quite special. Low-level members are barred from undertaking the mission, and I'm afraid I won't be able to reveal the contents of the mission to you unless you agree to accept it," Qilin 9 replied.

"Even if you can't reveal the contents of the mission to me, surely you can at least tell me the mission location," Han Li said.

"The location is on the Infernal Frost Continent," Qilin 9 replied.

"In that case, I'm afraid I'll have to turn down the mission. There are many things that I'm busy with at the moment, so I can't make any far journeys. My apologies, Fellow Daoist," Han Li refused as his brows furrowed slightly.

To the north of the Ancient Cloud Continent was a vast frozen sea, and across that sea was a continent that was perpetually enshrouded in ice and snow. That was the Infernal Frost Continent.

Crossing the frozen sea wasn't as difficult as crossing the Thunderstorm Sea, and there was supposed to have been a teleportation array for this purpose as well, but even so, the journey would've taken at least several years there and back.

Qilin 9 wasn't surprised by Han Li's refusal, and he said, "Don't be in such a hurry to refuse. Fellow Daoist. I suggest you hear the reward for the mission before you decide whether to accept it or not."

"Go ahead," Han Li prompted.

"Aside from 300 Immortal Origin Stones, you'll also receive a Jade Gleam Cloud Stone," Qilin 9 said, and he seemed to be quite confident that his reward would be sufficient to tempt Han Li.

Instead of being pleased or elated to hear this, Han Li remarked with a cold expression, "The fact that you know that I'm searching for a Jade Gleam Cloud Stone indicates that you've done your homework before coming here, Fellow Daoist."

"It's already been a few years since you released the mission searching for a Jade Gleam Cloud Stone, and to this day, no one has answered your call. Surely you're not going to pass up this opportunity, are you?" Qilin 9 asked.

Han Li fell into deep thought upon hearing this.

Seven or eight years ago, while carrying out a mission for the Transient Guild, he had decided to read through the beasthide book that he had obtained from the old man that had attacked Bai Suyuan, and in that book, he had read about a very strange type of smelting sword refinement technique.

The technique allowed one to smelt special metals and materials to drastically enhance the power of a flying sword, and if a set of multiple flying swords were smelted at once, those swords would be able to fuse as one during battle, making them significantly more powerful than before.

Most importantly, after the smelting process, not only would the physical forms of the flying swords be completely transformed, the auras that they gave off would also change as a result of the materials used in the smelting process.

Right there and then, Han Li had decided that he was definitely going to smelt his 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords again.

However, the spirit materials required for this smelting process were very difficult to acquire, with the most important material being the Dendrobium Gold Essence, while the most important supplementary material was the Jade Gleam Cloud Stone.

Coincidentally, Han Li already had some Dendrobium Gold Essence. It was that dark golden metal that he had obtained from the Origin Mirage Beast's palace, and he had acquired more of the material from the elderly man in the Profound Ice Mountain Range.

As for the other materials required, Han Li had managed to gather all of them from within the Blaze Dragon Dao at the cost of some Immortal Origin Stones. All that was left to find was the Jade Gleam Cloud Stone, which he had been unable to find in the sect or in the Transient Guild.

After a long silence, he asked, "How big is this piece of Jade Gleam Cloud Stone?"

"I'm sure you're aware of how precious the material is, Fellow Daoist. The reward is only a fist-sized chunk. Even so, that's already more than enough to be used as the main material to refine a flying sword," Qilin 9 said.

After a brief hesitation, Han Li finally said, "Alright, I'll accept this mission."

Even a fist-sized chunk of Jade Gleam Cloud Stone was sufficient to be used as a supplementary material to refine his 72 flying swords.

"Fantastic! With your inclusion, I'm sure we'll be able to complete this mission smoothly."

Only now did a hint of a smile creep into Qilin 9's voice.

"I've already accepted the mission, so you can tell me exactly what needs to be done now, right?" Han Li asked.

"There's no hurry. The people undertaking the mission haven't all been assembled yet. You can make some preparations, then meet us on Everlone Island situated at the northernmost tip of the Ancient Cloud Continent. There, I'll reveal the exact contents of the mission to you," Qilin 9 said.

"In that case, I'll see you there," Han Li replied with a nod.

Qilin 9 didn't stay any longer, instantly vanishing from the spot.

Han Li stowed his Transient Guild mask away, then departed from his secret chamber.

……

Three years passed by in the blink of an eye.

There was a peninsula situated in the northernmost tip of the Ancient Cloud Continent. It was a thin and long landmass with a slight curvature, extending into the boundless white sea.

The entire island had a black coloration, and it was completely encased under a thick layer of ice without any vegetation to be seen.

At the end of the island was a giant black rock, atop which sat a tall and imposing figure with his legs crossed. The figure was wearing a loose-fitting black robe with an azure deer mask on his face, and it was none other than Qilin 9.

Beside him at the foot of the rock was a tall and thin man wearing an ochre robe with plum blossom designs embroidered upon it. He was wearing a rat mask that was also azure in color.

Through the eye holes on the mask, one could see that he had a pair of extremely tiny pupils, and quite fittingly, his eyes were giving off a sly and sneaky gleam, much like one would see in the eyes of a rat.

"We've already been waiting for seven days, why has he still not shown up? He's certainly making us wait?" the rat-masked man complained in a high-pitched voice as he took a disgruntled glance in the direction of the Ancient Cloud Continent.

"We're the ones who got here earlier. The agreed time still hasn't arrived yet, so you'll have to wait a bit longer," Qilin 9 said.

The rat-masked man habitually flexed his neck from side to side upon hearing this and didn't say anything further.

Around 15 minutes later, a streak of azure light suddenly appeared in the distant sky before quickly landing in front of the giant black rock.

The azure light contained none other than Han Li, and he swept his gaze over Qilin 9 and the rat-masked man as he cupped his fist toward them in a salute.

Qilin 9 rose to his feet atop the giant rock, then introduced to Han Li, "Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15, this is Fellow Daoist Qilin 17."

"I've heard much about you," Han Li said with a nod.

"You sure kept us waiting!" Qilin 17 complained in an inhospitable voice as he sized up Han Li.

Han Li could hear the displeasure in his voice, but he merely smiled and didn't say anything.

Qilin 9 jumped down from the rock, landing beside Han Li's duo as he said, "Now that everyone's here, allow me to reveal the contents of the mission."

Han Li immediately turned to him, as did Qilin 17.

"According to the mission description, there's a certain valley in the Snowstorm Forest to the south of the Infernal Frost Continent, and there's an extremely high-level array set up in the valley. Our mission is to infiltrate the valley without triggering the array and kill the mid-True Immortal cultivator inside," Qilin 9 said.

"Do we know why the array exists and if there's anything special about it?" Han Li asked.

"That's all I know about the mission, we'll have to figure out the rest after we get there," Qilin 9 replied.

"It sounds like it's not a very difficult mission at all. By the way, why are all of the special missions in the guild like this? They're always so ambiguous and lacking in details," Qilin 17 complained.

Qilin 9 paid no heed to Qilin 17 as he declared, "Alright, time is of the essence, so let's set off right away."

He swept a sleeve through the air as he spoke to release a cascade of starry golden light, within which was a three-level louchuan that was entirely golden in color.

The louchuan was around 300 feet in length and over 50 feet tall, with many runes engraved on its surface for speed enhancement and other purposes. Furthemore, the exterior of the three-story pavilion on the louchuan was extremely ornate and embedded with all types of precious jewels, presenting an extravagant sight to behold.

"In order to get to the Infernal Frost Continent, we can take a teleportation array from Smoke Tomb Island. Prior to that, we can make the journey to the island on my Golden Veined Spirit Boat," Qilin 9 said, then rose up into the air before landing on the deck of the louchuan.

Han Li and Qilin 17 also did the same, landing on the spirit boat one after the other.

Upon his landing, Han Li swept his gaze over the spirit boat to find that there were also all types of complex patterns engraved onto the pillars, doors, and windows on the louchuan, all of which were giving off bursts of spiritual power fluctuations.

Standing outside each level of the pavilion were several slender and extremely beautiful young women, all of whom were wearing rainbow-colored or golden silken robes, appearing as if they were celestial maidens.

However, Han Li quickly came to realize that these stunningly beautiful women were actually all just intricately crafted puppets.

"Each of you can choose a level of the pavilion to stay in. If you need something done, just issue an instruction to the puppets," Qilin 9 said, then flew onto the top-floor of the pavilion before making his way inside.

Qilin 17 took a glance at Han Li, then didn't say anything as he rose up onto the second floor. He then reached out to stroke the cheek of one of the puppets standing in front of the door as he praised, "Oh, that's quite pleasant on the hands."

After that, he chuckled to himself as he opened the door of the pavilion and made his way inside.

Chapter 243: Extreme Cold

Shortly thereafter, after a burst of tremors, all of the runes on the Golden Veined Spirit Boat lit up, and it rose up into the sky amid a vast expanse of golden light, flying toward the frozen sea.

Instead of entering the pavilion, Han Li made his way to the bow of the boat, where he cast his gaze into the distance while standing with his hands clasped behind his back.

Up ahead was a boundless expanse of white with thick layers of ice spreading as far as the eyes could see, only punctuated by some frosty black rocks or giant mountains of ice jutting out of the surface of the sea.

The view in the extremely far distance was quite blurry due to the presence of the mist up ahead, and birds were an extremely rare sight in the sky above the frozen sea.

Both the sea and the sky above it were extremely silent, giving this frozen region a bleak and lifeless appearance.

However, through his spiritual sense, Han Li was able to detect the auras of many powerful demon beasts lurking in the clouds in the sky, the depths of the sea, and even within some of the mountains of ice, and the only reason why none of them had come out as they were fearful of Han Li's trio.

Thinking back to the Thunderstorm Sea, Han Li couldn't help but marvel at the vast diversity in the geographic environments in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

There were virtually no places like this in the Mortal Realm or in the Spirit Realm, and he was certain that there were still many more places that he couldn't even fathom here in the Immortal Realm.

For some reason, the memory of the short time that he had spent traveling the Spirit Realm as a pair of lovebirds prior to his ascension suddenly sprang into his mind.

This memory had always been one that he had suppressed and relegated to the bottom of his heart, and it was also why he had been alone for the vast majority of time during his cultivation journey, unwilling to casually dabble in relationships.

Parting with his loved ones had always been a painful experience that he didn't want to have to endure.

"If Wan'er were by my side, we'd be able to roam the Northern Glacial Immortal Region freely together. I wonder how she's doing right now. The resources that I left her prior to my ascension should be enough to support her cultivation to the Grand Ascension Stage. I wonder if we'll ever be reunited someday..." Han Li murmured to himself with an absentminded expression, then turned and made his way into the first-floor pavilion.

……

Close to a year later.

There was a white island with a radius of no more than 10,000 feet situated in the southern region of the frozen sea.

The island was circular in shape with a clear outline, resembling a massive white plate, and it was clear that it had been created artificially.

On the island were a series of white stoned pillars of different heights, some of which had runes engraved upon them, while others were embedded with spirit stones that contained abundant spiritual power.

The entire island appeared to have been a massive white array.

Right at this moment, the Golden Veined Spirit Boat arrived in the air from afar, then paused momentarily in mid-air before vanishing amid a flash of golden light.

Han Li's trio appeared in the sky, then began to descend toward Smoke Tomb Island.

They weren't making any efforts to conceal their own auras, but their appearances and statures had all been altered significantly.

Qilin 9 had turned into a burly man with a thick beard, while Qilin 17 had adopted the appearance of a scholarly man wearing an azure robe, and Han Li had transformed into a fair-skinned young man who appeared to have been around 20 years of age.

The three of them descended onto a small plaza on the edge of the island, and there was a hall constructed from white stone up ahead.

The three of them strode into the hall to find that the furnishings were extremely simple, with only a circular stone platform in the hall, atop which sat an elderly man with a white beard with his legs crossed.

To Han Li's surprise, the elderly man was an early-True Immortal cultivator, and his attire indicated that he was an inner sect elder of the Blaze Dragon Dao.

The elderly man took a glance at Han Li's trio, remaining seated as he asked, "Have you come here to travel to the Infernal Frost Continent?"

"Correct," Qilin 9 replied.

"That'll be seven Immortal Origin Stones per person," the elderly man said in an expressionless manner.

After the fee was issued, the elderly man rose to his feet, stepping down from the circular stone platform before leading Han Li's trio out of the hall through a rear door.

After emerging from the hall, the three of them followed the elderly man over a path that was around 10 feet wide, making their way toward the center of the island.

Han Li took a glance at the path beneath his feet to find that it was several inches lower than the ground on either side of it, giving it the appearance of a small trough embedded into the earth, and there was a rune engraved onto the ground once every several dozen feet.

The closer they drew to the center of the island, the more frequently these paths appeared, forming a complex system that was quite mysterious in appearance.

"Fellow Daoist Qilin 9, if I'm not mistaken, he's wearing a robe of the Blaze Dragon Dao, is that correct?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

"Indeed. This man seems to be an inner sect elder of the Blaze Dragon Dao," Qilion 9 replied.

"Could it be that all of the teleportation array between the Ancient Cloud Continent and the Infernal Frost Continent was constructed by the Blaze Dragon Dao?" Han Li asked.

"That's not the case. The teleportation array on Smoke Tomb Island is the only one that was constructed by and is under the control of the Blaze Dragon Dao, while the teleportation array on Extreme Ice Island near the Infernal Frost Continent is under the control of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace," Qilin 9 replied.

"I see. Thank you for enlightening me, Fellow Daoist," Han Li said.

As the two were conversing with one another through voice transmission, they followed the elderly man to a plot of flat land near the center of the island.

Han Li took a glance at the area to find a circular array surrounded by several dozen stone pillars in the distance. Each pillar was so thick that a chain of seven or eight people would've been required to link hands around it, and they were quite spectacular to behold.

There were seven or eight other people on the plaza around the array, some of which were seated with their legs crossed, while others were standing.

The elderly man led the trio onto the plaza, then said to a middle-aged man who was also in Blaze Dragon Dao elder attire, "Elder Fu, these people are traveling to Extreme Ice Island as well. We have enough people, so we can activate the array now."

"Alright, you can all enter the array now," the middle-aged man said as he turned to the others on the plaza.

Those people had already been waiting for quite some time, and they were quite elated to hear this as they eagerly stepped into the array.

Han Li's trio immediately followed suit, and once all 10 people had entered the array, the elderly man gave the middle-aged man a nod, and the two of them strode over to the circular stone platforms on either side of the array before sitting down with their legs crossed.

Immediately thereafter, the two of them began to chant an incantation, and the white stone pillars around the array lit up one after another, while the spirit stones embedded onto the ground and the runes engraved there also began to radiate dazzling light.

The light quickly spread until all of the patterns on the ground had lit up, and all of the stone pillars situated elsewhere on the island also began to give off dazzling radiance as the entire island array was activated.

A faint buzzing sound rang out, and the entire island began to tremble violently.

Situated within the array, Han Li looked up at the sky to find that the clouds up above were churning violently, gradually forming an enormous hole, out of which was emanating powerful spatial fluctuations.

The mist enshrouding the outskirts of the island was also impacted by these spatial fluctuations, quickly receding to form a ring-shaped wall of mist around the island.

Right at this moment, a resounding boom rang out, and the entire island shuddered violently as a vast expanse of five-colored light erupted out of the array at the center of the island, forming a massive pillar of five-colored light that erupted straight into the heavens.

Han Li and the others were swallowed up by the five-colored light before instantly vanishing on the spot.

Shortly thereafter, the array gradually subsided, but the hole in the sky and the wall of mist around the island continued to linger.

……

In the northern region of the frozen sea, fierce winds were howling incessantly, while dark clouds hung low in the sky.

Snow was fluttering everywhere, encompassing the entire area of the sea.

On the dim surface of the sea, the frozen snow and seawater had been molded into giant ice spikes by the ferocious wind, and they were pointing diagonally up at the heavens.

Amid this forest of ice spikes was an ovular island that was enshrouded under an azure light barrier.

Right at this moment, a sound that resembled a rumbling thunderclap suddenly rang out high up in the sky, and the entire ovular island shuddered as a vast expanse of five-colored light appeared, following which Han Li and the others emerged on an array at the center of the island.

Due to the symptoms from ultra long-distance teleportation, everyone was looking rather pale, and the ones among them with the lowest cultivation bases were even feeling some instability in their souls.

As for Han Li, he merely felt a slight tightness in his chest, but that quickly subsided.

He took a glance at his surroundings to find that the layout of the area was much the same as the one on Smoke Tomb Island, except the white stone pillars around the array had been replaced by pillars of translucent ice.

Right at this moment, a cold voice rang out from outside the array. "The teleportation is complete, it's time for all of you to go."

Han Li turned to discover a thin elderly woman with a head of white hair. She was wearing a white cloak while holding a white horned dragon wood cane, and she was looking at everyone with an inhospitable expression.

Everyone hurriedly stepped out of the array before making their way toward the northern border of the island under the elderly woman's instructions.

There was a white hall of ice standing there, within which was a wide table with a benevolent-looking round-faced elderly man seated behind it.

In contrast with how cold and inhospitable the elderly woman was, the elderly man had a far more friendly appearance.

"Welcome to the Infernal Frost Continent, everyone. I'll be requiring all of you to submit a further three Immortal Origin Stones per person prior to leaving Extreme Ice Island," the elderly man said with a smile.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then turned to Qilin 9 with an inquisitive look in his eyes.

"This has always been the arrangement between the Blaze Dragon Dao and the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, and the same fee applies when we go back to Smoke Tomb Island," Qilin 9 explained.

Han Li nodded in response, but he couldn't help but feel a little speechless.

A one-way trip required 10 Immortal Origin Stones, so a return trip was going to require 20, which was more than the reward that he would receive from completing a low-level mission for the Transient Guild.

If it weren't for the fact that this fee was quite paltry compared with the handsome reward for this mission, there was no way that he would've been willing to accept this so easily.

After the Immortal Origin Stones had been submitted, everyone was directed to a door on the side of the hall.

The round-faced elderly man remained seated as he swept a sleeve through the air toward the door, and a burst of azure light appeared on its surface, following which a circular passageway that was as tall as a grown man emerged on the light barrier that encompassed the door.

"I wish you all safe and smooth journeys, fellow daoists," the elderly man said with a smile.

Qilin 9 led the way out of the door upon hearing this, arriving on the plaza outside the hall, followed closely by Han Li and Qilin 17.

After them came the other seven people who had also been teleported here.

As soon as they emerged from the hall, they were immediately met with heavy snow and a bone-chilling glacial aura. Han Li was already prepared for this, but his brows still furrowed slightly in an involuntary manner.

Looking at the snow-covered world before him, Han Li couldn't help but think back to when he first ascended to the Northern Glacial Immortal Region. At the time, he had also been in an extremely cold setting, and the glacial aura from that time seemed to have been even more potent.

He could still recall the excitement he had felt as if it had only happened yesterday, but to this day, he still couldn't recall anything that had happened after that.

The path of cultivation was one that was fraught with peril, and he couldn't help but wonder when he would be able to present himself in his true name without having to worry for his own safety.

His hands clenched up into tight fists as this thought sprang into his mind.

Chapter 244: Judgment

While Han Li was lost in his own thoughts, lights of different colors had begun to emerge from the bodies of many of the cultivators beside him. Some of them had jade pendants with warming effects tucked up their sleeves, some were wearing belts woven from fire-attribute materials, and some were wearing insulating spirit garments.

All of a sudden, a feral roar rang out, and a massive snow rhinoceros with an entirely white body emerged from the dense snowfall, whipping its head from side to side as it gave off a vicious aura.

One of the people in the group jumped onto the snow rhinoceros's back, and as he pressed his legs into the sides of the beast, it immediately began charging away.

A string of loud thumps rang out as the snow rhinoceros plowed its way straight through a series of ice spikes, traveling so quickly that it was as if it were in flight, and it didn't take long before it vanished into the distance.

Everyone else also summoned different types of snow and ice beasts before riding them away, and it didn't take long before Han Li's trio were the only ones left.

Qilin 9 swept his gaze across his surroundings for a moment, then summoned his Golden Veined Spirit Boat again, and the three of them jumped on before setting off toward the Infernal Frost Continent.

……

Around half a month later.

The snowstorm had just ceased in a region of the frozen sea, yet there was still a dense blanket of dark clouds in the sky, while gusts of bone-chilling wind were ravaing the surface of the sea.

The Golden Veined Spirit Boat that Han Li's trio was on was rapidly approaching the area, and inside the pavilion on the first floor, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed on his bed when all of a sudden, he felt a violent jolt run through the boat.

His eyes immediately sprang open as he rushed out of the room, where he saw an enormous black tentacle wrapped around the railing of the boat. The tentacle was stretched completely taut, seemingly doing everything in its power to drag the boat down into the sea below.

The boat was already beginning to tilt slightly, and Han Li looked down along the tentacle to find that a massive hole had opened up in the ice sheet covering the sea down below.

The tentacle belonged to an enormous scaled octopus with half of its body extending out of the hole, and the tentacle was continuing to constrict further and further, causing the entire boat to lurch slowly toward the sea down below.

All of a sudden, a furious roar rang out. "Insolence!"

A figure then shot out of the third-floor pavilion on the louchuan, transforming into a streak of golden light that flashed through the air before returning in an instant.

In the next instant, the tentacle wrapped around the railing of the boat was severed into pieces.

At the same time, the body of the giant black octopus also exploded violently, sending an enormous volume of black blood erupting in all directions, staining large sections of the surrounding ice black.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon seeing this. The octopus demon beast only possessed Grand Ascension Stage power and had limited intelligence, so it wasn't all that difficult to kill, but its scales were no ordinary scales, and it was far from a simple matter to bypass the defenses of those scales to instantly slay the beast.

This was a clear indication that Qilin 9 had most likely mastered some type of special law powers that granted him extremely formidable offensive prowess.

……

Over three months passed by in the blink of an eye.

There was an enormous snowy mountain range sprawled across the southern part of the Infernal Frost Continent, and there were countless branches extending out of the mountain range on either side, making it resemble an enormous frost centipede when viewed from above.

Every single branch of the mountain range was filled with enormous mountains that extended all the way up into the clouds, and all of them were almost entirely covered in snow and ice, with only some sections of exposed black rock visible on parts where the ice had slid off.

Above the mountain range was a picturesque blue sky, where the bright sun was hanging like a golden medallion, giving off warm and gentle light. However, the entire place was extremely cold and completely devoid of warmth.

To the east of one of the mountain range's southern branches were two mountains, both of which were over 10,000 feet tall. They were like a pair of silver longswords that were pointed directly up at the heavens, and nestled in between them was an extremely deep valley.

Outside the valley was a vast snowland that extended for tens of thousands of kilometers.

The snowland was riddled with countless massive cedar trees that were over 1,000 feet tall, but they were mostly inundated by a thick layer of snow, leaving only their tips exposed, but those tips were also covered by snow, thereby forming a series of white snowy pagodas.

Right at this moment, a string of dull roars suddenly rang out from within the snowland outside of the valley.

All of a sudden, a pair of furry white ears poked out from beneath the snow in the cedar forest to the northeast, and they swiveled around a few times to listen for surrounding sounds, then began to move toward the entrance of the valley.

A string of loud booms rang out incessantly in their wake as one massive tree after another was felled, sending massive flurries of snow erupting in all directions, and a deep and massive trench also appeared on the ground as a result.

The terrain seemed to have become more elevated closer to the entrance of the valley, and the owner of the pair of furry white ears gradually emerged from beneath the snow.

As it turned out, it was a massive snow rabbit that was over 100 feet tal, with a pair of slightly red eyes and tall ears.

Upon arriving at the entrance of the valley, it sprang forward forcefully with its hind legs, plunging itself straight into the valley up ahead.

A resounding boom rang out, and the snow rabbit was sent flying back before landing on its backside, as if it had just crashed into an invisible barrier.

After righting itself again, a ferocious look appeared in its eyes, and it let loose a low snarl before sinking back on its haunches to prepare to spring forward again. This time, it did so with several times more force than before, launching itself violently at the entrance of the valley.

All of a sudden, a faint golden light barrier appeared in the air within the entrance of the valley, and the light barrier was riddled with runes. A bolt of golden lightning that was around as thick as a human thumb abruptly sprang forth before striking the snow rabbit, and its entire body was instantly charred black before exploding violently, sending a charred odor wafting through the air.

At this moment, three figures emerged from within the deep trench in the cedar forest, then made their way toward the entrance of the valley.

This was none other than Han Li's trio, and Qilin 9 stopped in front of the entrance of the valley before turning to Han Li and Qilin 17 as he asked, "What do you think, fellow daoists?"

"If I'm not mistaken, the array here should be the Golden Peak Lightning Array that was passed down from ancient times. The bolt of lightning that had struck down that snow rabbit just now was nothing more than a display of but a tiny fraction of the array's power," Qilin 17 replied.

"I'm also of the opinion that this is the Golden Peak Lightning Array. According to my observation just now, the foundations of the array should be situated on the two mountains on either side. There should be at least two metal-attribute treasures at or above the spirit treasure caliber on those mountains, and the area encompassed within the array most likely includes those two mountains and the entire valley," Qilin 9 said with a nod.

Meanwhile, Han Li remained completely silent, seemingly contemplating something.

"Have you noticed something, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15?" Qilin 9 asked.

"I've never seen this Golden Peak Lightning Array before, but I have heard of it before. The array is renowned for combining resolute defenses with formidable offensive prowess, and once activated, it'll release a storm of golden lightning comparable in power to a small lightning tribulation. The bolt of lightning that the snow rabbit triggered just now was quite powerful, but it was also extremely restrained, which seems uncharacteristic of this array," Han Li said.

"That's just because that snow rabbit was too weak to trigger an all-out retaliation from the array. What's so surprising about that?" Qilin 17 dismissed with a disdainful expression.

"In that case, what do you think this array is?" Qilin 9 asked.

After a moment of contemplation, Han Li shook his head as he replied, "I've never encountered an array like this before, nor have I ever read about it, so I don't know its name, I just have a feeling that it's not as simple as it appears on the surface."

"If you've never even seen the Golden Peak Lightning Array before, then I suggest you keep your mouth shut. You said a bunch of stuff just now, but you may as well have said nothing at all," Qilin 17 scoffed.

Han Li remained unbothered by Qilin 17's rude remarks, paying no heed to him as he continued to focus his attention on the array.

"It seems like you're convinced that this is the Golden Peak Lightning Array, Fellow Daoist Qilin 17. Do you have any way for us to bypass the array without alerting the person inside?" Qilin 9 asked.

A thoughtful look appeared on Qilin 17's face as he replied, "Those two mountains are the cores of the array, and 81 lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood are used as the array's foundation. Generally speaking, all that needs to be done is to find a weakness in any of those two things, and the array can be easily unraveled.

“However, if we want to bypass the array without alerting the person inside, then we'll have to think of a way to assimilate ourselves with the array in order to avoid triggering it."

"In order to assimilate ourselves with the array, we must alter our own auras so that it matches the metal attribute of the array cores, or to match the lightning attribute of the array foundation. That'll allow us to enter the array without triggering it," Qilin 9 added.

"This process must be completed instantaneously. Otherwise, there's still a chance that the array could be triggered," Qilin 17 said as he took a glance at Han Li.

"Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15, if you haven't discovered anything else, then let's follow Fellow Daoist Qilin 17's plan," Qilin 9 said as he turned to Han Li.

"The method described by Fellow Daoist Qilin 17 would normally be correct, but what's strange about this array is the manner in which it releases lightning is very different from that of ordinary lightning arrays. The lightning is very concentrated and formidable, and if we were to enter the array without careful consideration, I don't think we'll fare any better than that snow rabbit," Han Li said with furrowed brows.

A hesitant look also flashed through Qilin 9's eyes upon hearing this.

His initial assessment of the lightning array had been quite similar to Qilin 17's, and the only reason he was willing to consider Han Li's input was due to the reputation that Han Li had recently forged for himself in the Transient Guild. Otherwise, he wouldn't have been hesitating at all.

Chapter 245: Entering the Valley

"We'll know if my method works or not when I test it out. You two can watch from the side, but in exchange, once we kill our target, I get to have the first pick out of all of their treasures," Qilin 17 said.

Before Han Li had a chance to say anything, Qilin 9 replied, "You seem to be very confident in your plan, Fellow Daoist Qilin 17. In that case, feel free to give it a try, but before that, we need to set up a spatial sealing array outside the array so the person inside isn't alerted to our arrival and runs away."

Han Li naturally had no objections to this, either, and after briefly discussing some further details, the three of them split up to perform their own roles.

Close to a day later, right as it was beginning to get dark, Han Li's trio met back up at the entrance of the valley.

Qilin 9 chanted an incantation, then pointed a finger at an array flag on the ground in front of him, and a layer of invisible ripples immediately surged through the air, forming a barely visible spherical light barrier that encompassed the entire nearby area in a radius of several hundred kilometers.

"Alright, the spatial sealing array has been activated. The floor is now yours, Fellow Daoist," Qilin 9 said as he turned to Qilin 17.

Qilin 17 nodded in response, then took a few steps forward until he was directly in front of the light barrier at the entrance of the valley before producing a shimmering golden talisman with a flick of his wrist.

He then raised the talisman before pressing it against his own forehead, and all of the runes on the talisman instantly lit up before flowing straight into his head.

What followed was a profound incantation, and arcs of golden lightning began to emerge all over Qilin 17's body amid a string of loud buzzing and crackling.

Immediately thereafter, his entire body abruptly blurred as he transformed into a thin arc of lightning and sped directly into the valley.

A faint pop rang out from the entrance of the valley, but that was the extent of the disturbance, and Qilin 17's was nowhere to be seen.

"It looks like this method works!" Qilin 9 remarked with an elated expression.

However, Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he looked up at the sky, and Qilin 9 hurriedly looked up as well, seemingly also having sensed that something wasn't quite right.

All of a sudden, a figure with golden lightning surging all over their body came plummeting rapidly out of the sky before slamming violently down onto the snowland with a resounding boom.

A massive crater instantly appeared on the snowland, and a vast expanse of golden lightning erupted forth from within, charring the surrounding cedar trees black.

Han Li and Qilin 9 rushed onto the scene to find Qilin 17 seated at the bottom of the crater. His entire body was charred black and releasing plumes of white smoke, giving him a rather sorry and comical appearance, but he didn't appear to have sustained any severe injuries.

"What happened, Fellow Daoist Qilin 17?" Qilin 9 asked.

"This restriction isn't the Golden Peak Lightning Array. To put it more accurately, it's not just the Golden Peak Lightning Array," Qilin 17 replied as he jumped out of the crater before flipping a hand over to produce a pill that he promptly devoured.

"I see, that makes sense," Han Li suddenly remarked.

"It sounds like you discovered something, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15," Qilin 9 said.

After a brief pause for contemplation, Han Li replied, "Back when that snow rabbit crashed into the array, I felt some hints of spatial fluctuations in the air. The way I see it, the array here is a special type of fusion array."

Qilin 17 arrived by Han Li's side, having already recovered from his injuries and changed into a set of new robes.

This time, he was no longer looking at Han Li with the same derision as before, and he asked, "So you're saying that this array is a combination of the Golden Peak Lightning Array and some type of spatial array?"

"That's right. While it's true that you managed to successfully bypass the array just now, in the instant that you entered the Golden Peak Lightning Array, you were immediately teleported back out by the spatial array inside," Han Li analyzed.

"In that case, the lightning released by the Golden Peak Lightning Array had to have been condensed by the same spatial array," Qilin 9 speculated.

"I presume that's the case. It's a good thing that Fellow Daoist Qilin 17 was fast enough to escape the brunt of the retaliation from the Golden Peak Lightning Array after he was expelled by the spatial array. Otherwise, his injuries would've most likely been far more severe," Han Li said as he took a glance at Qilin 17, and a grim look appeared on the latter's face upon hearing this.

"It seems like whoever's in this valley is doing something extremely important, and they're trying to keep out all possible distractions. Otherwise, they wouldn't have set up such a strange array here. With this array in place, not only is it difficult for outsiders to enter the valley, leaving the valley for those inside won't be a simple matter, either," Han Li mused.

After a brief silence, a cold look appeared in Qilin 9's eyes as he said, "If we can't sneak in in secret, then the only way to proceed would be to destroy the cores of the array and enter by force."

"Hold on a second, I have a method that could perhaps work," Han Li suddenly said.

"Go ahead, Fellow Daoist," Qilin 9 prompted.

"I just so happen to know a lightning array technique that combines the power of lightning with the power of space to achieve instantaneous teleportation. This array is also a fusion of the same two types of power, so as long as I can control the fluctuations of my array to the same level as those of this array, perhaps we'll be able to pass through it," Han Li explained.

"What would you say is the probability of this method succeeding?" Qilin 9 asked.

"The lightning array technique is not easy to control, so I'd say the chances of success are only around 50%," Han Li replied after some brief thought.

"Only 50%? So you're saying that there's a 50% chance that we'll come under retaliation from this lightning array?" Qilin 17 asked, clearly feeling rather hesitant.

After a moment of contemplation, Qilin 9 decided, "We'll go with Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15's method. Even if it fails, I'll keep the attacks from the lightning array at bay, and after that, we'll just have to force our way through the array after that."

Qilin 17 nodded in response after hearing this.

After the trio decided on a plan, Han Li arrived at the entrance of the valley, then closed his eyes as he released his spiritual sense, carefully sensing the spiritual power fluctuations from the array at the entrance of the valley.

A long while later, his eyes suddenly sprang open, and arcs of silver lightning appeared all over his body.

Immediately thereafter came a rumbling thunderclap, and the arcs of silver lightning sprang forth before intertwining with one another in mid-air to form a lightning array with a diameter in excess of 100 feet, encompassing both Qilin 9 and Qilin 17 as well.

"Please come a little closer to me, fellow daoists," Han Li said.

A peculiar look flashed through Qilin 9's eyes as he took a couple of steps closer to Han Li, and Qilin 17 also did the same.

In the next instant, Han Li brought his palms together in front of himself, and the lightning array around the trio instantly shrank down to only around 10 feet in size, while the arcs of lightning that were springing forth from the array were also significantly compressed.

Immediately thereafter, the lightning array around Han Li's trio vanished from the spot in the blink of an eye.

Almost at the exact same moment, several dozen thin bolts of golden lightning erupted from the invisible light barrier at the entrance of the valley, only to then instantly vanish without a trace as if nothing had ever happened.

Inside the valley, a vast expanse of silver lightning suddenly appeared high up in the sky, and Han Li's trio could be seen within the silver lightning, hurtling toward a nearby black cliff in an uncontrolled manner.

Han Li hurriedly withdrew his lightning as he tapped a foot against the cliff to launch himself backward, and he performed a somersault before drifting down onto the ground.

Qilin 9 and Qilin 17 were also able to stabilize themselves before making smooth descents.

Han Li heaved a long sigh of relief as he said, "The spatial power within this array is even more potent than I imagined, and I almost lost control of my lightning array."

"That's fine, all that matters is that we were able to successfully enter the valley," Qilin 9 said with a wave of his hand.

Han Li swept his gaze across his surroundings to find that the entire valley was riddled with scattered rocks, and there wasn't any snow to be seen. The only thing that was worthy of note was a building constructed from piled-up rocks at the center of the valley.

What was rather surprising to him was that the world's origin qi within the valley was extremely abundant, far more so than even most of the areas in the Bell Toll Mountain Range. Furthermore, there was smoke rising up from the top of the black stone hall, forming a cloud that was giving off five-colored light.

Han Li's trio exchanged a glance with one another before rising up into the air in unison and flying toward the stone hall.

At this moment, the stone hall was filled with scorching fire, and waves of heat were surging incessantly out of the skylight on top of the hall.

At the center of the hall was a golden pill cauldron that was around three feet tall, and it was hovering in mid-air.

An octagonal array had been engraved onto the ground below the pill cauldron, and the entire array was filled with countless fiery runes. Eight fiery dragons were extending out of these runes, carrying the golden pill cauldron and keeping it aloft.

Sweltering flames were surging incessantly out of the bodies and mouths of the fiery dragons, releasing tremendous heat upon the pill cauldron.

The ancient runes engraved onto the golden pill cauldron were flashing incessantly, serving to completely seal in the fragrances of the spirit medicines inside, as well as to constantly draw the surrounding world's origin qi into the cauldron.

Outside the fiery array was a white-haired elderly man wearing a purplish-golden robe and a lotus flower crown. At the moment, he was making a hand seal while controlling the eight fiery dragons beneath the pill cauldron.

The elderly man had a gaunt face with high cheekbones and deep-set eyes, which were staring intently at the pill cauldron before him. There was a fanatical gleam within his eyes, and he seemed to have been completely immersed in what he was doing, as if to him, the pill cauldron was the only thing that existed in this world.

All of a sudden, the flashing runes on the pill cauldron suddenly began to glow with dazzling radiance.

Almost at the exact same moment, the golden light radiating from the pill cauldron itself also turned into a combination of five different colors, and it seemed that some type of important change was taking place.

The look of excitement on the elderly man's face became even more pronounced upon seeing this, and he was constantly murmuring to himself, "Here it comes, here it comes..."

Right at this moment, two beams of golden light pierced through the sealed stone door of the stone hall.

A pair of loud clangs then rang out as the heavy stone door was split up into four chunks before falling into the hall.

Chapter 246: Nascent Incinerating Blood Pill

The white-haired elderly man immediately turned to discover three masked figures standing at the entrance of the stone hall.

They were led by a deer-masked figure that was holding a golden longsword, which was giving off dazzling golden light.

"Who are you?" the white-haired elderly man questioned with a cold expression.

Qilin 9 offered no response, merely slashing his golden longsword through the air with a cold smile on his face.

A sharp screeching sound rang out as a streak of golden swordlight erupted out of the sword, sweeping directly toward the white-haired elderly man.

Instead of taking evasive measures, the elderly man threw himself in front of the pill cauldron without any hesitation.

He then swept a sleeve through the air to release a purplish-golden lightning serpent that was around 10 feet in length, which clashed against the golden swordlight with a rumbling thunderclap.

The purplish-golden lightning serpent instantly exploded into countless tiny arcs of lightning that sprang forth in all directions, while the golden swordlight was also destroyed, split up into countless tiny fragments that flew through the surrounding air.

A string of loud booms rang out incessantly as countless chunks of rock flew in all directions, and the entire stone hall was instantly destroyed.

Before the dust settled, another streak of swordlight arrived, and this time, it was Han Li who had sprung into action.

He was holding a silver flying sword, and he launched himself up into the air before slashing the sword directly down upon the white-haired elderly man.

This flying sword was something that he had obtained during a Transient Guild mission, and it was a treasure that had been forged with Galactic Astral Silver as its main material. Of course, it couldn't even begin to compare with his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, but given his suspicions that Qilin 9 could be Xiong Shan, it was naturally a good idea to keep his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords hidden.

Furthermore, he possessed the lowest cultivation base out of the trio, so he didn't want to display too much power.

He had already made a contribution by getting the three of them into the valley, so the Qilin 9 and Qilin 17 couldn't really say anything even if he were to hold back a little here.

The silver flying sword began to radiate dazzling light as it released hundreds of silver sword projections, forming a massive silver waterfall that came cascading down upon the white-haired elderly man.

The elderly man let loose a low roar as he raised a hand before spreading his fingers open, and a thumb-sized bead that he was holding in his hand instantly swelled to countless times its original size, transforming into a golden shield that positioned itself above his head.

At the same time, a purplish-golden whip appeared in his other hand, using which he lashed out violently to his left.

A string of loud clangs rang out incessantly from the golden shield overhead, and golden light flashed incessantly as a dense web of cracks appeared on its surface, but it was able to just barely keep all of the oncoming sword projections at bay.

On the other side, a loud thunderclap rang out from the elderly man's lightning whip, and a pair of formidable purplish-golden lightning serpents sprang forth toward Qilin 9, keeping him at bay as well.

Right at this moment, a burst of spatial fluctuations suddenly emerged above the elderly man's head, and Qilin 17 appeared in a wraith-like manner, holding a black spear with both hands, which he plunged down toward the elderly man from above.

All of a sudden, the scorching flame beneath the five-colored cauldron began to churn violently, and a fiery dragon abruptly sprang out from within before pouncing toward Qilin 17, bringing with it a scorching wave of heat.

Qilin 17 immediately adjusted the course of his attack, sweeping his spear through the air instead of continuing to plunge it down directly from above. In doing so, he conjured up a vast expanse of black spear projections that swept toward the fiery dragon.

The spear projections and the fiery dragon exploded in unison upon contact, resulting in a blinding eruption of crimson and black light.

This appeared to have been quite a lengthy process, but in reality, all of this had taken place in the blink of an eye.

The white-haired elderly man had withstood the attacks from Han Li's trio head-on without taking even a single step backward, and he was still resolutely defending the pill cauldron behind him.

Qilin 17 sprang back and descended onto the ground several thousand feet away, having avoided the shockwaves from the explosion that had just taken place, and a cold smile appeared on his face as he flipped his black spear around in an elegant manner before plunging its tip straight into the ground.

The white-haired elderly man held his lightning whip in one hand while his other hand was clasped behind his back, and there was a wary look in his eyes as he inspected the trio before him.

He had already stowed away the golden shield that had been severely damaged by Han Li's sword projections, and his spare hand was concealed up his sleeve, holding onto a a golden talisman that had slid discreetly into his grasp.

Han Li's gaze was fixed intently on the elderly man, and as soon as the latter opened his mouth, Han Li immediately lashed out once again, slashing his silver longsword through the air to release another barrage of several hundred silver sword projections that hurtled directly toward the elderly man.

After flying several hundred feet through the air, all of the sword projections abruptly split up into countless tiny streaks of sword qi that encompassed the white-haired elderly man's entire body from all directions.

The elderly man could only cease his chanting for now as he retaliated with his lightning whip.

A burst of purplish-golden lightning erupted from the lightning whip, accompanied by a draconic roar. Immediately thereafter, the purplish-golden lightning swelled drastically in size, transforming into purplish-golden lightning dragon that was several thousand feet in length, whipping its tail violently through the air as it twisted and thrashed from side to side.

A string of rumbling thunderclaps rang out as all of the sword qi hurtling toward the purplish-golden lightning dragon was eradicated.

A large chunk of the lightning on the surface of the purplish-golden dragon had also been exhausted, but the elderly man immediately made a string of hand seals, and the purplish-golden lightning dragon was instantly restored to the peak of its powers as it pounced viciously at Han Li.

Han Li feigned a panicked expression as he shot back in retreat, and right at this moment, a streak of golden swordlight that was over 1,000 feet in length came crashing down with unstoppable force, imbued with a burst of peerlessly sharp metal-attribute law powers.

The sword qi erupting from the streak of sword light split all of the clouds in the sky apart, forming a massive rift.

The wielder of the sword was naturally none other than Qilin 9, and at this moment, he was hovering high up in the sky, basked in a layer of golden light. Furthermore, his entire body was giving off an indescribably sharp aura, as if he were the embodiment of a peerlessly sharp sword.

Han Li continued to fly back in retreat while looking up at Qilin 9, and at this moment, it was confirmed to him beyond a reasonable doubt that this person was indeed Xiong Shan.

As the streak of golden swordlight descended from above, the white-haired elderly man raised his hands up into the air with all his might, and the purplish-golden lightning dragon temporarily abandoned its pursuit of Han Li as it flew up to oppose the streak of golden swordlight.

A dull clang rang out, and the purplish-golden lightning dragon was split into two down the middle by the streak of golden swordlight, and it exploded into a vast net of purple lightning.

The golden swordlight wasn't destroyed in the clash, but its power had been significantly diminished, and it was unable to descend any further with the purple lightning net standing in its way.

Right as the white-haired elderly man was about to do something else, the ground behind him suddenly shuddered, and a massive rift appeared, immediately following which a black spear shot out from within before crashing heavily into the pill cauldron.

A resounding clang reverberated throughout the entire stone hall, causing the surrounding space to ripple and quiver.

The pill cauldron was instantly sent flying by the spear strike, hurtling through the air before crashing down onto the ground over 1,000 feet away, only coming to a rest after rolling quite a distance away.

It was unclear what type of material the cauldron was forged from, but its surface remained completely unscathed in the face of the attack. However, the five-colored light radiating from it receded after flashing a few times, and it reverted back to its original golden color.

It was clear that the elderly man had been prioritizing the safety of the pill cauldron above all else, so Qilin 17 decided that it would be a good idea to destroy the cauldron in order to distract the elderly man, thereby creating an opportunity for Han Li and Qilin 9 to strike. This was why he had plunged his spear into the ground earlier, and his plan had worked flawlessly.

The elderly man instantly turned around, and as soon as he caught sight of the golden pill cauldron that had fallen onto the ground, a look of heart-wrenching fury and despair instantly appeared as he let loose a guttural roar.

"NO..."

Han Li and the others were quite taken aback by such a vehement reaction, and they were momentarily rooted to the spot.

"You've ruined tens of thousands of years of work! All of you must die!"

The resentment in the elderly man's eyes was becoming more and more ferocious, and it was as if he had lost all capacity for rational thought.

He flipped a hand over to produce a dark red pill, which he placed into his own mouth, but instead of swallowing it right away, he gnashed the pill into mush between his teeth before devouring it.

A sense of foreboding welled up in Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and Qilin 9's expression suddenly changed drastically as he yelled in alarm, "That's a Nascent Incinerating Blood Pill!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, the elderly man began to chuckle in a harrowing, inhuman voice, and his skin gradually began to darken, quickly turning into a dark red shade that resembled raw pig liver.

At the same time, his sunken eyes began brighter and brighter, and there were even glimmers of golden light shining through.

Qilin 9 rushed back over 1,000 feet in the blink of an eye as he cautioned, "Look out, fellow daoists! He's just taken a restricted pill that can ignite one's nascent soul and blood essence in unison to significantly elevate the consumer's cultivation base for a short time. With the aid of that pill, there's a chance that he could even reach the Golden Immortal Stage!"

Han Li and Qilin 17 also hurriedly rushed back in retreat upon hearing this.

All of a sudden, a strange sound rang out, and wisps of faint red steam began to rise up from the elderly man's body, giving him the appearance of a steamed crab.

Immediately thereafter, the elderly man abruptly vanished from the spot amid the sound of rushing wind, and all that was left in his place was a cloud of red mist that began to slowly drift upward.

In the next instant, a figure suddenly appeared directly in front of Qilin 17 several thousand feet away, and the figure raised a fist before lashing out at Qilin 17's face with ferocious power.

Qilin 17 was caught completely off guard, and he only had time to raise a hand to shield his own face.

A resounding thump rang out, and Qilin 17 felt as if a mountain had crashed straight into the palm of his hand. His hand wasn't able to act as much of a buffer at all before it crashed heavily into his masked face, and he was sent flying back like a cannon ball before craashing heavily into a black cliff over 10,000 feet away.

A resounding boom rang out as the mountain that was tens of thousands of feet tall instantly exploded. Chunks of giant rocks the size of houses flew through the air in all directions as the mountain was instantly toppled.

Chapter 247: Avoiding Direct Confrontation

Before the dust even had a chance to settle, Han Li felt a blur flash before his eyes, and the white-haired elderly man instantly appeared before him, moving at an extraordinary speed.

Han Li immediately reflexively raised his arms, and he only just had enough time to cross them to form a barrier in front of himself before he was sent flying back by a tremendously powerful punch.

Thankfully, he had already conjured up his True Extreme Membrane, as well as a layer of golden scales over his arms, so he was able to ward off the attack better than Qilin 17 did, but even so, he was still sent flying back several thousand feet before managing to steady himself.

Even though the white-haired elderly man had managed to send Han Li flying, he also stumbled back a step himself, and a hint of surprise flashed through his eyes.

Immediately thereafter, Qilin 9 came swooping in with his sword, and the elderly man let loose a thunderous roar as he lashed out with his fists.

At this point, his skin had already gradually turned from a dark red color into a bright red hue, and the steam that was rising up from his body had also turned a shade of light pink.

Accompanying this change was an increase in his speed and power, and with every single punch that he threw, a loud boom would ring out in the air from the sheer force of his blows.

Qilin 9 was slashing his golden sword repeatedly through the air, while the white-haired elderly continued to fight with his bare fists, and each punch struck the edge of the golden sword's blade with tremendous force, resulting in a string of deafening booms.

The two of them were constantly changing positions, and the clashes between fists and sword sent bursts of invisible law fluctuations erupting through the air, destroying everything in the surrounding area and even carving out giant craters into the ground.

Qilin 9's swordsmanship was nothing short of exceptional, but in the face of the ridiculously fast and powerful elderly man, he was struggling to hold his own.

"All of you must die!" the white-haired elderly man roared, and his fists blurred as around a dozen identical fist projections appeared in the air before hurtling toward Qilin 9 with immense power.

Qilin 9 didn't have any time to think, and he gripped onto the hilt of his sword with both hands as a ball of dazzling light suddenly appeared at the tip of the sword. The ball of light was rapidly becoming brighter and brighter, and it swelled to several dozen feet in size before flying through the air and exploding violently.

Countless streaks of golden sword qi were sent sweeping through the air, crashing into the oncoming fist projections to produce a string of sharp metallic screeching noises.

However, to Qilin 9's surprise, almost all of the streaks of sword qi were instantly destroyed, but the fist projections weren't completely eradicated.

Immediately thereafter, a vast expanse of golden light emerged from his body to form a protective barrier in front of him.

Right at this moment, a slightly disheveled Qilin 17 abruptly flew out of a nearby giant crater, and with a flick of his wrist, a yellow rope flew out of his sleeve.

The length of rope was writhing around in mid-air like a spirit snake, and it formed seven or eight loops in the blink of an eye before flying toward the white-haired elderly man.

A string of resounding booms rang out, and the golden light around Qilin 9 shuddered violently as he was sent flying back through the air. The white-haired elderly man was about to charge forward and press his advantage, but he was caught in the loops of the yellow rope, which instantly constricted to completely bind him.

Qilin 17 was holding onto one end of the rope with one hand, and with a forceful wrenching motion, the elderly man was forcibly dragged toward him.

At the same time, Han Li popped up out of nowhere with his silver longsword raised, and he pierced the tip of the sword directly toward the elderly man's head.

Golden light flashed within the elderly man's eyes as a burst of muffled chanting rang out from within his mouth.

In the next instant, bright crimson light erupted all over his entire body, and the skin and flesh on his arms split open to reveal the bones underneath, which were still covered in a layer of pink fascia, and he was able to slice through the yellow rope with his bones to free himself as if they were sharp blades.

Immediately thereafter, he raised an arm and swept his blade-like bones toward the nearby Han Li.

The tip of Han Li's silver longsword struck the elderly man's bones to produce an extremely unpleasant screeching sound.

Han Li felt a burst of tremendous force surging toward him, and he immediately made the decision not to fight fire with fire, allowing himself to be sent flying back instead.

Even though the white-haired elderly man had lost some of his capacity for rational thought, he was still rather taken aback to see Han Li being blown back so easily. However, a thought then seemed to have occurred to him, and he abruptly turned around before pouncing at Qilin 17, who was still holding one end of the yellow rope.

In the blink of an eye, he appeared directly behind Qilin 17, then plunged the blade-like bones of his arms through several layers of protective light barriers with ease before piercing straight through Qilin 17's chest, creating a gaping hole that blood instantly began to gush out of.

Qilin 17's entire body arched back violently as a huge mouthful of blood gushed out from beneath his mask, but immediately thereafter, a burst of white light erupted from his waist, sending his entire body plummeting rapidly downward before slamming violently into the ground.

The white light then faded to reveal Qilin 17 laying on the ground in a completely still manner, and it was unclear whether he was dead or alive.

The white-haired elderly man cackled in a harrowing voice, and he paid no further heed to Qilin 17 as he turned a cold gaze to Han Li, who had already retreated to several thousand feet away.

Meanwhile, Han Li was watching the unfolding scene with a grim expression.

The elderly man appeared to have been quite a powerful Profound Immortal, and after devouring that Nascent Incinerating Blood Pill, his powers had been enhanced to an extreme degree. If Han Li had chosen to fight fire with fire just now, he would've most likely sustained severe injuries.

At this point, the elderly man's eyes had already turned completely golden in color, and there was no longer even the slightest hint of rationality within them.

This was a Profound Immortal who possessed power close to the Golden Immortal Stage and had lost all capacity for rational thought. It was no wonder that Qilin 17 was no match for him.

All of a sudden, the elderly man vanished from the spot in a flash.

Han Li didn't hesitate in the slightest as he shot back in retreat while a layer of golden scales appeared over both of his arms, and he raised a fist before throwing a punch directly forward.

A resounding boom rang out as his fist clashed violently with that of the white-haired elderly man, who had suddenly appeared in front of him.

A burst of invisible shockwaves instantly erupted forth in all directions like an almighty wave, causing the surrounding space to shudder violently while loose rocks were sent flying in all directions.

Han Li felt a burst of tremendous force surging toward him, and he was sent flying back several thousand feet, only coming to a rest after crashing into a pulverizing a black cliff face behind him.

The white-haired elderly man was also sent flying back, but only for about 2,000 to 3,000 feet before he managed to steady himself.

"I didn't think you were also a Profound Immortal, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15. Having said that, do not oppose him directly. Instead, I'll set up an array to trap him, and you can lure him in once it's ready. At this point, he's already lost his sanity, so once the blood essence and nascent soul in his body is incinerated to nothingness, he'll drop dead on his own," Qilin 9 called out to Han Li as he hovered high up in the air.

Han Li took a moment to catch his breath, then replied, "Try to set up the array as soon as possible, Fellow Daoist Qilin 9. I can't guarantee that I'll be able to keep him occupied for long."

After that, he sprang up into the air before hurling the longsword in his hand forward.

The silver longsword flew through the air as it began to radiate dazzling silver light, and a circle of dense sword projections appeared around it, resembling a lotus flower that was blooming in mid-air.

Han Li then began to chant an incantation while pointing a finger downward, and a rapid string of silver sword projections instantly came raining down from above, completely inundating the white-haired elderly man that had only just emerged from a cliff face.

A string of rumbling booms rang out incessantly within the valley as dust and rock fragments flew in all directions, quickly concealing the elderly man's body.

All of a sudden, an animalistic roar rang out, and the white-haired elderly man sprang out of the cloud of dust.

All of the skin on his entire body was riddled with crimson cracks, while his long white hair, which had previously been bound up in a tight bun, was now dancing wildly around him in the wind, giving him the appearance of a ferocious devilish creature.

His arms were crossed to form a barrier to protect his face, and he plowed his way straight through the barrage of silver sword projections before crashing into the silver sword lotus flower.

The silver sword lotus flower instantly exploded into a flurry of silver sword projections that erupted froth in all directions, and the silver longsword that was situated at its center was also snapped into two.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and the muscles on his scaled arms bulged as he lashed out with his fists.

Meanwhile, on the other side of the valley, Qilin 9 was holding a golden staff that was around the same thickness as a grown man's arm, and he quickly strode over to a rock before plunging the staff forcefully downward.

There were countless runes engraved over the entire staff, which was around 30 feet in length, and around two-thirds of it was plunged into the earth, leaving only around the top 10 feet left exposed above the ground.

Qilin 9 took a glance at his surroundings to find that a circular array formed by golden staves had already taken shape, and there were two openings in the array, one to the east and one to the west.

"The array is ready, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15!" Qilin 9 yelled as he turned to Han Li.

Han Li immediately twisted around before flying toward the array, and having completely lost all sanity, the white-haired elderly man pounced after Han Li without any hesitation, hurtling through the air at an even higher speed than Han Li's.

Han Li had only just reached the edge of the array when the white-haired elderly man caught up to him, and the latter instantly plunged the bone blade on the outer edge of his arm straight at the back of Han Li's chest.

Right at this moment, a sharp screeching sound rang out as a golden longsword shot out of Han Li's body, clashing with the elderly man's bone blade to raise a flurry of golden sparks.

The elderly man was stopped cold in his tracks, situated directly above the array.

At the same time, Qilin 9 hurled a golden staff at Han Li with a flick of his wrist as he yelled, "Catch!"

Han Li instantly swooped down to catch the golden staff, then turned and plunged it straight into the ground where one of the openings of the array was situated, and almost at the exact same moment, Qilin 9 plunged another staff into the ground at the other opening.

A faint buzzing sound rang out as a burst of invisible fluctuations rose up within the array, and all of the runes on the golden staves began to radiate dazzling golden light. A series of shimmering golden chains then rose up from the ground before binding themselves tightly around the white-haired elderly man.

White mist was rising up from the white-haired elderly man's entire body, and he began to struggle and thrash violently in mid-air.

The dozen or so golden staves that were known as Dragon Locking Staves began to sway unsteadily in the face of the white-haired elderly man's tremendous power, resembling saplings in a ferocious storm that could snap at any moment, but they were somehow just barely able to hold on.

Chapter 248: Final Blow

Han Li heaved a slight sigh of relief upon seeing this, then turned to Qilin 9 as he asked, "Fellow Daoist Qilin 9, how much longer do you think he'll be able to last?"

"His blood essence has already been incinerated from his organs to his flesh, and from his bones to his skin, so he should be a completely spent force soon. All we need to do is wait another 15 minutes," Qilin 9 replied.

Right at this moment, Qilin 17, who had been laying still on the ground this entire time, suddenly spasmed a few times before getting up into a seated position, seemingly with great difficulty.

The bright red flesh around the hole in his chest was slowly squirming as it fused back together, and only after the hole was completely sealed did he heave a long sigh of relief with a look of lingering fear in his eyes.

"That was way too close! I almost died here..."

Han Li and Qilin 9 exchanged a glance, and both of them could see their own derision mirrored in one another's eyes, but neither of them bothered to say anything. After all, the mission was going to be over soon, so they wouldn't have to put up with Qilin 17 for much longer.

Qilin 17 naturally noticed this brief interaction, and he had no intention of immediately joining Han Li and Qilin 9. Instead, he flew over to the rubble that was once the stone hall, then began to search through the wreckage.

With a sweep of his sleeve, a section of loose rocks was swept aside to reveal the pill cauldron down below, and he crouched down to pick it up.

"Don't you dare!"

The white-haired elderly man who was trapped in the array seemed to have spotted Qilin 17, and he threw his head back before letting loose a thunderous roar.

The octagonal array on the ground that had been snuffed out earlier abruptly lit up once again, and scorching flames erupted forth to form eight fiery dragons that flew directly toward the white-haired elderly man.

Han Li's trio was greatly alarmed by this sudden turn of events, and they hurriedly tried to intercept the fiery dragons, but it was already too late.

The eight fiery dragons surged straight into the elderly man's abdomen before vanishing into his body.

The crimson coloration of his body instantly became even more pronounced, and it was as if there were molten lava flowing within the cracks on his body, giving him an extremely terrifying appearance.

Most importantly, his aura had swelled drastically once again, and he had broken through to the Golden Immortal Stage.

He reached out with both hands to grab onto the golden chains around him, then tugged on them forcefully, and all of the surrounding Dragon Locking Staves were instantly uprooted before being swung at Han Li and Qilin 9.

The two of them naturally didn't dare to fight fire with fire, and they hurriedly flew back in retreat.

In just a single stride, the white-haired elderly man was able to reach Qilin 17 before throwing a punch directly at his head.

The speed displayed in that single stride had been downright ridiculous, and it was as if the space between him and Qilin 17 had been compressed. There was no time for Qilin 17 to take evasive measures, so he could only raise both hands to summon a glowing yellow flag to protect himself, while a white light barrier also surfaced over his body.

The yellow flag was clearly no ordinary treasure, and there was an image of the almighty beast Baxia with a stone monument on its back emblazoned upon it. The Baxia was so life-like that it was as if it could spring out of the flag at any moment, and it was giving off an extremely powerful earth-attribute aura.

As soon as the flag was unfurled, it was struck by the white-haired elderly man's fist, and all of the surrounding space in a radius of over 100 feet collapsed violently.

However, despite the fact that the flag appeared to have next to no structural integrity, it merely rippled incessantly in the face of the white-haired elderly man's fist, but wasn't instantly torn apart.

However, it was only able to last a brief moment before the Baxia image emblazoned upon it crumbled away, immediately following which the entire flag was torn to shreds.

Taking advantage of this opportunity, Qilin 17 rolled to the side to take evasive measures, but he was still struck by the residual shockwaves from the blow, and the white light barrier around his body was instantly shattered, while he was sent flying through the air with blood gushing out of his mouth.

The white-haired elderly man didn't skip a beat as he caught up to Qilin 17 in an instant before throwing another punch at his head.

All of this had taken place so fast that even if Han Li and Qilin 9 wanted to save him, they simply wouldn't have been in time to do so.

Qilin 17 was cursing his own impatience, thinking to himself that he should've played dead for a while longer instead of being in such a hurry to secure the pill cauldron.

In a state of panic, he swiveled around and grabbed onto the ears of the golden pill cauldron, then raised it up high in front of him as a shield.

The white-haired elderly man's fist came hurtling through the air, yet right as it was about to strike the pill cauldron, a hint of reluctance appeared in his golden eyes, and he stopped his own fist dead in its tracks.

Qilin 17's eyes were tightly shut, and his entire body was drenched in cold sweat. He thought that his fate was sealed, but to his surprise, the final blow didn't come.

He carefully opened his eyes to find that the white-haired elderly man's entire body was completely wrecked, and he was standing in a completely motionless manner with his fist still outstretched in front of him.

There were still some specks of crimson light glowing within the cracks on his body, resembling the dying embers of a flame, but it was clear that his body was already completely devoid of life.

Han Li strode over to the elderly man's remains, and a myriad of emotions welled up in his heart.

It was unclear whether the elderly man had failed to deliver the final blow as he had exhausted all of his blood essence and nascent soul, or because he was unwilling to smash his prized pill cauldron.

Right as Han Li's trio heaved a collective sigh of relief, a glimmer of barely detectable golden light suddenly appeared in the white-haired elderly man's lifeless eyes, as if there were still a final hint of vitality in his body.

A sense of foreboding immediately welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this, but before he could do anything, an azure talisman suddenly flew out of the white-haired elderly man's sleeve.

With the emergence of that talisman, the final glimmer of golden light in his eyes completely faded, while the talisman flew through the air as a streak of azure light, instantly covering a distance of several thousand feet, immediately following which it began to release a flurry fo countless tiny golden runes in a frenzy.

It was a talisman that had been entirely inscribed using golden seal text, and in the next instant, all of the runes began to release countless rays of dazzling azure light.

All of the azure light converged in mid-air to form a sea of azure light that was blindingly bright, and a rumbling thunderclap rang out in the air, following which the sky above the valley was instantly concealed behind a dense blanket of dark clouds.

It was as if the entire world had been plunged into darkness with the exception of this sea of azure light.

All of the world's origin qi within a radius of thousand of kilometers converged toward the valley from all directions before fusing into the sea of azure light, causing it to churn violently like a turbulent wave.

Faint threads of azure light emerged from the center of the sea of light, then intertwined to form an azure figure clad in a suit of armor with a solemn look on his face.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and as soon as the azure figure appeared, he immediately took a glance at the remains of the white-haired elderly man down below before lashing out with an enraged expression.

A burst of azure light emerged from the palm of his hand, then split up into three thin azure threads that hurtled toward Han Li's trio at an incredible speed.

The space in the wake of the azure threads instantly became twisted and warped, and countless specks of azure light converged from all directions from all of the vegetation within the entire valley. With the emergence of these specks of azure light, all of the surrounding plants instantly wilted away.

The countless specks of azure light gathered around the three azure threads, which instantly transformed into three balls of azure light, each of which was around a foot in size. Countless azure runes were dancing on the surfaces of these balls of light, and they were giving off incredibly destructive law fluctuations.

All of the space in the wake of the balls of azure light trembled and warped violently, and numerous white spatial rifts appeared, releasing astonishing suction force that threatened to collapse the entire space.

Han Li immediately shot back in retreat, only for the ball of azure light to accelerate even further and catch up to him in a flash before crashing down with tremendous force.

Han Li was quite alarmed, but remained composed, and he conjured up his True Extreme Membrane while raising both hands to summon his Heavy Water True Axis, which instantly swelled to several dozen times its original size, forming a massive shield before him.

The azure ball of light crashed into the Heavy Water True Axis with an earth-shattering boom, and Han Li felt his entire body being jolted by a burst of devastating force, sending both him and the Heavy Water True Axis flying back for over 10,000 feet before he just barely managed to steady himself.

Having been fed so much heavy water by Han Li over the years, the Heavy Water True Axis had become as heavy as several mountains combined, and it had also been imbued with a great deal of water law powers, making it no lesser in power than a decent Acquired Immortal Treasure.

The ball of azure light had sent Han Li flying, but it had also disintegrated into countless specks of azure light itself.

Even so, Han Li was still stunned by the power of the ball of azure light, which far exceeded that of the attacks unleashed by the late-True Immortal cultivators that he had come across in the past.

He turned his gaze to the Heavy Water True Axis in front of him, and much to his dismay, he discovered that a faint mark had appeared on its surface, indicating that spiritual nature seemed to have been harmed.

Han Li hurriedly injected his immortal spiritual power into the Heavy Water True Axis, and the Water Dao Rune on its surface flashed momentarily as the mark on the axis quickly vanished.

Only then did he allow himself to heave a sigh of relief.

Meanwhile, Qilin 9 and Qilin 17 had also been sent flying, but they possessed superior cultivation bases to Han Li, and thanks to their treasures, they were also able to withstand the blows from the balls of azure light without much trouble.

Qilin 17 had summoned a turtle-shell-shaped shield with an extremely life-like demon beast that had the head of a dragon and the body of a turtle engraved onto its surface. The shield was flashing with spiritual light, and it appeared to have been quite a remarkable treasure.

However, a clear mark had been inflicted onto the shield, much to Qilin 17's anguish and chagrin.

As for Qilin 9, the golden flying sword in his hand had already disappeared, and instead, there was a golden millstone hovering in front of him. The millstone's surface was riddled with countless tiny golden runes, and had an extremely heavy and sturdy appearance.

A hint of surprise appeared on his face as he caught sight of Han Li's Heavy Water True Axis, but he then immediately composed himself and withdrew his gaze as if he hadn't noticed anything.

The change in Qilin 9's expression had only lasted an instant, but it hadn't managed to escape Han Li's notice.

Judging from Qilin 9's reaction, Han Li couldn't help but wonder if he had seen this Heavy Water True Axis before.

With that in mind, Han Li unconsciously became even more wary of Qilin 9.

Chapter 249: Making an Enemy Out of the Immortal Palace

After the azure figure forced back Han Li's trio, he didn't press his advantage. Instead, he descended beside the body of the white-haired elderly man, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light that enveloped the lifeless body, seemingly trying to save him.

However, the white-haired elderly man's soul had already been completely destroyed, leaving only a spent husk behind, and he was as dead as dead could be.

The azure figure turned to Han Li's trio with a look of thunderous rage on his face as he roared, "How dare you Transient Guild bastards come after members of our Immortal Palace!"

Han Li's heart jolted slightly upon hearing this, and he turned to Qilin 9 as he asked, "What's going on here, Fellow Daoist Qilin 9?"

Qilin 17 also turned to Qilin 9 with an accusatory look on his face.

"Please don't misunderstand, fellow daoists, I wasn't aware of this, either, and I can assure you that I didn't try to intentionally deceive you. The person who released the mission never revealed the identity of our target to me," Qilin 9 said with a sullen look on his face.

Han Li carefully observed Qilin 9's expression, and after determining that he didn't seem to have been lying, he immediately withdrew his gaze as he contemplated how to proceed.

In the face of such a formidable foe, he couldn't afford to panic.

Right at this moment, the azure figure made a hand seal, and bright azure light surfaced over his body alongside a series of azure patterns.

All of the specks of azure light that were the scattered remains of the three balls of azure light instantly converged toward him in a frenzy before surging into the azure patterns on his skin, causing him to swell drastically in stature to over 1,000 feet feet tall in the blink of an eye.

Han Li's trio immediately swept their spiritual sense over the azure-armored giant before them, and all three of them were extremely alarmed by what they detected.

The aura that the giant was giving off wasn't inferior in the slightest compared with that of the elderly man after he had consumed the Nascent Incinerating Blood Pill. In fact, the giant's aura was slightly more powerful in comparison, and the hearts of Han Li's trio immediately sank upon detecting this.

"This is Spiritual Origin Restoration! Look out, fellow daoists, we're dealing with an avatar of a Golden Immortal!" Qilin 9 exclaimed.

Han Li already suspected this to be the case, but he was still quite alarmed to have had his suspicions confirmed.

Having already been a member of the Blaze Dragon Dao for many years, he had accumulated a great deal of knowledge, and he had learned that one of the most prominent abilities of a Golden Immortal was Spiritual Origin Restoration.

Golden Immortals possessed far superior control over immortal spiritual power than True Immortals, and they were able to recover their spiritual power that was scattered during the course of battle, thereby significantly reducing their immortal spiritual power expenditure.

Judging from the powers that the azure figure had displayed thus far, he was clearly a Golden Immortal who had mastered some type of wood-attribute laws, allowing him to draw upon the wood-attribute spiritual qi in the surrounding area to unleash his attacks. If they were powerless to stop him from recycling his immortal spiritual power over and over again, then they would be in a world of trouble.

Right as these thoughts were running through their minds, the azure-armored giant pounced forward at an extraordinary speed despite its enormous frame, reaching Han Li's trio in the blink of an eye before slamming a giant fist straight down upon Qilin 9.

A burst of invisible fluctuations erupted forth amid a rumbling boom, and immensely powerful law fluctuations swept through the surrounding area like gusts of ferocious wind.

Instead of flying back in retreat, Qilin 9 made a hand seal, and the golden millstone in front of him began to glow brightly as it instantly swelled to the size of a small mountain, revolving rapidly as it rose up to meet the azure-armored giant's fist.

An earth-shattering boom rang out, accompanied by an explosion of golden and azure light, and the golden millstone was sent flying, as was Qilin 9.

However, the golden millstone was also quite a powerful treasure, and the repulsion force from the clash forced the azure-armored giant back a few steps, while the azure light radiating from hi fist also dimmed slightly. However, the azure patterns on his arm lit up once again, and all of the scattered azure light began to surge back to him.

Before he had a chance to fully recover, Han Li and Qilin 17 abruptly appeared on either side of the azure-armored giant.

Han Li's Heavy Water True Axis expanded even further at his behest, swelling to the size of a house, and it began to revolve rapidly while giving off tremendous law power fluctuations.

Immediately thereafter, the Heavy Water True Axis came crashing down toward the azure-armored giant as a streak of black light.

Meanwhile, Qilin 17 was making a series of hand seals before summoning a square seal that was giving off an earthy yellow glow. A yellow dragon was coiled on top of the seal, giving it hte appearance of an imperial jade seal from a mortal empire.

Qilin 17 quickly chanted an incantation before pressing his palm forward, and the yellow seal instantly swelled to countless times its original size.

A giant yellow dragon projection also emerged within the blinding yellow light around it, and it came crashing down upon the azure-armored giant.

Thanks to their earlier battle against the white-haired elderly man, the three of them had developed a decent amount of chemistry.

The azure-armored giant remained completely unfazed as he reached out with both hands, grabbing toward both the Heavy Water True Axis and the giant yellow seal.

Bright azure light radiated from his hands as countless azure runes surged forth in a frenzy, forming around a dozen layers of azure ripples that clashed against the opposing treasures.

A string of loud cracks rang out as the giant yellow seal broke through several layers of azure ripples in succession, but these azure ripples were extremely resolute, and with each layer that was breached, the seal would noticeably slow down.

Finally, after breaking through eight layers of ripples, the momentum of the giant yellow seal was completely exhausted, and it was stopped in its tracks before being caught in the grasp of the azure-armored giant.

At the same time, Han Li's Heavy Water True Axis was also clashing against the azure ripples, and a string of loud cracks rang out in succession as all of the layers of azure ripples were torn apart by the Heavy Water True Axis with ease.

The axis wasn't even slowed own in the slightest as it continued to forge ahead, and the azure-armored giant seemed to have been rather taken aback to see this as it clenched its palm into a tight fist, while the azure patterns on the surface of his hand began to glow.

All of the destroyed layers of azure ripples were instantly drawn back into the azure fist, giving it a more substantial form and lending it more power as it was launched through the air.

Han Li let loose a loud roar, and his face suddenly turned bright red as he made a rapid string of hand seals.

The Water Dao Rune on the Heavy Water True Axis instantly lit up with dazzling radiance, and a row of incredibly bright water blades emerged on the edge of the axis. The Heavy Water True Axis rapidly revolved as it clashed against the giant azure fist, and a resounding boom rang out as the azure fist, which was still yet to fully recover, was split into two.

The Heavy Water True Axis continued to rapidly revolve as it sliced all the way up the giant's arm, aiming to split the azure-armored giant's entire body in half.

The azure-armored giant's expression changed drastically upon seeing this. It clearly hadn't anticipated that the Heavy Water True Axis would be so formidable, and it opened its mouth to release a thin, yet blindingly bright azure thread.

The azure thread was giving off powerful law fluctuations, and it wrapped itself around the Heavy Water True Axis at an incredible speed.

The Heavy Water True Axis was instantly stopped cold in its tracks, and all of the water blades on its surface were shattered upon making contact with the azure thread.

The azure-armored giant took advantage of this opportunity to rush back in retreat, but before it could do so, Han Li abruptly switched to a different hand seal, and numerous black runes appeared on the surface of the Heavy Water True Axis to destroy the azure thread, but were also destroyed themselves in the process.

Immediately thereafter, the axis resumed slicing up the azure-armored giant's arm, managing to slice its arm off cleanly at the shoulder before it was able to get away. The axis then continued to revolve relentlessly, shredding the severed arm into balls of azure light.

The azure-armored giant came to a rest in the distance, then turned to look at its missing arm with slightly furrowed brows.

"Looks like I may have underestimated you earlier."

The azure-armored giant took a glance at Han Li, and it was clear that it was still furious, but it was also clearly far calmer than before.

A layer of azure light appeared at the spot where its arm had been severed, and the azure light that the severed arm had disintegrated into instantly surged back into giant's shoulder, where a new arm emerged, except the azure patterns on this one were dimmer than before.

Han Li made a beckoning motion to draw his Heavy Water True Axis back to him, and his face had turned very pale. It appeared as if he had exerted himself quite severely, and he flipped a hand over to produce an Immortal Origin Stone to replenish his immortal spiritual power.

Using the Heavy Water True Axis had been quite taxing on his immortal spiritual power, but not to such a severe extent. However, he didn't want to make himself appear excessively powerful in the face of Qilin 9 and Qilin 17.

Qilin 9 was put slightly at ease by the sight of Han Li's labored display.

Han Li's Heavy Water True Axis had been astonishingly powerful, but it was clear that using it had also severely depleted Han Li's immortal spiritual power reserves, and that was quite reassuring to Qilin 9.

As for Qilin 17, he wasn't paying much attention to Han Li. Instead, he was making a string of hand seals in an attempt to recover the giant yellow seal that was still locked firmly in the grip of the azure-armored giant's other hand.

Yellow light was flashing urgently from the seal, but no matter how much it struggled, it was unable to break free.

After taking a moment to compose himself, Qilin 9 turned to the azure-armored giant and said, "May I ask which Golden Immortal Stage senior of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region you are? We only came here to carry out a mission, and we have no intention of making an enemy out of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region. Could it be that there's been some type of misunderstanding?"

From the series of clashes that had just taken place, he was able to determine that even though the azure-armored giant was a Golden Immortal avatar, it didn't possess the power of a Golden Immortal. Instead, at the very most, it was only at the pinnacle of the True Immortal Stage. Otherwise, the three of them wouldn't have had any chances.

The azure-armored giant offered no response as it opened its mouth to release a ball of azure light that contained countless dancing azure runes, and the ball of light instantly vanished into the giant yellow seal in its grasp.

Light flashed erratically on the surface of the sea, and it was instantly enveloped in a layer of faint azure light.

Qilin 17's expression changed drastically as he discovered that his mark in the seal had been erased. His spiritual connection with the seal had instantly vanished, meaning that the treasure no longer belonged to him.

"How dare you!"

Qilin 17 was furious, and he immediately pounced forward.

The seal was an extremely important treasure to him that was virtually equivalent to his bonded treasure, and having it taken away was no less severe a loss than having an arm severed.

Qilin 9 wanted to stop him, but it was already too late.

Qilin 17 swept a sleeve through the air to release five yellow beads, which transformed into five earthy yellow mountains in the blink of an eye, each of which was around 1,000 feet in size.

The five mountains then instantly fused into a single giant mountain that was over 10,000 feet tall, and it was giving off dazzling yellow radiance while countless yellow runes had appeared on its surface.

A burst of extremely heavy law fluctuations erupted out of the enormous mountain, and everything with a radius of several hundred kilometers instantly became countless times heavier than before.

He's mastered the laws of gravity!

Han Li's body also sank downward, but this amount of gravitational force was simple for him to withstand, and he immediately recovered as a layer of azure light flashed over his body.

The light radiating from the giant mountain grew even brighter as it came crashing down upon the azure-armored giant while releasing an incredibly destructive aura.

Han Li and Qilin 9 exchanged a glance before pouncing forward in unison.

Just like before, the two of them split up to flank the azure-armored giant from either side, and the Heavy Water True Axis and the golden millstone were giving off dazzling light as they hurtled toward the azure-armored giant.

At this point, negotiation was clearly no longer an option, so all they could do was fight.

Chapter 250: Falling Into Dire Straits

The azure-armored giant remained completely unfazed by the sight of the oncoming trio.

It began to chant an incantation as it swept a hand through the air, and the giant seal in its hand was hurled through the air, flying toward the enormous mountain as it swelled to close to 100 times its original size in a flash.

A resounding boom rang out as the giant seal shuddered violently before sinking downward slightly, but from there, it was able to hold its position and keep the huge mountain at bay.

At the same time, the azure-armored giant made a strange hand seal in front of its own chest, and a burst of azure light that contained countless surging azure runes instantly rose up from its body.

The azure light spread outward in all directions, forming a vast sea of azure light in the blink of an eye to protect the azure-armored giant.

The Heavy Water True Axis and the golden millstone crashed into the sea of azure light from the left and the right, causing it to churn and surge violently.

A series of azure ripples appeared around the giant before proliferating outward in all directions in layers, and there were over 100 such layers.

The Heavy Water True Axis was rapidly revolving as it crashed into the azure ripples, tearing through 50 to 60 layers in the blink of an eye, but it was then stopped cold in its tracks, unable to advance any further.

As for the golden millstone, it was imbued with even greater power, breaking through 70 to 80 layers of azure ripples before also coming to a rest, still situated around 2,000 to 3,000 feet away from the azure-armored giant.

Right at this moment, all of the azure ripples around the pair of treasures began to rapidly revolve in a frenzy, and from afar, it appeared as if two massive vortexes had appeared in the sea of azure light.

As the layers of azure ripples coiled themselves around the pair of treasures, two giant balls of azure light were instantly formed, trapping the treasures within them.

All of this had taken place in the blink of an eye, and by the time that Han Li and Qilin 9 realized what was happening, it was already too late for them to withdraw their treasures.

Both the Heavy Water True Axis and the golden millstone lit up in unison, sending waves of black and golden light crashing into the surrounding balls of azure light in an attempt to break free.

However, the balls of azure light were extremely resolute, and even though they were shuddering incessantly, they displayed no signs of breaking as more and more azure ripples continued to converge from the surrounding area.

After trapping those two treasures, the azure-armored giant paid no further heed to Han Li and Qilin 9 as it turned to lash out at the enormous mountain hanging above its head.

Five threads of azure light shot out of its fingertips, then came together to form a thin strand of azure light that resembled a streak of sword qi, and it was giving off incredibly powerful law fluctuations.

Countless specks of azure light appeared in the surrounding air before surging into the streak of azure sword qi, which then struck the giant mountain in a flash, easily slicing it into two as it were made of tofu, much to the alarm and astonishment of Qilin 17.

The streak of azure sword qi wasn't slowed down in the slightest as it continued to hurtle directly toward Qilin 17, looking as if it were going to slice him in half as well.

Qilin 17 hurriedly stomped a foot down onto the air below, and at the same time, dazzling yellow light erupted from his body to form a ball of yellow radiance as he flew back in retreat. At the same time, several talismans emerged within the yellow light to form a series of protective barriers all around him.

As soon as these protective light barriers took shape, the streak of azure sword qi had already arrived.

The protective light barriers around Qilin 17 appeared to have been quite resolute, but all of them instantly fell away in the face of the streak of azure sword qi, and an agonized howl quickly rang out as an arm came falling out of the sky.

Only after summoning so many talismans at once was Qilin 17 just barely able to avoid being killed on the spot, but even so, his left arm had still been severed at the shoulder, and his aura had diminished to less than half of what it was as a result.

In the next instant, he immediately made a hand seal with his remaining hand, and the blood that was pouring out of his severed arm was abruptly set alight. His entire body transformed into a ball of radiant crimson light that sped into the distance at a speed that was several times faster than before.

Han Li and Qilin 9's expressions instantly changed drastically upon seeing this.

The latter bit down onto the tip of his own tongue before expelling a mouthful of blood essence, and he flicked his fingers at the blood essence in rapid succession, upon which it instantly transformed into a cloud of blood mist that vanished in a flash.

Immediately thereafter, a vast expanse of red and golden light was released by the golden millstone that was trapped within the ball of azure light, making it resemble a two-colored sun. Balls of red and golden flames had also appeared on its surface, burning through all of the surrounding azure ripples and allowing the millstone to return to Qilin 9 in a flash.

Immediately thereafter, Qilin 9 fled in a different direction from Qilin 17 as a streak of golden light.

Almost at the exact same moment, the Water Dao Rune on the surface of the trapped Heavy Water True Axis also began to glow, and numerous blades of water re-emerged on its edge before the axis began to rapidly revolve, tearing the surrounding azure ripples apart before flying back into Han Li's grasp.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li sped away in another direction as an arc of silver lightning, traveling no slower than Qilin 9.

Upon realizing that their opponent was too formidable for them to defeat, all three of them had decided in unison that fleeing the battle was the best course of action.

Within the arc of silver lightning, Han Li's mind was racing.

This Golden Immortal avatar didn't possess the power of a true Golden Immortal, but it was still an extremely difficult opponent to deal with, and just that streak of azure sword qi that was formed by those law threads was something that Han Li doubted that he would be able to deal with.

"It's too late to try and get away now!"

The azure-armored giant was completely unconcerned by the attempts made by Han Li's trio to flee the battle, and a cold smile appeared on its face as it abruptly raised both of its arms in unison.

The sea of azure light around it shuddered before exploding violently, sending countless streaks of azure light flying in all directions before vanishing into thin air.

All of the surrounding space in a radius of several thousand kilometers instantly began to ripple violently as countless balls of azure light appeared, releasing blinding azure radiance that became interconnected to form an enormous azure domain in the blink of an eye.

Han Li's trio were all caught within the domain, and they felt as if the space around them had suddenly become tens of thousands of times heavier than before, thereby significantly reducing their speed.

Han Li let loose a low roar, and his Heavy Water True Axis appeared above him as those blades of water reappeared on its edge, and it began to rapidly revolve in an attempt to slice through the surrounding space.

The surrounding azure space churned violently for a moment, but it then instantly recovered amid a flash of azure light.

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and before he had a chance to do anything else, countless azure runes suddenly appeared around him before rapidly revolving around his body.

His surroundings blurred, and he abruptly vanished from the spot, reappearing no more than 2,000 to 3,000 feet away from the azure-armored giant in the next instant.

Almost at the exact same moment, Qilin 9 and Qilin 17 also appeared nearby with two more flashes of azure light.

At this point, Qilin 17 had already regrown a new left arm, but he was clearly still in very bad shape as he exclaimed with an alarmed and fearful expression, "Could this be... a spirit domain?"

Qilin 9 was far more calm and composed, and he quickly took a glance at his surroundings without offering a response.

Han Li also inspected his surroundings for a moment, then mused, "It doesn't seem to be a complete spirit domain. Instead, some other method seems to have been used to assist in its formation."

The surrounding azure space was just like a spirit domain in that it had completely separated them from the outside world, making it impossible for them to draw upon the world's origin qi. As a result, they were only going to be able to unleash less than 50% of their power.

A cold smile appeared on the azure-armored giant's face as it said, "If you had tried to flee the battle from the very beginning, I may not have been able to stop you with this avatar of mine, but now, it's time for you to pay with your lives!"

As soon as its voice trailed off, the nearby space rippled, and countless balls of azure lightning the size of houses appeared before hurtling toward Han Li's trio like a ferocious storm.

Qilin 9 immediately raised a hand to summon his golden millstone, which hovered in front of him like a shield.

At the same time, golden light flashed around his body, and countless golden sword projections appeared, forming a golden sea of swords around him.

The entire sky was filled with formidable sword qi that swept toward the balls of azure lightning.

Almost at the exact same moment, Han Li made a hand seal, and his Heavy Water True Axis swelled even further in size before situating itself in front of him.

It then released a vast expanse of watery black light, which formed a huge black cloud that was 700 to 800 feet thick.

The Time Dao Rune on the axis was glowing with dazzling radiance as huge balls of blue water lightning flew out of the black clouds, hurtling toward the surrounding balls of azure lightning amid rumbling thunderclaps.

Meanwhile, Qilin 17 had summoned a yellow gourd that was suspended above his head.

He began to chant an incantation, and a layer of translucent runes emerged over the surface of the gourd as it rapidly swelled to the size of a house. Loud rumbling could be heard within the gourd, and several thousand grains of translucent golden sand came pouring out, presenting a stunning sight to behold.

As soon as the sand was released, each grain split up into countless more, forming a sea of golden sand in front of Qilin 17.

Countless balls of azure lightning came crashing down upon the defensive measures that Han Li's trio had set up before exploding violently into azure lightning, forming a destructive sea of azure lightning.

Lights of all types of different colors intertwined with one another as earth-shattering booms rang out in succession, causing the surrounding space to shudder violently.

Han Li's trio were all looking on with grim expressions.

Each of these balls of azure lightning wasn't all that formidable on their own, but with each ball of lightning that exploded, a new one would instantly be conjured up in its place, and it seemed that there was no end to this barrage.

The blue water lightning released by the Heavy Water True Axis was quickly overwhelmed by the relentless barrage of azure lightning, and countless balls of azure lightning came crashing down upon the black cloud.

The black cloud shuddered violently as it was rapidly worn down, and it didn't take long before its original thickness of 700 to 800 feet was whittled away.

500 feet, 400 feet, 300 feet, 200 feet...

In the blink of an eye, the thickness of the black cloud had been reduced to less than 200 feet.

Qilin 17 was also facing a similar predicament, with only a thin layer of yellow sand remaining above his head.

Qilin 17 made a hand seal, and two thick pillars of yellow light erupted out of the palms of his hands as he desperately injected his immortal spiritual power into the film of sand overhead.

Having already had so many of his most powerful treasures destroyed or damaged, this film of sand was the only thing he had left to rely on at this point, and if it were also destroyed, then his fate would be sealed.

Out of the trio, Qilin 9 appeared to have been struggling the least. The sea of golden swords around him continued to swirl, and its radiance had dimmed a little, but it was still able to release streaks of golden sword qi to destroy all of the oncoming balls of azure lightning.

Chapter 251: Stalling for Time

While Han Li's trio was clinging on desperately for dear life, the balls of lightning in the sky seemed to have finally been exhausted.

They were initially elated to see this, but the three of them exchanged a glance, and each of them could see their own bewilderment mirrored in one another's eyes.

This was because as soon as these balls of azure lightning had appeared, the azure-armored giant had vanished into the thin air, but the fact that this azure domain still remained indicated that they were clearly not out of the woods yet.

Sure enough, before the three of them even had a chance to catch their breath, a series of azure vortexes of light suddenly appeared out of thin air.

Countless azure tree branches then flew out of the vortexes before crashing down from above.

They appeared to have been branches, but each of them was over 100 feet in length and comparable in size to entire trees, and they were raining down upon Han Li's trio with ferocious might.

Fortunately, during that brief period of respite, Han Li's trio had banded together in a triangular formation, with each person defending one side.

The cloud above Han Li's head had already been whittled down significantly, and it began to tremble violently in the face of the falling branches. The cloud was whittled down even further, but it was able to keep close to a third of the azure branches at bay.

Meanwhile, the sword array that was swirling around Qilin 9 was releasing streaks of sharp azure sword qi that shredded the oncoming branches.

Out of the trio, Qilin 17 was the one who was struggling the most. Having already sustained severe injuries and expended a great deal of immortal spiritual power, cracks were already beginning to appear in the barrier of yellow sand that he had summoned.

Just like with the balls of lightning, there seemed to be no end to the torrent of azure branches, and Han Li's trio was certainly not having a good time in the face of such a ferocious barrage, but thankfully, the triangular formation that they had adopted allowed them to hold their own for now.

"We can't keep this up forever. If I had known this was going to happen, I would've never taken on this mission. How am I even going to get out of this alive now that I've made an enemy out of the Immortal Palace?" Qilin 17 complained with a sullen expression.

There was a dark look on Qilin 9's face as well as he said, "It looks like we fell into a trap. The person who released this mission is most likely intentionally trying to stir up conflict between the Transient Guild and the Immortal Palace for whatever purpose."

"Let's try and figure out how we're going to get out of this alive before we think about those things, fellow daoists. I have a bad feeling about this situation," Han Li suddenly said.

Sure enough, Han Li's concerns were very much warranted.

As it turned out, all of the branches destroyed by Han Li's trio had disintegrated into specks of azure light that had burrowed into the earth down below, following which seedlings began to emerge from the soil. As more and more specks of azure light descended from above, the seedlings began to grow rapidly at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye.

In a span of no more than a few seconds, the seedlings had grown into huge trees that were several hundred feet tall, and they were only continuing to grow even taller.

In the blink of an eye, Han Li's trio found themselves situated in a lush forest that was giving off an extremely potent wood-attribute aura.

"At this rate, we're going to be trapped here until we die! Fellow Daoist Qilin 9, you possess the most advanced cultivation base out of the three of us, do you have any way to get us out of here?" Qilin 17 asked with an uneasy expression.

"We may only be facing a Golden Immortal avatar, but its abilities are extremely formidable. Even I can only just barely hold on, and escaping would be near impossible. At this point, perhaps the only way to secure a slim chance at survival for ourselves would be to go against conventional wisdom," Qilin 9 replied.

"Go against conventional wisdom?" Qilin 17's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged, but he was also rather intrigued.

Just as Qilin 9 alluded to, the three of them had their powers severely restricted inside the azure domain, and it was next to impossible for them to escape in the face of this endless barrage of attacks.

Even if Han Li were to reveal his Mantra Treasured Axis and Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, he still wouldn't have been confident in his ability to escape, and revealing those two treasures would have far-reaching consequences, so he absolutely didn't want to use them unless his life was under threat.

Even though Qilin 9 was in the same situation, he was a late-True Immortal cultivator, and even now, he was still looking quite calm and composed, so he clearly still had some trump cards up his sleeve.

As these thoughts were running through Han Li's mind, Qilin 9 opened his mouth to release three objects of different colors, and they swelled rapidly to become a set of three giant flags. The flags were extremely antiquated in appearance with eight strange runes embroidered upon them, and aside from their colors, which were golden, silver, and black, the flags were identical to one another, so they clearly worked as a set.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes at the sight of the eight runes as they were very similar to the ones on the stone cauldron that he had obtained from the monkeys at the foot of the Crimson Dawn Peak, and he couldn't help but wonder if the two were connected in some way.

He had studied the stone cauldron on many occasions during these past years without making any useful discoveries, and he certainly wasn't expecting to find any leads on the matter here.

His expression remained unchanged, but his mind was racing.

"These flags are known as Triple Origin Great Millet Flags, and they can only be activated by three people at once. They're an extremely formidable defensive treasure, but the immortal spiritual power expenditure required to use them is far too immense for me to support on my own. My proposal of going against conventional wisdom involves using this treasure to focus solely on defending ourselves rather than trying to escape," Qilin 9 explained.

"If these flags are so taxing to use, then wouldn't we be completely trapped once we inevitably run out of immortal spiritual power?" Qilin 17 asked, sounding rather disappointed.

"According to my knowledge, there's generally a time limit on all avatars formed by talismans, so I'm presuming that what Fellow Daoist Qilin 9 is suggesting is that we defend ourselves until time runs out for the avatar, is that right?" Han Li asked.

"That is indeed what I'm suggesting, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15," Qilin 9 replied with a nod.

"It seems like this set of Triple Origin Great Millet Flags are rather different from normal treasures. In particular, may I ask what's so special about the eight runes on them? We're in a dire situation right now, so please pardon me for being extra cautious, Fellow Daoist," Han Li said.

"These flags are indeed rather special, and I only came into possession of them by chance, but I've managed to figure out how to use them after over a century of experimentation. Time is of the essence here, so please familiarize yourselves with them as quickly as possible," Qilin 9 urged.

He made a hand seal as he spoke to expand his sword array slightly to keep close to half of the azure branches at bay, and at the same time, he raised his other hand to send two jade slips flying toward Han Li and Qilin 17.

Han Li caught the jade slip, and he speculated that Qilin 9 most likely knew more about those eight runes that he was letting on, but he wasn't willing to divulge this information.

He injected his spiritual sense into the jade slip in his hand to find that it contained a mantra for treasure refinement, and it was a rather special one that was very different from all of the other refinement methods that he knew.

Han Li quickly read through the contents of the jade slip while thinking back to the discoveries that he had made from studying that stone cauldron over the years, and as he did so, a sense of elation welled up in his heart.

If he weren't mistaken, then this refinement method should've been effective on that stone cauldron as well.

Shortly thereafter, the barrage of azure branches falling from the heavens abruptly ceased without any warning. At this point, all of the trees around them had already grown to around 2,000 to 3,000 feet tall, and their canopies had virtually obscured the entire sky.

"We don't have any time left! Please hurry!"

Qilin 9's brows were slightly furrowed as he immediately thrust the silver and black flags upon Han Li and Qilin 17.

Immediately thereafter, he raised a hand to release several incantation seals in succession, all of which vanished into the golden flag before him in a flash, following which specks of golden light appeared on its surface.

Han Li took a deep breath before casting a series of incantation seals himself into his silver flag.

The flag slowly rose up into the air as specks of silver light appeared on its surface, giving it a resplendent yet mysterious appearance.

Qilin 17 also closed his eyes as he made a series of hand seals, and the specks of black light appeared on his flag as it rose up into the air as well.

Right at this moment, a burst of spatial fluctuations erupted overhead, and the Gold Immortal avatar appeared, having already reverted back to the size of a normal adult human.

"I didn't think that a trio of lowly immortals like yourselves would be able to last this long, but it's time to put this to an end!"

The Golden Immortal avatar raised a hand as it spoke, and a ball of azure spiritual light with countless azure runes flashing within it instantly appeared, then vanished into one of the giant trees down below in a flash.

The tree was immediately uprooted as it rose up from the ground, and it began to radiate dazzling green light as it rapidly transformed, sprouting four thick limbs and an ugly head.

In the blink of an eye, the tree had transformed into a giant that was several thousand feet tall.

As soon as the giant took shape, it immediately raised an enormous fist and lashed out at Qilin 9's golden sword array.

A resounding boom rang out, and the entire azure space shuddered, as did the golden sword array, but it was able to remain intact.

As more streaks of azure spiritual light flew out of the Golden Immortal avatar's hand, around half of the trees down below instantly transformed into formidable giants, but the azure light radiating from the avatar's body also dimmed slightly as a result.

All of the tree giants swung their massive fists through the air, unleashing countless massive azure fist projections that hurtled toward Han Li's trio from all directions.

After withstanding several ferocious barrages of attacks, the black cloud and the screen of yellow sand had dimmed significantly and were appearing rather scattered, but they were still just barely clinging on.

The Golden Immortal avatar was beginning to run out of patience, and it opened its mouth to release a burst of azure light, which instantly enveloped all of the remaining trees down below.

All of those trees immediately began to glow with azure light as they rose up from the ground, but instead of instantly transforming into individual giants, they fused together to form a giant that was around 20,000 to 30,000 feet tall.

Green light was surging up and down its body incessantly, and as it raised an arm, all of the other tree giants around it exploded into balls of azure light that swept toward it before forming an azure wooden saber that was around the same length as the tree giant was tall.

There were countless green runes that were shimmering with a cold light engraved onto the blade of the saber.

Chapter 252: A Threat From a Golden Immortal

As soon as the tree giant took shape, it crouched down slightly before springing up into the sky, and all of the green runes on the wooden saber in its hand began to glow with dazzling radiance that illuminated the entire azure space.

In the next instant, the burst of azure light came crashing down with devastating might like a radiant waterfall.

Even before it fully descended upon Han Li's trio, a burst of terrifying power was already cascading down from the heavens, causing the black cloud and the barrier of yellow sand to tremble violently.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the giant wooden saber came crashing down, and the black cloud, the barrier of yellow sand, and the golden sword array finally imploded amid an eruption of black, yellow, golden, and azure light.

At the same time, gusts of fierce wind were sent sweeping through the air in all directions, creating ripples that were visible even to the naked eye in the surrounding azure space.

However, the wooden saber didn't continue to come crashing down from above. Instead, it was repelled upward, and the tree giant stumbled back several steps in succession before steadying itself.

After the dust settled, Han Li's trio was revealed with a set of massive flag projections glowing radiantly above them while releasing vast spiritual power fluctuations.

The space around the flag projections was rippling, but the projections themselves remained completely resolute and steady, seemingly having withstood the attack from the tree giant with ease.

Even so, Han Li's trio didn't dare to get complacent, and they were continuing to cast incantation seals relentlessly into the flags before them.

All of a sudden, the three flag projections fused as one at Qilin 9's behest, forming a giant egg-shaped three-colored light barrier.

The outermost layer of the light barrier was golden in color, while the middle layer was black, and the innermost layer was silver.

Countless flag projections could be seen around the light barriers, giving off dazzling radiance while emitting a sharp screeching sound, and it seemed as if they were forming an independent space within the azure domain.

A dark look appeared on the Golden Immortal avatar's face upon seeing this, and it made a hand seal, upon which dazzling azure light erupted from the tree giant's body, and it strode forward before swinging its wooden saber viciously down onto the three-colored light barrier again.

The entire light barrier shuddered violently, and the spot that was struck caved in significantly.

However, the indentation was quickly mended amid a flash of three-colored light, repelling the wooden saber once again.

The tree giant swung its saber down over and over again, and with each strike, an indentation would appear on the three-colored light barrier, but it would always recover very quickly, and the light barrier was displaying no signs of breaking.

"This set of Triple Origin Great Millet Flags is truly extraordinary, Fellow Daoist Qilin 9! The aura of that avatar has already diminished significantly, so it must not be able to last much longer," Qilin 17 said in an ecstatic voice while recovering his immortal spiritual power using an Immortal Origin Stone.

Qilin 9 was also holding an Immortal Origin Stone, and a proud look appeared in his eyes upon hearing this, but he said in a cautious manner, "Don't get complacent. I'm sure the avatar has more tricks up his sleeve, so take this time to recover as much as possible."

Han Li was also absorbing immortal spiritual power from an Immortal Origin Stone, and all three of them had taken recovery pills to boot, but they were still struggling to keep up with the immortal spiritual power demands of the Triple Origin Great Millet Flags.

"Let's see how much longer you'll be able to last," the Golden Immortal avatar chuckled coldly as it switched to a different hand seal, then pointed a finger at the tree giant from afar.

The tree giant instantly stopped what it was doing, and its feet sank into the soil down below, following which it reverted back into an enormous tree amid a flash of blinding azure light.

Immediately thereafter, all of the leaves on the branches of the tree rapidly enlarged, following which a series of massive red flower buds emerged.

In the next instant, all of the red flower buds bloomed into vibrant flowers in unison.

The flowers then began to release flurries of red pollen-like particles that disintegrated into a cloud of red mist, which descended toward the three-colored light barrier at an astonishing speed. Upon reaching the three-colored light barrier, the red mist was able to bypass it with ease as if it didn't exist at all.

Han Li's trio were naturally extremely alarmed by this, and Han Li immediately released his spiritual sense to examine the cloud of red mist.

In the next instant, a drowsy sensation arose in his mind, and the circulation of immortal spiritual power in his body became a lot more sluggish.

However, in the next instant, his enormous spiritual sense jolted him out of his dazed state, and he immediately yelled, "Look out, this is a spiritual sense attack!"

At the same time, the nascent soul in his dantian made a hand seal with both hands, and a burst of cool and refreshing energy surged through his meridians, restoring his original rate of immortal spiritual power circulation.

Qilin 9 immediately issued an instruction upon hearing this, and Han Li and Qilin 17 instantly switched to a different set of hand seals accordingly.

All of a sudden, the middle black light barrier shuddered slightly before rising to the surface, and as a result, the silver light barrier shifted to the middle, while the golden light barrier became the innermost layer.

Following this transition, the light radiating from the three-colored light barrier became extremely gentle, while ripples began to surge over its surface.

This time, the three-colored light barrier was able to completely keep the cloud of red mist at bay.

However, the red mist that had already seeped into the light barrier had enveloped Han Li's trio, constantly lulling them into a state of drowsiness.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly as he activated his Spirit Refinement Technique while also summoning a small white jade bell that began to revolve on the spot above his head.

Bursts of cool energy surged through his mind, instantly dispelling the majority of the red mist's effects to minimize its influence.

Following Han Li's warning, Qilin 9 had also braced himself, slamming a palm down onto the top of his own head, upon which a small white lock flew out of his sleeve, releasing halos of white light that enveloped his body down below.

Immediately thereafter, a hint of clarity returned to his eyes.

As for Qilin 17, he had summoned a yellow silken scarf that was revolving around him to keep the red mist at bay.

Even though all three of them had ways to deal with the red mist, it was requiring additional immortal spiritual power expenditure on top of having to maintain the three-colored light barrier, and inside this azure domain, they were unable to draw upon the world's origin qi.

As a result, even though they were constantly using Immortal Origin Stones to replenish themselves, their faces had still turned extremely pale, and they weren't going to be able to last much longer at this rate.

Unbeknownst to them, the Golden Immortal avatar was astonished by the resilience that they had displayed up to this point.

It had thought that it would be able to easily take down this trio of pesky little rats, but that was not proving to be the case here, and it was becoming more and more frustrated by the second.

Bright azure light erupted out of the Golden Immortal avatar's eyes, and it made a strange hand seal with both hands as it declared in a furious voice, "I'm going to make you pay for what you did even if I have to make some heavy sacrifices myself!"

All of a sudden, all of the red flowers on the giant tree down below shuddered slightly in unison, following which they were enveloped by balls of azure flames that instantly spread over the entire tree while giving off extremely formidable law fluctuations.

As the tree was set alight by azure flames, the Golden Immortal avatar's body began to take on a transparent appearance.

Immediately thereafter, the massive tree shuddered violently before collapsing toward Han Li's trio with devastating might.

Even before it fully descended upon Han Li's trio, it was already giving off an indescribable sense of pressure that struck them with a sense of asphyxiation, and it was already too late to take evasive measures.

"Look out!" Qilin 9 yelled in an urgent voice as he expelled a mouthful of blood essence into the golden flag before him.

Countless specks of golden light instantly emerged from the flag to form a golden wall of light, and Han Li and Qilin 17 also immediately followed suit, injecting all of their remaining immortal spiritual power into the Triple Origin Great Millet Flags.

As a result, the other two flags released walls of silver and black light, respectively, following which Han Li summoned his Heavy Water True Axis to act as a shield.

At the same time, Qilin 9 and Qilin 17 also summoned a series of treasures that released layers of light barriers that enveloped the trio from all directions.

Before they had a chance to do anything else, the giant tree fell upon them with an earth-shattering boom, and Han Li's trio was inundated by an eruption of dazzling azure light.

The azure light then exploded violently, creating rifts that were visible even to the naked eye in the surrounding space, and it was as if the entire area were about to be torn apart.

Incredibly fierce gusts of azure wind swept through the air in all directions, and Han Li's trio were sent flying out of the explosion of azure light.

Their robes were in tatters, their faces were deathly pale, and their bodies were riddled with wounds, but all of them had ecstatic looks on their faces, having finally weathered the storm.

The azure light quickly faded to reveal the Golden Immortal avatar, but at this point, its body was already virtually completely transparent, and it appeared to have been on the verge of fading away.

"You may have gotten away this time, but remember my name, I am Gu Jie of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region. Once I come out of seclusion, I'll be sure to capture all three of you and torment you for the rest of eternity! Mark my words!"

The Golden Immortal avatar's body gradually faded away as its voice trailed off into silence.

The golden talisman re-emerged in the avatar's place, then erupted into flames before quickly being incinerated into ashes.

"It looks like we've finally managed to get out of this predicament, but there's going to be more trouble to come now that we've made an enemy out of a Golden Immortal from the Northern Glacial Immortal Region," Qilin 9 said in a grim voice.

"Considering how much trouble we had with this avatar, our chances of surviving against the actual Gu Jie would be slim to none," Qilin 17 sighed.

"There's no point in talking about that now. What's done has already been done, and we should clean up the battlefield here and leave this place as soon as possible," Han Li suggested, two which both Qilin 9 and Qilin 17 nodded in agreement.

Chapter 253: Trouble

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a pill before swallowing it, and his complexion gradually began to improve.

The Heavy Water True Axis was hovering beside him, looking a little dim, clearly having suffered quite a bit of damage during the battle, so he was going to have to refine it when he got back to the Blaze Dragon Dao.

Meanwhile, Qilin 9 had already stowed away his Triple Origin Great Millet Flags, which had also lost some of their spiritual nature during that final clash against Gu Jie's avatar, much to Qilin 9's dismay.

Of course, Qilin 17 was the one who fared the worst of the three. Not only had he suffered severe injuries, the seal that was equivalent to his bonded treasure had also lost almost all of its spiritual nature from being eroded by the Golden Immortal avatar's law powers. However, he was already extremely fortunate to have been able to survive this ordeal and recover his treasure.

The three of them took a brief rest, then flew back into the valley.

Following the intense battle that had just taken place, the valley was already completely unrecognizable, and most of the surrounding mountains had been razed to the ground. The earth was riddled with countless craters of different sizes, some of which were so deep that molten lava could be seen at the bottom.

This mountain range was quite secluded, but the battle that had just taken place had caused a massive commotion, and some of the nearby cultivating powers had taken notice.

Over the course of the next few decades, many people traveled to this area to try their luck, but that was a story for another time.

Upon entering the valley, a thought suddenly seemed to have occurred to Qilin 9, and he said, "Oh, I almost forgot. Let me go and fetch the two treasures that were serving as the core of the array."

"In that case, I'll go retrieve the Lightning Restraining Wood. Can we count on you to take care of things in the valley, Fellow Daoist Qilin 17?" Han Li asked.

Qilin 17 naturally had no objections to this.

The three of them knew that it was best to leave this place as soon as possible, and they immediately sprang into action while supervising one another with their spiritual sense to ensure that no one played any tricks.

Han Li appeared outside the valley in a flash, then swept a sleeve through the air to send a streak of azure light flying into the ground.

A large hole was blown into the ground, inside of which was a length of golden wood that was taller than a grown man and around the same thickness as a human leg.

The length of wood was entirely golden in color with a series of lightning shaped growth rings visible on its cross section. Its surface was completely smooth and riddled with more golden lightning patterns that were giving off a strong lightning aura.

Even though it was a wooden material, the Lightning Restraining Wood more closely resembled some type of metal ore.

With a sweep of his sleeve, the length of Lightning Restraining Wood was drawn into his grasp, and he took a close glance at it.

According to a book that he had previously read, the Lightning Restraining Wood was a type of rare lightning-attribute spirit material that was extremely sturdy and was able to absorb the power of lightning, making it a top-notch material for refining lightning-attribute spirit treasures.

It was very difficult to grow this type of wood, so it was very rarely seen being sold anywhere, and Han Li certainly wasn't expecting to come across a batch of it here.

Han Li then flew over to another place and blasted the ground open with another burst of azure light to dig up a second length of Lightning Restraining Wood.

Before long, he had retrieved all 81 lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood that were buried around the valley, and as he returned to the valley, Qilin 9 and Qilin 17 were already there, with a pair of treasures hovering in front of the former.

One of the two treasures was an antiquated golden sword that was completely different from normal flying swords, possessing a far bulkier and heavier blade, upon which was engraved nine golden stars.

The other treasure was an antiquated square golden mirror with hollow edges. The surface of the mirror was rather murky and indistinct, and there was a fierce tiger engraved onto its back.

Clearly, these were the two treasures that had acted as the core of the array.

It was very apparent that this was a pair of very remarkable treasures, and the metal-attribute fluctuations that they gave off indicated that even if they weren't immortal treasures, they weren't far away from that level.

As for Qilin 17, he had dug up a storage bracelet in addition to that golden pill cauldron, both of which had once belonged to the white-haired elderly man.

This was quite a bountiful haul, but for some reason, both of them were standing in a solemn silence.

"Have you found something, fellow daoists?" Han Li asked as he landed beside the two of them.

"Take a look for yourself," Qilin 17 said in a neutral voice as he patted the golden pill cauldron.

Han Li immediately injected his spiritual sense into the pill cauldron, and even though the pill refinement process had already ceased, there was still a burst of scorching spiritual power that was slowly circulating inside, forming a resolute array that kept his spiritual sense at bay.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he increased his spiritual sense output, allowing him to instantly bypass the array and see what was inside.

There was a thumb-sized purple pill hovering with the cauldron, and close to half of it had been charred black, clearly indicating a failed pill refinement.

With a flick of his wrist, Han Li sent several incantation seals flying into the cauldron, then slammed a hand down onto the cauldron's lid, following which a burst of azure light flashed over his palm.

A faint crack rang out from within the cauldron, and with a sweep of Han Li's sleeve, the lid of the cauldron was removed, and the purple pill inside flew out.

Qilin 9 raised an eyebrow ever so slightly upon seeing this, seemingly rather taken aback by the fact that Han Li was able to break open the restrictions on the cauldron so easily to retrieve the pill inside.

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face as he inspected the purple pill.

There was a purple lightning-shaped spirit pattern on the pill, but it was incomplete, with the charred section swallowing up the majority of the spirit pattern.

Furthermore, the purple lightning spirit pattern was giving off extremely faint law fluctuations.

"So he really was refining a dao pill," Han Li murmured to himself.

"That's right. I took a closer look at his face earlier, and I recalled that this man is Ping Yaozi, a vastly renowned top-tier Earthly Pill Master of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region. However, he's a very secretive person, so very few people know what he looks like. I've heard that he's been trying to become a Heavenly Pill Master for a very long time, but I don't know if he's succeeded or not. If he has..."

Qilin 9's voice trailed off here as a wry smile appeared on his face.

Han Li's expression also darkened slightly upon hearing this.

Even the Blaze Dragon Dao, one of the top-ranking sects in the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region, didn't have a single Heavenly Pill Master among its ranks, and that was a clear reflection of just how precious pill refinement masters of this lofty caliber were.

If Ping Yaozi really had already become a Heavenly Pill Master, then he would've possessed an unimaginably lofty status in the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace. Even if he had only been a top-tier Earthly Pill Master, this would've still been extremely heavy loss for the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, and now, they had just killed him to complete a Transient Guild mission.

It was no wonder Gu Jie had sworn to hunt them down, and with that in mind, a chill instantly ran down Han Li's spine.

They had truly landed themselves in hot water this time...

"It's too late to regret our actions now. All of us have cultivated countless years to become True Immortals, and we all have some innocent blood on our hands. The pursuit of the Great Dao is an endeavor that goes against the natural order to begin with, so we should be accustomed to adversity on our path of cultivation. I, for one, certainly won't just accept my fate and resign myself to death," Qilin 9 declared.

"You're right, Fellow Daoist Qilin 9. The Northern Glacial Immortal Region is an extremely vast place, so as long as we make ample preparations, there's no guarantee that Gu Jie will be able to find us, even if he's a Golden Immortal. Time is of the essence, so let's split these things, then get out of here as soon as possible," Qilin 17 replied with a nod.

Han Li naturally had no objections to this, and thus, Qilin 17 emptied all of the content of the white-haried elderly man's storage bracelet onto the ground.

Most of his belongings were various types of spirit plants and ingredients, all of which were filled with abundant spiritual qi and instantly caught the attention of Han Li's trio.

Han Li's gaze immediately settled onto one of the spirit plants, which was as green as jade and slightly curved. It had tiny leaves that were pressed tightly against the stem of the spirit plant like scales, and this was none other than a Horned Dragon Herb, the main material for refining Spring Rain Pills.

Furthermore, there were around a dozen of these Horned Dragon Herbs on the ground, and they appeared to have all been above 50,000 years of age.

As for the other spirit plants and materials, Han Li only recognized less than half of them, but they were all premium ingredients and materials that weren't inferior to the Horned Dragon Herb.

Just these spirit plants and materials alone were already a massive haul, and in addition to them, there were also six or seven treasures, a pair of white jade vials, a purple jade box, and a small pile of what appeared to have been around 50 to 60 Immortal Origin Stones.

The treasures were all spirit treasures of a very high caliber, but they were far inferior to the pair of spirit treasures that had served as the core of the array.

The two white jade vials had restrictions placed upon them to keep out spiritual sense, so it was impossible to tell what they contained.

As for the purple jade box, there was a silver talisman plastered to its surface, and countless tadpole-like silver runes were roaming over its surface, giving off immense spiritual power fluctuations.

There were also several layers of spirit patterns engraved onto the box, releasing a silver light barrier that was also capable of keeping out spiritual sense.

Qilin 17 handed the storage bracelet to Qilin 9 for an examination, but Qilin 9 was staring at the treasures laid out before him in a completely transfixed manner, and only after hearing Qilin 17 call out to him did he return to his senses.

"My apologies, I was just surprised that Ping Yaozi had so many things in his possession," Qilin 9 said as he accepted the storage bracelet from Qilin 17.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon seeing this. It was only for an instant, but he had noticed a peculiar look flash through Qilin 9's eyes just now.

He turned his gaze to the treasures on the ground, only to find that they were all ordinary treasures that didn't appear to have been remarkable in any way.

However, beside those treasures was a rather strange-looking black badge that was giving off a faint black glow.

Qilin 17 also seemed to have noticed the badge, and he remarked, "That's a badge from the Ubiquitous Pavilion. Could it be that this Ping Yaozi is somehow tied to that place?"

Han Li's heart stirred slightly once again upon hearing this.

"Whether he had ties with the Ubiquitous Pavilion has nothing to do with us," Qilin 9 said as he handed the storage bracelet to Han Li after a brief examination.

Han Li injected his spiritual sense into the storage bracelet as nothing more than a formality ,and after verifying that it had indeed been completely emptied, he set it aside and turned his attention back to the spoils laid out on the ground.

Chapter 254: Fighting Over the Cauldron

"Have either of you thought about how we should split everything?" Qilin 17 asked as he licked his slightly dry lips.

"Let's take a look at what's in these jade vials and this jade box first," Qilin 9 said as he drew one of the white jade vials into his grasp before removing the stopper, and Han Li did the same with the other vial.

An identical fragrance wafted out of both of the vials, and after just a slight whiff, Han Li's trio were all struck by a sense of comfort and reinvigoration.

Each of the jade vials contained around a dozen yellow pills that were giving off a faint sheen.

Han Li didn't recognize these pills, but his pill refinement experience told him that this was most likely a type of pill for advancing one's cultivation base, and its effects were definitely more potent than those of the Origin Unifying Pill.

"These are Dawn Luster Pills!" Qilin 17 exclaimed with a hint of elation in his voice.

"I'm guessing Ping Yaozi prepared these for himself," Qilin 9 replied with a nod.

He set down the white jade vial in his hand as he spoke, then picked up the purple jade box, and after taking a close look at the silver talisman adhered to its surface, he released several incantation seals in succession, only for them to be repelled by a layer of silver light that suddenly appeared over the surface of the box.

Qilin 9's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and after a brief moment of contemplation, he laid a hand down onto the jade box, then began to chant an incantation, following which golden light began to radiate from the palm of his hand.

Han Li and Qilin 17 exchanged a glance, and each of them could see their own curiosity mirrored in one another's eyes.

Generally speaking, the more tightly secured a container was, the more important its contents were.

Qilin 9 was clearly thinking the same thing, and it appears that he was planning to adopt some slightly more aggressive methods to try and break open the restriction on the jade box.

He began to chant an incantation, and a layer of dazzling silver light appeared over the jade box, keeping all of the golden light that was radiating from Qilin 9's hand at bay.

Qilin 9's brows became even more tightly furrowed upon seeing this, and the golden light radiating from his hand brightened even further, while golden runes also appeared within it.

In response, the silver light radiating from the jade box also brightened, and it was able to hold its own against the golden light.

Qilin 9's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and sweat was already beginning to roll down his cheeks from his forehead, but his hand remained firmly pressed against the jade box, while the golden light radiating from it became brighter and brighter.

However, the silver light glowing from the box was able to keep up, thwarting Qilin 9's efforts to bypass it.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this. It seemed that the restrictions placed on the jade box were so profound that even a late-True Immortal cultivator like Qilin 9 was powerless to break through them.

A short while later, the golden light radiating from Qilin 9's hand had already brightened to the point that it was almost too radiant to look at, and the silver seemed to have finally reached its limits, beginning to succumb to the golden light.

A hint of elation appeared on Qilin's 9’s face upon seeing this, but his expression then suddenly changed as he hurriedly pulled his hand away.

The silver light on the jade box flashed a few times before returning to normal.

"Why did you stop, Fellow Daoist Qilin 9?" Qilin 17 asked.

It had appeared to him like Qilin 9 had stopped right as the silver light restriction was about to be overwhelmed.

"Whoever set up this restriction concealed a self-destruction restriction in its deepest part. If I hadn't stopped in time, this jade box and its contents would've all been destroyed," Qilin 9 explained, much to Qilin 17's dismay.

Ping Yaozi was already dead, so where were they supposed to find the method to open the box?

Han Li's brows also furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

"Judging from my past experience, it's not impossible to unravel this restriction, but I'll need ample time to study it and make preparations. At the moment, I'm powerless to do anything, but the two of you are free to give it a try," Qilin 9 said as he set the jade box back down.

A hint of intrigue appeared in Qilin 17's eyes as he picked up the box, and yellow light emerged from his hand to envelop the entire box.

A layer of silver light instantly appeared on the jade box to oppose the yellow light, and a solemn look appeared in Qilin 17's eyes as he cast a series of incantation seals toward the box.

The silver light radiating from the box instantly brightened further to keep the incantation seals at bay, and after about 15 minutes, Qilin 17 was already beginning to sweat as he made a rapid series of hand seals, releasing threads of yellow light that enveloped the jade box.

If one were to look closely, they would discover that the threads of yellow light were formed by countless yellow runes, and they were slowly suppressing the silver light on the jade box.

Qilin 9's eyes lit up upon seeing this, and Han Li also took an involuntary step forward.

Right at this moment, the silver runes on the jade box flashed, and they abruptly released a burst of light that snapped all of the threads of yellow light.

"What a ridiculous restriction!" Qilin 17 harrumphed coldly as he withdrew his hand, making no further attempts to undo the restriction on the jade box.

Qilin 9 heaved a faint sigh of disappointment upon seeing this, then turned to Han Li as he suggested, "Why don't you give it a try as well, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15? Perhaps you'll have better luck than the two of us."

"Do be careful, Fellow Daoist. If you break what's inside, that'll count against your allocation of the spoils," Qilin 17 chuckled as he handed the jade box to Han Li.

"I'll give it a try, but seeing as neither of you were successful, I most likely won't be able to do anything, either," Han Li said as he accepted the jade box, then released a burst of azure light to envelop it.

He then made a string of hand seals, conjuring up threads of azure light that enveloped the jade box, only to be opposed by that same layer of silver light.

A short while later, the silver light on the jade box abruptly brightened, tearing all of the threads of azure light apart, and Han Li shook his head as he placed the jade box back onto the ground.

"I can't do anything about this restriction, either."

"In that case, let's not force it. We don't have much time, so let's discuss how we're going to split the rest of the treasures among ourselves," Qilin 9 said.

"You're the leader in this mission, Fellow Daoist Qilin 9. Do you have any suggestions on how we can split everything?" Han Li asked, and Qilin 17 also turned to Qilin 9.

"There are quite a few spirit plants, materials, pills, and Immortal Origin Stones, so we'll be able to split those evenly. What's difficult to allocate are this cauldron, these treasures, and that jade box," Qilin 9 said.

"That's a simple matter. There are three of us, so I suggest one of us gets the cauldron, another one gets the treasures, and the final one gets the jade box. What do you think?" Qilin 17 proposed.

"That's not a bad idea, but who's going to get what?" Qilin 9 asked.

"I've always been very interested in pill refinement, so how about I take the cauldron?" Qilin 17 asked.

"I also happen to have a keen interest in the art of pill refinement," Qilin 9 said as a meaningful smile appeared on his face, and Qilin 17's expression immediately darkened slightly upon hearing this.

Meanwhile, Han Li was standing off to the side in silence, contemplating how best to proceed.

There really wasn't a comparison to be made here. The golden cauldron was the most precious of all of the items here, being an immortal treasure, so of course everyone wanted it, regardless of whether they actually had any interest in pill refinement.

Han Li wanted to refine some pills in order to accelerate his cultivation in order to make a breakthrough as soon as possible, so he naturally wanted the cauldron as well.

However, at the moment, he was merely observing and didn't verbally express his intentions.

As he was sweeping his spiritual sense over the cauldron, he noticed that there seemed to have been something concealed within it, and this feeling was very similar to the one that he had gotten from that black saber previously in Fang Pan's protection.

Given that Gu Jie had bestowed that avatar talisman upon Ping Yaozi, it was very likely that the cauldron had been tampered with.

If coming into possession of this treasure would increase his chances of being tracked down by Gu Jie, then he definitely wouldn't take the risk, so he was very wary of trying to claim the cauldron for himself.

Having said that, perhaps Qilin 17 wouldn't have noticed anything with his mid-True Immortal Stage cultivation base and spiritual sense, but as a late-True Immortal cultivator, was it really possible that Qilin 9 had also failed to notice that something was amiss?

Qilin 17 forced a smile onto his own face as he turned to Han Li and said, "I've been stuck at the mid-True Immortal Stage for many years and desperately need this cauldron for pill refinement purposes. If you two are willing to give me the cauldron, I can give up a third of my allocation of the rest of the treasures."

"In that case..."

Han Li was just about to say something when Qilin 9 interjected, "Truth be told, I've already been searching for a suitable pill cauldron for the past several centuries. If you two can give me the cauldron, I'm willing to give up on two thirds of my allocation of everything else."

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly upon hearing this, seemingly tempted by this proposition.

Qilin 17 took a glance at the cauldron, then gritted his teeth as he decided, "Alright, in that case, all I want is this cauldron, and I'm willing to give up on everything else. Is that enough?"

Qilin 9 considered this proposition for a moment, then smiled as he said, "If you're this insistent on claiming the cauldron, then it would be unbecoming of me to pursue it any further. What say you, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15?"

"I can see that Fellow Daoist Qilin 17 is very earnest in his proposal, so I'm also willing to hand over the cauldron to him. If the cauldron had been unearthed while you were unconscious, perhaps you would've been able to wake up a bit earlier," Han Li said with a faint smile.

"Thank you, fellow daoists."

Qilin 17 could hear the mockery in Han Li's words, and was just about to flare up with rage, but decided against it after recalling the power that Han Li had displayed during the recently concluded battle.

Thus, he immediately swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of yellow light to stow the cauldron away.

He then winced slightly at the sight of all of the precious materials and ingredients on the ground before looking away with a pained expression.

"Which one would you like out of these treasures and this jade box, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15?" Qilin asked.

"I lost two sets of flying swords during the battle just now, so I'd like to claim these treasures to replace them," Han Li replied.

"Aren't you cultivating water-attribute laws at the moment, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15? All of these are metal-attribute treasures, so they're not very suitable for you. In contrast, I just so happen to be using a metal-attribute cultivation art. Speaking of the jade box, given the power restrictions placed upon it, it must contain something extremely precious, so how about you take it instead, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15?" Qilin 9 proposed with a smile.

"Perhaps so, but the restrictions on the box are extremely troublesome to deal with, and if I'm not careful, the contents of the box could be easily destroyed. Out of the three of us, I think you're the one with the highest hopes of successfully opening the box, so I'll settle for those treasures instead," Han Li replied.

Chapter 255: Lying Low

"I beg to differ, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15. If it wasn't for you, the three of us may still not even have entered this valley yet, and that's a clear indication of how proficient you are at bypassing restrictions. If you can't open this box, then my chances of success are even slimmer. Surely you wouldn't force this thing onto me, would you?" Qilin 9 asked with a meaningful look in his eyes.

Han Li refused to budge, shaking his head in response. "You're far too kind, Fellow Daoist. I know what I'm capable of, and if I had to give a number, I would say my chances of opening this box are less than 10%. Given your cultivation base and status in the Transient Guild, you must have a large social circle, and surely there are experts in restrictions among your friends and acquaintances."

Qilin 9 was silent for a moment, then seemed to have arrived at some type of decision as he said, "You just want a few of these spirit treasures to make up for the losses you suffered earlier, right? How about this? Aside from this jade box and that failed pill, we can split everything else 60:40 in your favor. Surely that's sufficient compensation for you."

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this, but after some contemplation, he said, "I suppose I can accept that, but I'll have to go a step further. Among those materials and ingredients, those Horned Dragon Herbs and those lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood are particularly useful to me, so would you be able to hand them over to me? I can allow you to pick out items of equal value out of the rest of the things here as compensation."

"That's not a problem at all! You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist."

Qilin 9 cupped his fist toward Han Li in a salute upon hearing this, then swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of golden light, claiming all of the treasures on the ground.

He didn't actually care much for the rest of the treasures, but the nine star golden sword and the antiquated golden mirror that had served as the cores of the array were extremely pure metal-attribute spirit treasures that were very compatible with his cultivation arts. All he had to do was refine them for 1,000 years, and they would become no less powerful than immortal treasures, and that was why he was so insistent on acquiring them.

Han Li also swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a burst of azure light that claimed the purple jade box and the failed dao pill.

The two of them then turned their attention to the spirit plants, materials, and Immortal Origin Stones on the ground, and it didn't take long before they split everything among themselves.

With that, the distribution of spoils was complete, and Qilin 9 flicked a finger through the air to release a ball of fire, which incinerated Ping Yaozi's remains into ashes, then said, "Alright, time is of the essence, so let's get out of this place."

Han Li's brows were slightly furrowed as he heaved an internal sigh, but didn't say anything.

The three of them quickly flew out of the valley as three streaks of light, and several months later, they emerged from the teleportation hall on Smoke Tomb Island.

"The mission didn't quite progress as planned, but thankfully, we were able to survive the ordeal. This is the reward for the mission. With this, we can go our separate ways."

Qilin 9 pulled out a pair of storage pouches as he spoke, then handed them to Han Li and Qilin 17.

Han Li examined the contents of the storage pouch briefly with his spiritual sense, then gave a slight nod before stowing it away.

"I still have some matters to attend to, so I'll be taking my leave now."

Qilin 17 also stowed his storage pouch away, then cupped his fist in a parting salute and flew away into the distance as a streak of yellow light.

"Fellow Daoist Qilin 9, now that I think about it, the reward for this mission doesn't match its difficulty. Back when you were accepting this mission, surely you would've detected that something was amiss, right?" Han Li asked.

"What are you trying to say, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15?" Qilin 9 asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"I'm assuming the actual reward for this mission is far greater than what you've revealed to us, right? In any case, I'll also be taking my leave," Han Li said in a meaningful voice, then flew away into the distance as a streak of azure light.

"Hmph, of course I wouldn't have taken on such a perilous mission without a reward of corresponding value! I didn't think that an itinerant cultivator with such terrible aptitude would have so many tricks up his sleeve. It appears I've misevaluated him," Qilin 9 murmured to himself as he watched Han Li fly away into the distance, then vanished on the spot with a flash of golden light.

Meanwhile, Han Li was flying through the air with the purple jade box and the failed dao pill in his hands, and there was a faint smile on his face.

The refinement for the dao pill had failed, but it would still be a useful resource to be studied and examined.

As for the jade box, the restrictions on it appeared to have been quite profound, but in reality, during that earlier attempt to bypass the restrictions, Han Li had already thought of a way to break through them. Otherwise, there was no way that he would've agreed to take it.

Of course, he couldn't reveal this in the presence of Qilin 9 and Qilin 17. Otherwise, not only would that cause unnecessary trouble for himself, it would reduce his share of the spoils as well.

He was very curious about the contents of the box. Ping Yao was either a Heavenly Pill Master or very close to it, and such a prized possession of his had to have been extremely valuable.

With that in mind, a hint of excitement welled up in his heart, and he was itching to get back to his cave abode and unravel this mystery.

……

Several months later, in the Bell Toll Mountain Range.

Inside the main hall of the cave abode on the Crimson Dawn Peak, Han Li was seated on a taishi chair, holding a green teacup in his hand.

Meng Yungui and the others were quickly gathering before him, and after they had all arrived and paid their respects to him, Meng Yungui strode forward as he reported, "Elder Li, Sun Buzheng is currently at an important juncture in his seclusion, so he can't be present, but everyone else is here."

Han Li took a glance at his nine servants, all of whom had made significant progress in their cultivation since they had come here. Among them, the two with the highest cultivation bases were Meng Yungui and Sun Buzheng, but Meng Qianqian was the one who had been making the fastest progress.

At this moment, she was standing next to Meng Yungui, looking at Han Li with admiration glowing in her large and sparkling eyes.

"I'm going to have to leave the sect for a while soon, and I summoned all of you here today because I have some instructions to pass down," Han Li said.

Meng Yungui was rather taken aback to hear this, but he still cupped his fist in a salute as he prompted, "Please go ahead, Elder Li."

"Following my departure, the Crimson Dawn Peak will be temporarily closed to all visitors. During this time, all of you should also stay on the mountain unless it's absolutely necessary for you to leave. Just stay in your cave abodes and cultivate, and look after the spirit plants in the fields. As for cultivation resources, I'll give some to Yungui, so you won't have to worry about running out. Alright, you can all go now," Han Li said, then waved a hand to dismiss everyone.

"Yes, Elder Li," everyone replied in a respectful manner, then turned and departed from the hall.

Meng Yungui was waiting to be given the cultivation resources by Han Li, so he naturally didn't leave, and after a brief moment of hesitation, Meng Qianqian turned to depart as well.

"Qianqian, you stay behind as well," Han Li suddenly instructed.

Meng Qianqian was ecstatic to hear this, and she stopped in her tracks before turning around and making her way over to her brother's side.

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a blue storage pouch, which he tossed at Meng Yungui as he said, "I'm going to be away for quite a long time, but these pills should be enough to support everyone's cultivation needs. Just hand them out every once in a while. Also, there are some Origin Stabilization Pills in there, and you can give them to Sun Buzheng once he comes out of seclusion for him to consolidate his cultivation base."

Meng Yungui hurriedly caught the storage pouch as he nodded in response. "Yes, Elder Li."

"Alright, you can go now," Han Li instructed.

Meng Yungui took a glance at his sister with a slightly puzzled look in his eyes, but still did as he was told and departed from the hall.

"I went to take a look at the egg a few days ago, and I can tell you've been looking after it quite well. It still hasn't hatched yet, but even I was surprised by the abundant vitality within it," Han Li praised with a smile.

"Please forgive me for failing to hatch the egg even after so long," Meng Qianqian apologized as she lowered her head slightly.

"That's a matter that's mostly up to fate anyway, so there's no need to be overly critical of yourself. Just make sure to keep looking after the egg," Han Li said.

"Rest assured, Elder Li, I'll be sure to do my best," Meng Qianqian replied as she gave a firm nod.

Han Li smiled as he produced a small white jade vial that he tossed at her, and he said, "I obtained this vial of Fire Essence Pills during one of my earlier outings, and you're at a stage where you're ready to take it. It'll be very beneficial for your cultivation."

"Thank you, Elder Li," Meng Qianqian said with a wide smile as she hurriedly caught the vial.

"Alright, you can go as well," Han Li said with a dismissive wave of his hand.

However, Meng Qianqian remained standing on the spot with a rather hesitant look in her eyes.

"Is there something else you need to speak to me about?" Han Li asked.

"It's not been very long at all since you last left, yet you're leaving again, and you're closing the mountain to the outside... I'm just a little worried. Did something happen?" Meng Qianqian asked in a hesitant voice.

"What could possibly happen to a True Immortal like me, you silly girl?" Han Li chuckled.

"I see, it looks like I was just overly sensitive."

Meng Qianqian was very relieved to hear Han Li's response, and she promptly departed from the hall.

Following her departure, Han Li's smile immediately faded as a grim look appeared on his face.

He had brushed off her concerns, but in reality, her assumption hadn't been far from the truth.

It had only been three days since he returned to the sect, but close to a year had already passed since he left the Infernal Frost Continent.

Not only had Gu Jie's avatar identified them to be members of the Transient Guild, at the very end, it had also revealed to them that he was an elder of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, and that was certainly not good news for Han Li.

He had a feeling that staying in the sect at this time was not a wise move, so he had taken on a mission that required him to be far away from the sect so that he could lie low for a while.

With that in mind, he rose to his feet and exited the cave abode, then began flying down toward the foot of the Crimson Dawn Peak.

Chapter 256: Meddling

It didn't take long before he appeared in the cave where the underground fire vein was situated.

The air in the entire cave was still filled with a scorching aura, and molten lava was tumbling incessantly within the underground lake of lava, Occasionally, a bubble on the surface of the lake of lava would pop, producing a sound akin to a rumbling thunderclap.

The array that he had set up was still hovering above the lake, but all of the array flags had become devoid of luster, indicating that the array had been defunct for some time, and the fiery red cocoon at the center of the array was also nowhere to be seen.

Han Li immediately attempted to contact the Essence Fire Raven through their spiritual connection, and a clear cry instantly rang out from within the lake.

Immediately thereafter, the surface of the lake began to bulge, following which a silver figure sprang out before hurtling directly at Han Li at an extraordinary speed while giving off a scorching aura.

The silver figure flew straight into Han Li, sending a burst of burning pain surging across his chest.

Before he had a chance to reach out, the silver figure transformed into a tiny humanoid figure that was no more than two feet tall, and it rapidly flew in a circle around him in an agile fashion.

Much to Han Li's elation, he discovered that the silver figure was formed by none other than the Essence Fire Raven, and in this form, it resembled a child that was around five to six years of age.

Not only had its aura completely surpassed its peak back when it was in the Spirit Realm, even its eyes, which were formed by flames, were sparkling with intelligence, clearly indicating that it had made significant progress, and it would most likely keep making rapid progress if it were to continue cultivating here.

The tiny silver figure danced around Han Li for a while, then suddenly transformed into a fire ball before rising up and descending onto the palm of Han Li's hand, where it reverted back into the form of a small child.

Han Li gently patted the tiny silver figure's head, and it seemed to have been relishing his touch, narrowing its eyes in contentment as it rubbed its head against his hand.

"This place has clearly done wonders for you, but I have to leave for some time, and I don't know when I'll be able to return, so I'll have to take you with me," Han Li said, and it was unclear whether he was talking to himself or explaining the situation to the Essence Fire Raven.

To his surprise, the Essence Fire Raven seemed to have understood him, and it let loose an elated cry as it transformed into a fiery silver bird that flew straight upward.

After that, it circled around in the air before swooping back down and vanishing into Han Li's body in a flash, ready to follow him wherever he went.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and he withdrew the array and erased all signs that he had ever been here before turning to depart.

After leaving the cave, he traveled to the Gourd Peak rather than returning to his cave abode.

Having obtained so many Horned Dragon Herbs from Ping Yaozi's storage bracelet, it was time to begin attempting to refine Spring Rain Pills, and seeing as he was going to leave the sect, he had to purchase the recipe for the Spring Rain Pill prior to his departure.

Only when it was late into the night did he return to his cave abode without alerting anyone, and he gathered all of the spirit medicines from his garden that had reached sufficient maturity, then also retrieved the strange stone cauldron that had been offered to him by the monkey king before leaving the Blaze Dragon Dao.

……

Half a year later.

A streak of azure light came tumbling out of the sky above a massive mountain in the northern region of the Ancient Cloud Continent, and it crashed heavily into the mountain summit, causing half of the mountain to collapse violently.

After the dust settled, a middle-aged man with a cold expression was revealed standing on the collapsed mountain summit, wearing a suit of antiquated azure armor with golden patterns on its surface. The suit of armor wasn't giving off much of a glow, but it had an extremely solid and sturdy appearance.

The man was none other than Gu Jie!

Beneath his left boot was a portly man wearing an outer sect elder's robe of the Blaze Dragon Dao ,and blood was pouring down from the corner of his mouth as he desperately implored, "Please spare me, Senior! I honestly have no idea who you're looking for..."

However, Gu Jie's patience had run out, and he pointed a finger straight at the portly man's glabella.

A thread of azure light shot out of his fingertip before vanishing into the portly man's head, and the man gave a muffled groan before immediately losing consciousness.

Moments later, Gu Jie withdrew his finger, then gave a cold harrumph as he slammed a palm down onto the portly man's head, causing it to instantly explode like a watermelon.

As a result, a golden nascent soul was revealed with its entire body ensnared within a mass of azure threads. The golden light radiating from the nascent soul's body gradually dimmed until it completely faded, upon which the nascent soul disintegrated into nothingness.

Gu Jie remained standing on the spot with a contemplative expression, seemingly pondering something.

Moments later, he swept a hand through the air, and seven or eight blue masks appeared in the air before him.

He reached out toward the portly man's remains, and an azure horse mask flew out of his body to join the other masks that were hovering in mid-air.

"I've finally managed to dig up something useful. It looks like they are indeed in the Blaze Dragon Dao," Gu Jie murmured to himself as he inspected the mask, then reached out to make a grabbing motion with one hand, and the mask that was hovering before him was instantly crushed into powder.

Immediately thereafter, he vanished from the spot amid a flash of azure light.

……

Several months later, in a secluded valley in the eastern part of the Bell Toll Mountain Range.

At the entrance of the valley was a massive trench that was 100 feet wide, and it extended all the way to the end of the valley.

All of the snow and ice in the trench had melted away to reveal the rocky black surface underneath, and there were even many patches of moss and short weeds growing on the rocks.

On a cliff in the deepest part of the valley was a thin figure that had been bound tightly to the rock face behind them by a massive of azure vines.

A dark red line of blood ran all the way down from his head to his torso, and his body would've most likely split apart had it not been for the vines keeping the two halves together.

The man's face was very unremarkable, but he had a pair of tiny rat-like eyes that were quite memorable.

At this moment, Gu Jie was hovering in front of him, holding a shimmering golden nascent soul in his hand, and the nascent soul was struggling with all its might to escape, but to no avail.

"Who are the people who killed Ping Yaozi with you on that day, and where are they now?" Gu Jie asked.

"Even if... you're a Golden Immortal Stage elder of the Immortal Palace... you have no right... to barge into the Blaze Dragon Dao... Our dao lords won't let you get away with this..."

The nascent soul's voice was filled with horror and was cutting off intermittently, but it was still hoping to intimidate Gu Jie by bringing up the Blaze Dragon Dao.

"I know that there's a restriction in your nascent soul that makes it impossible for me to perform soul search technique by force, but I'm sure you've heard of a nascent planting technique, right? I have some top quality Dark Water Soil here, and if I plant your nascent soul into it... Oh, I'm really looking forward to seeing what'll happen," Gu Jie chuckled coldly.

The golden nascent soul shuddered in horror upon hearing this.

A nascent planting technique was a restorative technique used to nurture damaged nascent souls by planting them in spirit soil, but if a nascent soul were to be planted in contaminated soil, then it would become an extremely horrific torture method.

Once a nascent soul was planted into contaminated soil, it would constantly be subjected to the most excruciating pain imaginable until it eventually became a part of the soil. This process would take countless years to complete, and it was completely irreversible, robbing the owner of the nascent soul of any chance of reincarnation.

The nascent soul remained silent, and a cold smile appeared on Gu Jie's face as he said, "Looks like you're determined to test my patience."

He then flipped a hand over to produce an incense burner that was holding any sticks of incense. Instead, it was filled with a type of black soil that resembled fat, and it was giving off a foul odor that should've been unique to decaying bodies.

The golden nascent soul was even more horrified upon seeing this, and it hurriedly yelled, "I'll talk! Those two are..."

In reality, he didn't know who Qilin 9 and Wyrm 15 actually were, but in the face of Gu Jie's threats and absolute power, he had no choice but to tell Gu Jie everything that he knew, as well as his guesses on the identities of Qilin 9 and Wyrm 15.

After hearing what the nascent soul had to say, a sinister smile appeared on Gu Jie's face as he abruptly tightened his grip and crushed the nascent soul into nothingness.

He then made a beckoning motion with his other hand, and Qilin 17's storage bracelet flew into his grasp.

After taking a moment to refine the storage bracelet, he swept a hand through the air, and a golden pill cauldron and an azure rat mask instantly appeared before him.

Gu Jie raised a hand to stroke the golden cauldron, and a series of concealment runes instantly appeared on its surface, releasing an azure glow while giving off a burst of peculiar fluctuations.

"I'm impressed that he was able to conceal most of the mark I left on this cauldron. No wonder I could only track down the cauldron to the Ancient Cloud Continent, but couldn't verify its exact location beyond that," Gu Jie mused as he raised an eyebrow.

After that, he stowed the cauldron, the mask, and the storage bracelet away before flying deeper into the Blaze Dragon Dao.

Close to a month later, an azure figure was flying through the air above a vast snowland near the central region of the Blaze Dragon Dao.

Behind it was a massive white snow lotus flower that was traveling at even higher speed, and it was steadily closing in on the azure figure.

Reclined within the snow lotus flower was a voluptuous woman in a pristine white dress.

She was wearing a crimson fox mask that covered her face, leaving everything to the beholder's imagination, as well as giving her an aura of mystery.

On the glabella of the mask was inscribed the number "3" in the form of a peculiar rune.

The gap between the azure figure and the snow lotus flower was steadily closing, and all of a sudden, both of them drew to a halt while they were still separated by several thousand feet.

The woman in white continued to recline in her snow lotus flower with her head resting on the palm of her hand, and she was holding a white flower in her other hand as she cast a seductive gaze toward Gu Jie.

"I don't want to fight you, but that's not because I fear you! I'd advise you not to test my patience!" Gu Jie declared in a cold voice as he cast his gaze toward the woman in the snow lotus flower.

"It's not like I'm a tigress that's going to eat you, so of course you have no reason to fear me. However, as an elder of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace, you've barged into our Blaze Dragon Dao and gone on a killing spree without any explanation. Could it be that you think that our Blaze Dragon Dao fears your Immortal Palace?" the woman asked.

"You're wearing a Transient Guild mask right now, yet you keep bringing up the Blaze Dragon Dao. Aren't you meddling in business that has nothing to do with you? Do you not have anything better to do with your time?" Gu Jie chuckled coldly.

"Truth be told, I have been feeling quite bored lately, and you just so happened to appear at this juncture," the woman sighed.

Her voice was as pleasant as a warm spring breeze, and there was also a seductive quality to it that struck Gu Jie's mind with a numbing sensation.

Chapter 257: Returning a Favor

"How dare you try to bewitch me!" Gu Jie yelled in a thunderous voice that instantly drowned out the woman's laughter.

With a flick of his wrist, a burst of spatial fluctuations erupted in front of him, and an azure flying sword shot out of thin air, hurtling directly toward the woman.

The woman didn't appear to have done anything in response, but the snow lotus flower beneath her suddenly began to glow with dazzling radiance, and a pristine flower petal rose up in front of her like a shield.

A sharp clang rang out as the tip of the azure flying sword pierced about an inch into the flower petal, but it was unable to progress any further than that.

Gu Jie made a hand seal and began to chant an incantation upon seeing this, and the runes on the azure flying sword suddenly lit up, while a tiny speck of azure light the size of a grain of rice emerged the tip of the flying sword, giving off a strong wood-attribute aura.

As the speck of azure light appeared, the entire flower petal began to turn from a pristine white color to a glowing jade-like color, and all of a sudden, the speck of azure light brightened drastically, following which a translucent azure thread shot out from within.

The azure thread was as thin as a strand of hair and appeared to have been extremely fragile, but it was astonishingly fast and instantly pierced through the flower petal before hurtling into the flower itself.

The masked woman's expression stiffened slightly upon seeing this, and she swept the white flower in her hand toward the azure thread.

A pair of dull thuds rang out as the azure thread pierced through two layers of flower petals before dissipating into nothingness, while two of the white petals of the flower that the woman was holding turned black before wilting away and detaching themselves from the flower.

"Don't you know you have to be gentle with women?"

The masked woman gently stroked the white flower with a displeased expression, then rose to her feet and flicked a finger toward the tip of the azure flying sword that had pierced into the snow lotus flower petal.

The azure flying sword instantly shuddered violently as if it had been dealt a heavy blow, then flew back through the air before landing in Gu Jie's grasp.

As soon as Gu Jie closed his hand around the hilt of the flying sword, he was instantly struck by an itchy sensation in the palm of his hand, and he looked down to find that the hilt of the flying sword was covered in some type of pink powder.

Before he had a chance to let go of the sword, countless vibrant and colorful butterflies suddenly flew out of the pink powder, quickly enveloping his entire body.

Gu Jie's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and bright azure light erupted from all of the patterns on his suit of armor. A series of slender azure vines instantly emerged from his armor before spreading in all directions, swallowing up all of the butterflies and eradicating all of them in the blink of an eye.

However, he then discovered to his surprise that the masked woman and the white snow lotus flower were both nowhere to be seen, and even their auras had completely vanished.

He quickly swung around to inspect his surroundings, only to find that there was nothing around him, and even the snowland down below had disappeared.

"An illusion like this won't be enough to trap me!" Gu Jie scoffed, then closed his eyes and began to chant an incantation.

As he did so, a glimmer of azure light appeared in his hand, and all of the patterns on his suit of armor and the flying sword in his grasp lit up in unison, releasing a burst of dazzling green radiance.

Moments later, his eyes sprang open, and he gripped onto his sword with both hands before swinging it down in a forceful motion.

Seven massive azure sword projections, each of which was over 10,000 feet tall, appeared behind him in a flash, then came crashing down like falling mountains.

A string of resounding booms rang out in the air as the seven sword projections came crashing down one after another, causing the entire space to tremble violently.

However, after the tremors finally subsided, his surroundings remained completely empty, and nothing had changed.

Gu Jie's expression finally changed slightly upon seeing this, and only now did he come to realize that he seemed to have been situated in a space of absolute nothingness.

Right at this moment, the masked woman's voice rang out in the surrounding space. "I don't think there's a need for us to continue our battle any further beyond this point, Fellow Daoist Gu. How about we sit down and have a chat now?"

"What do you want to talk about?" Gu Jie asked.

"I've already gathered some information about the situation, and it seems like the people you're looking for were only carrying out a mission for the Transient Guild, so they haven't done anything wrong," the masked woman said.

"That's preposterous! They killed a True Immortal cultivator of our Immortal Palace who was extremely likely to become a Heavenly Pill Master, yet you say that they did nothing wrong? In that case, am I not also well within my rights to seek vengeance for Ping Yaozi?" Gu Jie countered in an enraged voice.

"It's true that you're not at fault, either, except they only killed a single member of your Immortal Palace, yet you've already killed far more than just one member of the Blaze Dragon Dao. Am I correct in saying that?" the masked woman asked.

"How could those people possibly compare with Ping Yaozi?" Gu Jie scoffed.

"That's your perspective on this matter. From my perspective, you've already gone too far, and it's time that you stopped," the masked woman replied in a calm voice.

"I'm not going to stop pursuing this matter until the other two perpetrators are also dead!" Gu Jie harrumphed coldly.

A cold look finally appeared on the masked woman's face upon hearing this, and she said, "I'm only willing to negotiate with you as you're a member of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace. If you continue to be so rude and unreasonable, then even if I can't kill you here, I can at least seal 12 of your immortal acupoints and severely suppress your power.

“The Immortal Palace isn't going to declare war on both the Blaze Dragon Dao and the Transient Guild at once over a Golden Immortal like yourself. Otherwise, you wouldn't have come here alone."

Gu Jie finally fell silent upon hearing this.

"I can turn a blind eye to the people that you've killed up to this point as long as you don't go any further than this. If you know what's good for you, then you'd leave the Ancient Cloud Continent right away."

The masked woman's voice grew fainter and fainter, and all of a sudden, a burst of light appeared above Gu Jie, following which several massive flower petals opened up to release him from the space that he was trapped in.

Immediately thereafter, the giant white snow lotus flower vanished on the spot amid a flash of white light.

Gu Jie remained hovering in mid-air for a while with a contemplative look on his face, then finally flew away toward the north as a streak of azure light.

Half a day later, on a nameless mountain range in the Blaze Dragon Dao.

Inside the belly of the mountain was a large circular altar, around which stood eight black stone pillars. There was a lit brazier on each of the stone pillars, within which some type of oil was burning, giving off a crimson glow that illuminated the entire surrounding space.

A tall and broad figure in a black cloak with an azure deer mask on his face was pacing back and forth on the altar while rubbing his hands together, appearing to be quite anxious and agitated.

It was none other than Qilin 9.

He had already heard about all of the Transient Guild members that had been killed within the territory of the Blaze Dragon Dao, and through his sources in the guild, he had deduced that the Golden Immortal Stage elder of the Northern Glacial Immortal Palace was responsible for all the killings.

He had originally planned to find an excuse to leave the sect and travel to some secluded region, only returning to the sect after making a breakthrough to the Golden Immortal Stage, but right as he was about to set off, he received a message from a high-ranking member of the Transient Guild, instructing him to remain within this mountain in the Bell Toll Mountain Range for his own safety, and to await further news.

However, close to a year had already passed by with not a single update, and he was starting to grow quite concerned.

Right at this moment, a burst of white light appeared at the center of the altar, and a white snow lotus flower appeared before blooming to reveal a woman in a white dress.

"Dao Lord Yun... I mean, Senior Qilin 3," Qilin 9 hurriedly greeted.

"The matter concerning Gu Jie has already been settled, but I'd advise you not to set foot on the Infernal Frost Continent for the next 1,000 years," the woman declared in an indifferent voice.

"Thank you, Senior Qilin 3," Qilin 9 hurriedly said in a respectful voice as he extended a deep bow.

"I've repaid you for the favor that I owe you, and I won't intervene even if you get yourself into any further trouble from now on, so do try to be more prudent in your future decision-making," the woman said, then vanished from the spot amid a flash of white light.

Qilin 9 could only extend a parting bow with a wry smile on his face.

After that, he removed his deer mask, and his body abruptly shrank down into a short and stocky man wearing a lavish golden robe. It was none other than Xiong Shan.

……

To the east of the Ancient Cloud Continent was a deep blue sea that hadn't frozen solid.

Within this region of the sea was a ring-shaped coral island, beneath which was a trench that was over 100,000 feet deep.

At the bottom of the trench was a gray stone monument that was over 100 feet tall, and it was riddled with holes of different depths and sizes from the erosion of the surrounding seawater. Furthermore, it was covered in a layer of black seaweed, making it appear identical from the average rock on the seabed.

As it turned out, this gray stone monument was actually the entrance of a secret area under the jurisdiction of the Blaze Dragon Dao.

On a white stone plaza hovering in the air above a lush mountain within the secret area was Han Li, who was peering into the distance with his hands resting on the railing in front of him.

He could see a series of tall mountains that were covered in lush undergrowth, all of which were suspended in mid-air. The bases of the mountains were completely disconnected from the ground, and there were only countless lush green vines trailing down from the mountains into the gray mist below.

This secret area was filled with thousands of these floating mountains, and the entire area was filled with abundant world's origin qi. All of the mountains were laden with all types of premium spirit medicines, including ones that were ingredients required to refine various types of earthly pills.

Beneath these floating mountains was a bottomless mist-filled canyon, within which resided many strange humanoid creatures with grayish-white skin.

There were no books or records that assigned any names to these creatures, so those in the Blaze Dragon Dao referred to them as "white ghosts".

Under normal circumstances, these white ghosts wouldn't leave the canyon to venture onto the floating mountains, but once every few years, the mist within the canyon would spill over and rise up toward the floating mountains up above without any warning.

Whenever this happened, a large number of white ghosts would come rushing out of the canyon before climbing onto the floating mountains to devour the spirit plants growing upon them, and whenever any cultivators tried to stop them, battles would ensue.

These white ghosts weren't all that formidable individually, but their numbers were vast, and they had no regard for their own safety, so neither the cultivators nor the white ghosts had been able to gain the upper hand during the large-scale conflicts that had arisen between the two parties throughout history.

In order to keep these white ghosts at bay once and for all, a dao lord of the Blaze Dragon Dao who was proficient in the art of arrays had set up powerful restrictions on the bases of the floating mountains that were able to keep the rising mist at bay, thereby preventing the white ghost invasions altogether.

However, people soon noticed that without the mist rising up from the canyon once every few years, the number of spirit plants on the floating mountains steadily declined year after year, to the point that some of the more prized species of spirit plants went extinct altogether.

Only then did the cultivators of the Blaze Dragon Dao come to realize that this secret area contained a unique symbiotic ecosystem, and that it was not to be tampered with without consequences.

After that, the dao lord removed the restrictions, and an order was also released prohibiting members of the Blaze Dragon Dao from engaging the white ghosts in battle unless they appeared on the floating mountains in areas that weren't encompassed within the mist.

Furthermore, in order to prevent unforeseen mishaps, there was a large number of Spatial Tempering Stage disciples and puppets stationed in the secret area, and at least one True Immortal Stage elder was also required to be present in the secret area at all times.

Han Li was currently serving as the True Immortal Stage elder overseeing proceedings in this secret area.

Chapter 258: Opening the Box

Han Li was looking out at the unique scenery of the secret area with a rather absentminded expression, and it was clear that his mind was elsewhere.

He had already been here for over a month, and during that time, he had determined that the only way to enter and exit this place was through that sole entrance. Hence, he had set up some restrictions at the entrance and also left a wisp of his spiritual sense behind so that he would be alerted in advance if Gu Jie were to ever come after him in this secret area.

Of course, the fact that there was only a single entrance and exit meant that it was also rather troublesome for him to escape this place.

In order to resolve this issue, Han Li had made a trip to the southern end of the Ancient Cloud Continent before coming here, and there, he had carved out a cave on a secluded cliff face near the Thunderstorm Sea.

Inside the cave, he had used nine lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood to set up a stable lightning array that could facilitate ultra long-distance teleportation, and he had also left a spiritual mark there.

As a result, whenever he used his lightning array for teleportation, he would be able to instantly teleport himself to that cave thanks to the spiritual mark that he had left there.

Even if Gu Jie really were to track him down to this place, he would be able to instantly teleport himself to the cave before fleeing into the Thunderstorm Sea, and there was a very good chance that he would be able to escape.

However, due to the fact that the lightning array was constantly active, it was constantly using up the power of lightning within the lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood, so it would only be able to last no more than a century before going defunct.

"I've done everything that I can, so there's no point in worrying about things outside of my control," Han Li murmured to himself, then turned and made his way toward the cave abode on the other side of the plaza.

After returning to the secret chamber in the cave abode, Han Li sat down with his legs crossed, then flipped a hand over to produce two thin sheets of yellow paper, which he began examining closely.

The two sheets of paper contained the recipes for the Origin Unifying Pill and the Spring Rain Pill.

In order to advance his own cultivation base as quickly as possible, he would have to refine large batches of earthly pills to enhance his progress.

At this point, he had already become quite skilled at refining Origin Unifying Pills, achieving a far higher success rate than before. He had never refined any Spring Rain Pills, but he was confident that it wouldn't have been very difficult thanks to his Mantra Treasured Axis.

He also had a decent supply of ingredients required to refine these two types of pills, but in order to plan for the future, he had still planted most of his spirit medicine seeds in the private spirit medicine garden in his cave abode.

He knew that even though he had obtained two earthly pill recipes, his body would eventually begin to develop tolerance if he were to repeatedly consume the same types of pills, and once that happened, the pills would no longer be as efficacious as before.

Hence, he required a more diverse range of earthly pill recipes.

For this purpose, he had released a mission in the Transient Guild, expressing a desire to exchange resources for earthly pill recipes, but pill recipes of this caliber were extremely rare and precious, and he hadn't been able to secure any further recipes through that avenue.

All of a sudden, he flipped a hand over to produce a purple jade box, the very same one that had once belonged to Ping Yaozi.

The fact that the box had been so closely guarded by someone who was close to becoming a Heavenly Pill Master indicated that whatever was inside had to have been extremely precious, and there was a chance that it contained Ping Yaozi's collection of pill recipes.

He swept his gaze over the patterns on the surface of the purple box, then flipped a hand over to summon around a dozen black flags, each of which was only around an inch in size. The flags were made from a black metallic material with many complex patterns engraved onto them.

Han Li planted these metal flags in a circle into the stone ground, then raised a finger and began inscribing lines onto the ground in between the flags.

Before long, a tiny yet complex array had taken shape on the ground.

Han Li set the purple jade box down onto the center of the array, then made a hand seal as he began to chant an incantation.

As he did so, all of the patterns on the black flags and the array engraved into the ground lit up in unison.

A burst of dazzling light then erupted out of the array at Han Li's behest to swallow up the entire purple jade box, and the silver talisman that was adhered tightly to the box suddenly erupted into flames.

The flames illuminated all of the patterns engraved onto the surface of the box, giving it a glittering and translucent appearance, as if it were a gorgeous piece of purple crystal. However, Han Li didn't get a chance to appreciate its beauty as the box had suddenly began to tremble violently, and the patterns on its surface were glowing brighter and brighter, looking as if they were about to crack open.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately activated his Brightsight Spirit Eyes.

In doing so, he discovered that there were secret runes engraved onto the interior of the box, and all of these runes had lit up, initiating a self-destruct sequence to destroy the jade box and its contents.

There were two layers of restrictions placed upon the jade box, and if one were to only remove the silver talisman, the secret runes on the inside of the box would be activated to destroy everything.

In this tense situation, Han Li immediately summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis, and it appeared behind him in the form of a golden wheel that was around a foot in size, slowly revolving in mid-air.

The Mantra Treasured Axis began to revolve faster at his behest, and it released countless golden ripples that spread through the air in all directions, instantly encompassing the entire surrounding area in a radius of 100 feet.

All of a sudden, everything in the secret chamber aside from Han Li himself was slowed down.

The runes within the purple jade box had been flashing so quickly that it had appeared as if they had been glowing continuously this entire time, and only now that they had been slowed down did Han Li discover that they were actually flashing.

He immediately made a rapid string of hand seals before quickly rearranging the black flags with both hands, creating a brand new miniature array in the blink of an eye.

After that, the new array began to radiate dazzling light at his behest, and a burst of black light shot out of the black flags like miniature arrows before hurtling into the box.

Inside the jade box, the light glowing from the concealed runes faded, and the flame that was burning outside the box also gradually shrank down.

By the time the flame was completely snuffed out, the patterns on the box had also fallen dark, and the box opened up on its own with a faint crack.

Han Li withdrew the Mantra Treasured Axis back into his own body, then reached out to make a grabbing motion, drawing the purple jade box into his grasp.

He had already set up a high-level restrictive array outside the secret chamber, so he wasn't concerned that the jade box would contain some type of secret mechanism that would expose his current location.

He peered into the box to find that it was completely empty with the exception of a stack of thin golden pages laying at the bottom.

Han Li released his spiritual sense to verify that there weren't any spiritual marks planted on the pages, and only then did he pick them up for a closer examination.

The words "Growth Bearing Pill" were inscribed on the top sheet of paper in ancient text, and below that was the recipe and refinement method for the pill.

An elated look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this. Just as he expected, the box contained Ping Yaozi's collection of pill recipes.

After briefly reading through the first page in the stack, he flipped through a dozen or so of the pages that came after the first one, and to his elation, he discovered that most of them were earthly pill recipes. Including the recipe for the Growth Bearing Pill, there were as many as seven earthly pill recipes.

However, this made sense to him after he considered the fact that Ping Yaozi already possessed the ability to refine dao pills prior to his demise.

With these seven earthly pill recipes in addition to the recipes for the Origin Unifying Pill and the Spring Rain Pill, he wasn't going to have to dedicate any time and energy to searching for more earthly pill recipes anytime soon.

According to the description of the pill enclosed in the recipe, Han Li was able to confirm beyond a reasonable doubt that the vial of yellow pills he had obtained from Ping Yaozi earlier was a vial of Growth Bearing Pills.

These pills seemed to have been of a higher caliber than Spring Rain PIlls, and of course, the spirit medicines used for their refinement were all extremely precious.

Thankfully, this secret area of floating mountains was a natural treasure trove of spirit medicines, so he could source many of the ingredients here, and given his status, the sect definitely wasn't going to come after him if he only collected a batch of spirit medicines that were no more than 100 years of age.

After that, he would just have to nurture those spirit medicines to the correct age with the spirit liquid from the Heaven Controlling Vial, and he could purchase any ingredients that he couldn't find with Immortal Origin Stones.

Han Li suppressed the elation in his heart as he picked up the jade box, and he was just about to put all of the pill recipes back into the box when he suddenly noticed that something didn't seem to have been quite right with the bottom of the box.

He flipped a hand over to produce a dagger that was as thin as a willow leaf, then plunged it into the edge of the jade box before gently prying it upward.

A faint crack rang out, and a purple jade board that was as smooth as a mirror was pried up from the bottom of the box.

The jade board wasn't much thicker than a sheet of paper, and Han Li picked it up before carefully examining it.

With the light of the flames in the secret chamber, he could see that the jade board was riddled with countless extremely thin runes that were interconnected to form an extremely complex design.

Han Li released his spiritual sense to encompass the jade board, and as soon as his spiritual sense came into contact with the board, a layer of golden light instantly rose up from all of the patterns on its surface, releasing a series of golden runes that repelled his spiritual sense.

After a few more attempts, he was still unable to make any progress, so he could only give up on this endeavor for now.

It wasn't that he couldn't forcibly bypass the golden light barrier with his spiritual sense. Instead, he simply didn't want to risk breaking the jade board as he had a feeling that it was something quite precious.

In the end, he could only place the jade board back into the box along with the pill recipes before stowing the box away again.

After that, he swept a sleeve through the air, and a gray stone cauldron appeared in front of him amid a flash of light before landing on the ground with a dull thud.

Chapter 259: Busy at Work

The stone cauldron was the same one that he had obtained from the monkey king, and the monkey wine inside had already been removed, but due to the fact that the monkey wine had been in there for a long time, it was still giving off a faint wine aroma.

Han Li took a deep breath, then quickly made a string of strange hand seals.

Bursts of azure light flew out of his palms in succession before landing upon the stone cauldron, and the eight large runes engraved onto its surface instantly began to glow with silver light.

It worked!

Han Li was ecstatic to see this.

Sure enough, the treasure refinement method that he had obtained from Qilin 9 was effective on this cauldron.

More incantation seals continued to fly out of his hands as he began to chant and incantation, and the light radiating from the runes on the stone cauldron became brighter and brighter.

A string of faint cracks rang out from the cauldron, and a series of patterns similar to the veins of the a leaf appeared on its surface before also radiating dazzling silver light.

Chunks of stone slid off the cauldron amid the silver light before crashing to the ground, and as a result, the cauldron rapidly shrank in size, reduced to only around half its original size before too long.

By the time all of the silver light faded, the original stone cauldron had been replaced by a silver pill cauldron with complex patterns engraved onto its surface. Those eight runes were still present, but they had become even more beautiful and intricate than before.

Refining pills in a cauldron like this must have many benefits.

After taking a moment to observe the material and the aura of the cauldron, he discovered that it wasn't inferior to Ping Yaozi's golden cauldron in the slightest.

All of a sudden, a fiery silver figure that was no more than two feet tall flew out of his body amid a flash of silver light, and it jumped onto the ground before immediately having its attention drawn to the pill cauldron before it. It took a few glances at the cauldron, then looked back at Han Li before circling around the cauldron.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he issued an instruction to the silver figure, and it immediately jumped into the lid of the cauldron. Immediately thereafter, its round cheeks began to bulge, and a massive burst of fire that was completely disproportionate to its own body came surging out of its mouth.

The silver flame swept through the air in an arc, then flew under the cauldron and immediately began to burn fiercely.

As this happened, a wave of scorching heat spread through the entire secret chamber.

A short while later, all of the spirit patterns on the silver cauldron lit up, and it gradually took on a crimson hue, while the cauldron itself also rose up into the air while swaying slightly from side to side.

The tiny silver figure seated on the lid of the cauldron seemed to have been greatly intrigued by this, and it scooted over to the edge of the cauldron's lid, swaying with the cauldron while its little legs were dangling over the edge of the lid.

With a sweep of his sleeve, Han Li summoned a batch of around a dozen spirit medicines, including a Blaze Tuber Herb.

He then rubbed his hands together momentarily, and all of the spirit medicines were instantly reduced to medicinal powder.

Immediately thereafter, he brought two of his fingers together before raising them up, and the cauldron of the lid beneath the tiny silver figure instantly flew up into the air at his behest.

The medicinal powder that was suspended in mid-air was drawn into the cauldron by a burst of invisible force, following which the lid of the cauldron also fell into place with an audible click.

Immediately thereafter, the eight runes on the silver cauldron lit up one after another.

The silver flame beneath the cauldron seemed to have been restricted by some type of invisible force, causing it to twist and swirl, becoming a miniature fiery tornado that enveloped the entire cauldron.

The fiery silver figure seated on the cauldron's lid instantly transformed into a silver fire raven as it flew into the fiery tornado to become one with it.

The fiery tornado abruptly shuddered, and the heat radiating from it increased by several fold.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this.

At this rate, it was going to take far less time to refine this batch of pills, but the success rate was still yet to be seen.

Time slowly passed by, and Han Li was occasionally using his Mantra Treasured Axis for assistance during the pill refinement process. The cauldron was radiating rainbow light, but no medicinal aroma had begun to waft out of the cauldron up to this point.

Around 16 hours later, the rainbow light glowing from the cauldron suddenly faded, and the cauldron reverted back to its original silver color, except some parts were red-hot.

The silver flame swept back before converging to reform a fiery silver figure, which flew out from under the cauldron before landing on Han Li's shoulder.

A loud clang rang out as the silver cauldron landed back on the ground.

Han Li's brows were slightly furrowed as he approached the cauldron, then gently swept a sleeve toward it.

The lid of the silver cauldron was removed, and an extremely rich medicinal aroma instantly wafted out to fill the entire secret chamber.

Han Li peered into the cauldron to find 16 golden pills laying inside, and they were still giving off faint wisps of white mist from the residual heat that they retained.

This is incredible! Not only has this cauldron significantly shortened the time required to refine these pills, it's also produced a far larger batch than usual!

Han Li suppressed his elation as he stored the pills into a jade vial, then swept a sleeve through the air to summon another batch of ingredients to refine some more pills.

……

Several months later, the silver flames within the secret chamber faded, and a silver fire raven flew out from under the cauldron. It transformed into a fiery silver figure that landed on the ground, then skipped over to Han Li before climbing up onto his shoulder along his robes.

There was a slightly weary look on Han Li's face as he turned to the fiery silver figure with a smile, then made his way over to the silver cauldron.

The lid of the cauldron flew off at his behest, and a rich medicinal aroma was instantly released.

Han Li made a grabbing motion to pull out the pills in the cauldron for an examination, and he discovered that they had a bright green hue and each of them was around the same size as a longan.

"Not bad! 11 pills is already a lot more than I would normally be able to refine in one batch," he remarked to himself as he flipped a hand over to store the pills into a white jade vial.

A thought then suddenly occurred to him, and he sat down with his legs crossed before flipping a hand over to produce his Transient Guild mask, which he promptly put on.

A massive array was projected onto the wall of the secret chamber amid a flash of azure light, and Han Li began to carefully inspect the missions column on the left side of the array.

After a long while, he withdrew his gaze before removing his mask, and a grim look appeared on his face as he heaved a faint sigh.

He had noticed that all of the missions released by Qilin 17 had disappeared. Barring the extremely slim chance that all of the missions had been withdrawn or completed, something had to have happened to him or his Transient Guild mask.

Han Li took a moment to check the spiritual marks that he had left at the entrance of this secret area and the cliff near the Thunderstorm Sea, and both of them were still intact.

Around a dozen years passed by in the blink of an eye.

He had spent half of this time refining pills, and he had also derived many crystals containing the laws of time using the Heaven Controlling Vial.

On this day, several dozen young men and women dressed in Blaze Dragon Dao disciple robes converged from directions, landing on the plaza in front of the entrance of Han Li's cave abode.

Han Li was standing before them, and his gaze roamed over them as he called out a few names.

"Hu Zhen, Luo Tang, Xin Sui..."

The young men and women who had had their names called immediately stepped forward before cupping their fists toward Han Li in a collective salute.

All of them were at the pinnacle of the Spatial Tempering Stage, and they were the most formidable ones among the disciples stationed in this secret area.

"I'm going into seclusion for a while, so I'll be counting on you to take care of all of the affairs in the secret area. There's no need to report to me unless something important or urgent arises," Han Li instructed.

"Yes, Elder Li," the disciples answered in unison.

"I'll be leaving a secret talisman with you. If you encounter a situation that you can't handle on your own, just inject your spiritual power into the talisman, and it'll fly into my cave abode to notify me," Han Li said.

The disciples gave an affirmative response once again.

A dark-skinned young man stepped forward to accept the secret talisman with both hands as he said, "Rest assured, Elder Li, we'll be sure to perform our duties diligently."

Han Li nodded in response as he waved a dismissive hand and said, "Alright, you can all go now."

Everyone extended a collective parting salute, then flew away as streaks of light.

Close to a day later, the mountain that Han Li was situated on began to shudder, and pillars of azure light rose up into the heavens, then converged in the sky to form a massive azure light barrier that encompassed the entire mountain.

Inside a newly carved out giant cave on the mountain, there was a fire pit in the stone wall to the left, and on the stone table next to the fire pit were seven or eight different types of spirit materials.

The most eye-catching ones among them were around a dozen chunks of dark golden metal the size of human heads, and a fist-sized white rock with many flower-petal-like patterns on its surface.

These were none other than the Dendrobium Gold Essence and the Jade Gleam Cloud Stone.

Han Li was standing beside the fire pit, and he drew the Jade Gleam Cloud Stone into his grasp, gently massaging it to feel its warm and smooth texture.

During the time that he had spent in this secret area, he had been refining pills while keeping up with news from the Blaze Dragon Dao, and according to his sources, it appeared that Gu Jie was no longer situated near the Blaze Dragon Dao.

Hopefully, he was forced away by a certain Golden Immortal of the sect.

Even so, Han Li still didn't dare to underestimate the wrath of a Golden Immortal, so he didn't let down his guard.

At this point, he had already refined quite a large number of pills, and he was planning to begin consuming these pills and resuming his cultivation soon.

However, prior to that, he had to refine his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords again.

He pointed a finger forward, and a joyful cry rang out within his body as the Essence Fire Raven flew out of his fingertip before hurtling into the fire pit, setting it alight.

A scorching silver flame instantly appeared within the fire pit.

Chapter 260: Sword Refinement

Han Li gently extended a hand forward, and the Jade Gleam Cloud Stone sitting on the palm of his hand slowly flew into the silver flame, enveloped within a burst of immortal spiritual power.

The silver flame immediately swallowed up the Jade Gleam Cloud Stone and began to burn it.

Time slowly passed by, but the white stone was still maintaining its original form, displaying no changes at all.

Han Li remained unfazed as he made a hand seal while chanting an incantation, and rings of crimson light suddenly appeared around the fire pit, following which a series of antiquated-looking runes began to emerge.

Following the emergence of those runes, the silver flames within the fire pit instantly rose up, and it became enveloped by a layer of crimson light. There wasn't much change to its heat, but it was giving off a type of peculiar fluctuations that were finally bringing about a slight change in the Jade Gleam Cloud Stone.

A sizzling sound rang out as the stone gradually began to melt within the silver flames, producing drops of waxy white liquid that hovered within the fire.

An extremely strong sandalwood aroma instantly filled the entire secret chamber.

Han Li immediately withdrew his outstretched hand upon seeing this, and the Jade Gleam Cloud Stone, which had already completely liquefied at this point, was instantly pulled out of the fire by his immortal spiritual power.

He then reached out with his other hand, which was holding a black stone vial with fiery red patterns all over its surface, and he used the vial to store the liquefied Jade Gleam Cloud Stone.

As soon as the white liquid flowed into the vial, a circle of runes instantly lit up on its surface, and the entire vial turned scorching hot, like a red-hot piece of metal.

A layer of azure light appeared over Han Li's hand, and he sealed the opening of the vial before setting it down onto the stone table beside him.

After that, he swept a sleeve through the air, and a chunk of Dendrobium Gold Essence rose up before landing in the fire pit.

This time, he made no hand seals to manipulate the array in the fire pit. Instead, he made his way over to a stone platform at the center of the cave that was around half a foot tall, and he sat down with his legs crossed, allowing the silver flame to melt the chunk of metal on its own.

All of the patterns on the surface of the chunk of Dendrobium Gold Essence began to give off a golden glow within the scorching flame, but it displayed no signs of melting.

Han Li only took a brief glance at it before closing his eyes to rest.

Seven days and seven nights later.

The silver flame was still raging within the fire pit, and at this point, the chunk of Dendrobium Gold Essence had already turned a crimson color. It was like a chunk of melting ice, and drops of molten golden liquid were dripping down from it.

Beneath it was a black stone vial that was twice as large as the one from before, and it was catching all of the drops of molten golden liquid.

Only after another entire day had passed by did the chunk of Dendrobium Gold Essence completely melt into liquid.

Han Li opened his eyes and strode forward to retrieve the black stone vial, then sent another chunk of Dendrobium Gold Essence flying into the fire pit.

Three months later.

Inside the cave, Han Li was standing beside the fire pit, holding a book with a beasthide cover in one hand. He was reading the book with a look of concentration on his face while scribbling something into the air with the index finger of his other hand.

Several thousand yellow pages were strewn across the stone platform beside him, and there was a series of extremely strange-looking patterns inscribed onto every single one of them.

The patterns on the sheets of paper near the bottom were extremely thick and chaotic, but the closer to the top one looked, the more slender and orderly the patterns they would find.

The patterns on the four sheets of paper at the top were already extremely intricate, resembling four large circular flowers.

The only part of the stone platform that wasn't laden with sheets of paper was its upper left corner, and there were around a dozen vials of different sizes placed there, containing all of the spirit liquids required for the upcoming sword refinement.

Aside from the time that he spent on refining those spirit liquids, Han Li had spent all of the rest of his time on studying the smelting sword refinement technique recorded in the book that he was holding, as well as practicing the accompanying array patterns.

Even though he had already made several thousand attempts, he was still not satisfied with the patterns that he was currently able to inscribe. He couldn't shake the feeling that there was something missing, and that was why he had refrained from commencing the refinement process this entire time.

Moments later, Han Li set down the book and closed his eyes, seemingly having fallen into deep thought. He remained standing still on the spot while tracing his right index and middle fingers through the air, as if he were still visualizing the patterns.

After a long while, his eyes suddenly sprang open as if he had been struck by a spark of inspiration, and he quickly made his way over to the fire pit.

A layer of golden scales appeared over his hand amid a flash of golden light, instantly covering his outstretched index and middle fingers.

After that, he crouched down beside the fire pit, plunging his fingers straight down into one of the rocks that had been used to construct the fire pit.

He then closed his eyes and rid himself of all unnecessary thoughts, immersing himself entirely in the vision of the patterns that he wanted to inscribe as his fingers began to carve through the rock.

Initially, his fingers were moving extremely slowly, taking a long time just to move a single inch. However, he then gradually sped up, and in the end, his fingers were virtually flying as he completed a set of patterns in a smooth and flowing manner.

The pattern was completely identical to the ones on the top four sheets of paper, except it was several times larger, extending all the way down from the stone platform, with the majority of it stretching onto the ground below.

After carving out this first set of patterns, Han Li took a moment to rest, then exhaled as he made his way over to the right side and repeated the same process.

Some time later, he rose to his feet as he slowly opened his eyes to find that another set of patterns had been completed. The two sets of patterns were in different positions, but were somehow connected, as if they were a single entity.

Han Li gave a pleased nod upon seeing this, and he rubbed his hands together, upon which the Essence Fire Raven flew out of his body before transforming into a silver flame that began burning within the fire pit.

The entire cave was filled with waves of scorching heat, and Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to release a string of azure light.

The azure light then faded to reveal his 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, all of which were hovering in the air before him while giving off an azure glow.

With another sweep of his sleeve, all of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were sent flying into the fire pit.

The silver flame within the fire pit instantly rose up to engulf the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, following which Han Li sat down with his legs crossed and began to chant an incantation while making a strange hand seal.

As his incantation continued, the array around the fire pit began to buzz audibly, and four pillars of golden light rose diagonally upward to meet at the center of the fire pit, forming a golden light barrier that encompassed both the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords and the Essence Fire Raven.

Moments later, Han Li spread his fingers open, then raised both hands slightly, and the sound of stoppers being pulled out of vials rang out as all of the spirit liquid within the dozen or so vials flowed out before surging into the golden light barrier.

Through the golden light barrier, Han Li could clearly see the molten Dendrobium Gold Essence splitting up on its own before completely enveloping every single one of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

Immediately thereafter, all of the other types of spirit liquid also split themselves up into 72 parts before fusing into the molten Dendrobium Gold Essence on the surface of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

Han Li closed his eyes again upon seeing this, then released his spiritual sense into the golden light barrier.

The light barrier shuddered slightly, and it instantly transformed into a five-colored light barrier.

At the same time, the 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords also began to glow brightly with five-colored light, giving them a dazzling and spectacular appearance.

Two hours passed by before Han Li opened his eyes once again, and he opened his mouth to release a burst of nascent flames. The nascent flames passed through the five-colored light barrier without any impediment before fusing with the silver flames inside.

The two types of flames instantly combined before rising up as a pillar of fire that enveloped all of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and all of a sudden, around a dozen of the flying swords suddenly began to struggle with all their might, releasing their sword qi as they frantically darted away in all directions.

Han Li instantly increased his spiritual sense output upon seeing this, establishing close contact with all of the flying swords at once to immediately quell the unrest.

I didn't think there would still be some stubborn sword essence that hasn't been completely refined. They were certainly concealing themselves very well...

Despite this unforeseen turn of events, Han Li felt himself to be quite fortunate.

Thankfully, the sword essence had reared its head now. If he had lost control of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords during a battle instead, then the consequences would've been catastrophic.

The sword essence that was still yet to be refined surged out of the flying swords within the scorching flames, then quickly disintegrated.

However, instead of being lost, the spiritual power that it was converted into was reabsorbed by the flying swords.

Even so, Han Li still didn't let his guard down, continuing to control the combination of the silver flame and his nascent flame to refine the 72 flying swords. Over time, the rainbow coloration of the flying swords gradually began to fade.

49 days later, the flying swords in the fire pit beneath the golden light barrier had turned as white and translucent as ice, looking almost completely transparent.

Compared with before, the blades of all of the flying swords had elongated by about an inch and also become much wider.

Han Li was inspecting these rather unfamiliar Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords in an expressionless manner, and he swept a sleeve through the air once again.

The stopper of the final black vial on the stone platform flew out at his behest, and the white spirit liquid inside emerged before surging into the golden light barrier and splitting up into 72 parts, each of which dripped onto one of the flying swords, producing a sound much like that of spring rain falling onto the parched earth.

All of the flying sword shuddered in unison, following which all of the spirit patterns on their surfaces lit up, and countless arcs of golden lightning sprang forth, intertwining to form a miniature forest of lightning that was crackling incessantly.

If it weren't for the presence of the golden light barrier, the arcs of golden lightning would've most likely spilled out and destroyed the entire cave.

Chapter 261: Change In the Floating Mountains

Han Li's eyes were illuminated a golden color by the light barrier, and he activated his Spirit Refinement Technique before releasing his enormous spiritual sense. His spiritual sense passed through the light barrier, then split up into 72 parts before piercing straight into the golden lightning to control the 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

Under his control, the 72 flying swords shuddered in unison, following which all of the light glowing from them faded, and the arcs of golden lightning also slowly fused back into the swords before vanishing entirely.

Han Li then made a hand seal, and the array around the fire pit flashed a few times before all of the pillars of golden light faded, leaving only the flying swords hovering within the flames.

After that, he opened his mouth and inhaled forcefully, upon which all of the nascent flames interspersed within the silver flames instantly swept back into his belly.

With the withdrawal of the nascent flames, the temperature of the fire was slightly lowered, while specks of azure light began to appear on the translucent jade-like Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, slowly restoring them back to their original azure color.

There was also faint golden light gleaming from the edges of the swords, forming a series of lightning-cloud-like golden patterns that were quite dazzling to behold.

Han Li swept his hands through the air, leaving trails of shimmering golden afterimages behind, and all of the flying swords instantly flew out of the silver fire as if they were living creatures before descending in front of him.

Han Li slashed a fingernail across the palm of his hand to draw a drop of golden blood essence, which formed an egg-sized ball of blood that was scattered into 72 drops at his behest, with each drop spilling onto one of the flying swords, and they instantly vanished into the flying swords upon contact.

At the same time, Han Li could feel his connection with his flying swords becoming stronger, and all of the unfamiliarity that had arisen due to the change in the aura of his flying swords had vanished.

With another wave of his hand, the 72 flying swords flashed with azure light once again, then flew back into the fire to continue the refinement process.

A short while later, Han Li approached the fire with his eyes closed and began to engrave the tiny array recorded on the beasthide book onto the flying swords with his spiritual sense.

……

Close to a year later, the azure array outside the floating mountain receded, and Han Li emerged from his cave abode with a calm and collected expression, but on the inside, he was quite elated.

The refinement of all 72 of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords had been completed, and their appearance and the auras that they were giving off had undergone a complete change, while all of the sword essence that was still yet to be fully refined in the past had been completely absorbed, thereby significantly elevating the power of the swords.

What he was most pleased about was that due to the injection of blood essence into the flying swords following the refinement process, his connection with them had become stronger, and as a result, he was able to sense the astonishing spiritual nature that had developed within them.

It felt as if these swords were no longer just treasures, and they were now extensions of his own body instead.

Situated in this secret area, he didn't have time to test out their power, but he was certain that they would've been far more formidable than before.

On the plaza outside the cave abode, Hu Zhen and the other disciples had already been waiting for quite some time. Han Li enquired them about the situation in the secret area, then rewarded them with some spirit stones.

After that, he asked them about what had been happening in the Blaze Dragon Dao, but due to the fact that most of them had been in this secret area this entire time, they weren't able to provide many answers.

There was only a single disciple who had only recently arrived in the secret area, but he had no noteworthy news to share, and that clearly reflected that nothing of importance had happened in the sect, something that Han Li was quite relieved to hear.

Time slowly passed by, and several years later, Han Li finally learned by chance through the Transient Guild that Gu Jie had been forced out of the Blaze Dragon Dao by a high-ranking member of the Transient Guild, and he felt as if a load had been lifted from his shoulders.

Not long after that, all of the arrays around the floating mountain that he was situated on were activated once again.

……

200 years flew by in the blink of an eye.

Within the secret area of floating mountains, there were seven or eight young men in Blaze Dragon Dao disciple robes waiting anxiously outside a floating mountain that was enveloped in a layer of azure light.

A young man with a round face turned to the dark-skinned young man by the name of Hu Zhen as he asked, "What do we do, Senior Martial Brother Hu? The mist in the canyon is behaving very strangely. In the past, it would only take a month at most for it to recede, but it's already been over three months, and it's still showing no signs of receding. In fact, it's only risen up higher the past few days."

"Prior to going into seclusion, Elder Li told us that this is an extremely important seclusion for him, so we're not to disturb him unless an urgent situation arises. If we contact him over something like this and disrupt his cultivation, only for it to be a false alarm, then who's going to bear the consequences?" Hu Zhen asked.

"But Elder Li has already been in seclusion for close to a century, and no one knows when he's going to come out. What if what's happening in the canyon right now affects the spirit medicine harvest? If that happens, we'll be in deep trouble regardless," the round-faced young man countered with an urgent expression.

Everyone else nodded in agreement with the round-faced young man's statement.

Hu Zhen's brows were tightly furrowed, and after extensive consideration, he decided, "Alerting Elder Li right away is definitely not the right course of action to take. We have to figure out exactly what's happening in the canyon before we make a decision.

“For now, keep an eye on the mist and look out for large-scale white ghost invasions. I'll think of a way to find out what's happening down there, and if it's a problem that we can't resolve on our own, then we'll have to disturb Elder Li."

The round-faced young man nodded in response.

However, his expression then suddenly changed slightly as he turned toward the floating mountain enveloped within the azure light.

Ferocious gusts of wind had suddenly begun to sweep through the sky, and clouds were converging from all directions, quickly forming a massive gray cloud that encompassed a vast area.

Streaks of five-colored light that resembled shooting stars were flashing incessantly through the cloud, and the light was gradually becoming brighter and more stable.

"Is Elder Li about to make a breakthrough?" the round-faced young man exclaimed.

"It appears so," Hu Zhen replied.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the gray cloud in the sky began to revolve in a frenzy, and a beam of five-colored light that was formed by the world's origin qi cascaded down from the heavens, encompassing the entire mountain.

Everyone felt the air tighten around them, as if some type of invisible restriction had suddenly appeared, striking them with a sense of discomfort.

Right at this moment, a loud and insistent buzzing sound began to ring out from the canyon down below.

Hu Zhen's expression instantly changed slightly upon hearing this sound, and he hurriedly yelled, "Something's happening down there! We have to go!"

Immediately thereafter, he swooped toward the canyon down below, and everyone else also followed suit without any hesitation.

The group of disciples passed by hundreds of floating mountains during their descent, and they were joined by more and more Blaze Dragon Dao disciples, gradually forming an army of over 1,000 cultivators.

Aside from the handful of leaders of the disciples, who were at the pinnacle of the Spatial Tempering Stage, the majority of the rest of the disciples were at the early-Spatial Tempering Stage, and most of them had already been stationed in this secret area for several centuries.

Everyone knew that this buzzing sound indicated that the mist had already risen up to the previous highest point recorded in history, which meant that around a dozen additional mountains were going to be swallowed up by the mist, and the precious spirit medicines growing on them would be devoured by the white ghosts.

After flying downward for several hundred kilometers, the disciples finally caught sight of the mist, which was as dense as a dark cloud.

Mountains that had never been swallowed up by the mist before currently being quickly inundated, and countless shadowy figures could be seen rushing through the mist while letting loose feral roars.

"How is this happening?" the round-faced young man exclaimed with an incredulous expression.

"Junior Martial Brother, you have the secret talisman that Elder Li gave to us. Go and wait outside his mountain, and if we're unable to keep the white ghosts at bay, use the talisman to contact Elder Li right away!" Hu Zhen said in an urgent voice, and the round-faced young man immediately nodded in response.

"Elder Li is currently in the middle of a breakthrough, so you absolutely must not use the talisman unless we're being overwhelmed by the enemy," Hu Zhen cautioned.

"Yes, Senior Martial Brother Hu," the round-faced young man replied with a solemn nod, then immediately turned around and began flying directly upward.

There was a concerned look on Hu Zhen's face as he turned to everyone else and yelled, "Set up the Azure Light Flight Restriction Array!"

All of the disciples immediately gave a collective affirmative response, while the peak-Spatial Tempering Stage disciples around Hu Zhen split up in all directions, with each of them leading several hundred disciples to different parts of the secret area.

All of the disciples then each summoned a large azure flag in an orderly fashion before tossing it forward and making a string of hand seals while chanting an incantation. The entire process appeared to have been extremely well-rehearsed.

As the incantation rang out, all of the runes on the azure flags lit up in unison, releasing bursts of azure light that interconnected with one another to form an enormous azure light barrier above the rising mist.

Inside the canyon, the dense mist was churning in a frenzy like a pot of boiling water, and it began to rise up at a rate that was several times faster than before, reaching the azure light barrier in mere moments.

The sound of howling wind rang out from deep within the canyon, and the churning mist struck the azure light barrier, causing it to ripple and sway violently.

All of the Blaze Dragon Dao disciples above the light barrier were gripping tightly onto the shafts of their flags with both hands while spiritual light radiated from their bodies as they struggled to stabilize the array with all their might. Some of the disciples among them with lesser cultivation bases were already swaying incessantly like small rafts in a turbulent sea.

Right at this moment, countless humanoid figures suddenly began to shoot up rapidly from the dense mist down below, crashing violently into the azure light barrier amid a string of dull thuds.

The Blaze Dragon Dao disciples looked down to find countless hideous white ghosts springing up out of the mist before crashing into the light barrier as if they had gone insane.

This was extremely strange and inexplicable behavior from the white ghost, and it looked as if they had no regard for their own lives.

In fact, some of them were crashing into the light barrier with such violent force that their heads were split open, sending intracranial fluids splashing down into the mist below.

Hu Zhen's expression became even more concerned upon seeing this.

Chapter 262: Coming Out of Seclusion

At this point, the massive gray cloud in the sky had already turned into a five-colored cloud, and a huge hole appeared at its center, through which a ray of dazzling golden light was shining down directly upon the floating mountain below.

The entire mountain was basked in a bright golden glow, giving it the appearance of an incandescent mountain of gold.

Inside the secret chamber of his cave abode, Han Li's eyes were tightly shut, and he was seated with his legs crossed with golden light radiating from his body, giving him the appearance of a golden deity.

Meanwhile, 11 specks of golden light were flashing incessantly on his chest and abdomen, and not far away from, a fist-sized golden vortex was slowly taking shape.

Right at this moment, a loud rumbling sound akin to a thunderclap rang out in the sky, and the entire five-colored cloud began to churn in a frenzy.

The placid-looking pillar of golden light also shuddered before beginning to rapidly revolve, quickly transforming into a giant golden tornado that stood like a pillar between heaven and earth.

A resounding boom rang out as the azure light barrier around the mountain was shattered by the giant pillar of golden light, which then shone straight down into the cave abode on the mountain.

The entire floating mountain shuddered as it descended slightly, and a burst of violent shockwaves swept through the air in all directions.

The round-faced young man had only just begun to approach the mountain from below when he was struck by the shockwaves, and the protective spiritual light around his body was instantly dispelled while he was sent flying back through the air like a rucksack.

Only after crashing into a nearby mountain did he come to a rest, and an unnatural flush appeared on his face as he threw up a mouthful of blood.

He wiped the blood from the corner of his lips as he carefully stood in mid-air, glancing down at the canyon below before turning his gaze back to the mountain up above while holding tightly onto the silver talisman in his hand.

Upon entering the mountain, the pillar of golden light disintegrated into countless specks of golden light that descended like rain.

Inside the secret chamber of the cave abode, Han Li's eyes abruptly sprang open, and the golden vortex on his body began to rapidly revolve while releasing a burst of tremendous suction force.

The sound of howling wind rang out as the countless specks of golden light swept up the surrounding world's origin qi before surging toward the vortex on Han Li's body like a turbulent river, and his twelfth immortal acupoint was beginning to take shape!

Looking up the river of golden light descending down onto the mountain, the round-faced young man was astonished beyond words. He had witnessed breakthroughs from other immortals in the past, but never had he witnessed one quite so spectacular.

Right as he was looking up in shock and awe, a deafening boom suddenly rang out, followed by a chorus of alarmed and agonized screams coming from the canyon down below.

It seemed that the situation was taking a turn for the worse, but as the round-faced young man looked down, he found his vision being obstructed by all of the mountains in the way, so he couldn't see anything, and he was unsure of whether the other disciples were still able to hold on.

A conflicted look appeared on his face, and his grip tightened even further around the talisman. The palm of his hand was sweating profusely, and in the end, he gritted his teeth and injected a wisp of magic power into it.

A streak of azure light instantly flew out of the talisman before hurtling toward Han Li's cave abode with a sharp screeching sound.

After that, the round-faced young man turned and rushed straight toward the canyon down below.

At this point, the situation had already erupted into complete pandemonium.

The azure light barrier conjured up by the Blaze Dragon Dao had already been broken, and there only some parts of it were still intact, but it didn't appear as if they were going to be able to last much longer.

Mist was already surging up through the broken parts of the light barrier, en route to swallowing up even more floating mountains.

The round-faced young man arrived just in time to see Hu Zhen leading the Blaze Dragon Dao disciples upward in a retreat with a grim look on his face.

As soon as he caught sight of the round-faced young man, he immediately approached him before asking, "Luo Tang, have you informed Elder Li of the situation?"

"I have, but he's still currently in the middle of his breakthrough, and I don't know when he'll come out of seclusion," Luo Tang replied.

"This is something that's never happened before, and Elder Li is the only True Immortal Stage elder currently in this secret area. If he doesn't come out of seclusion soon..." Hu Zhen's voice trailed off here, but what he was implying was very obvious.

All of a sudden, a thunderous roar rang out from down below, and countless white ghosts came surging out of the canyon, springing toward the floating mountains up above regardless of whether they were encompassed within the mist or not.

All of the Blaze Dragon Dao disciples unleashed their treasures to intercept the white ghosts, and a fierce battle instantly ensued with countless white ghosts being slain on the spot.

Even the white ghosts that weren't successfully intercepted weren't able to survive for long out of the mist. All of them began clutching at their own throats as if they could breathe while their skin turned black, and they began plummeting down toward the canyon in agony.

Even so, these white ghosts were still springing up without any regard for their own lives, and it was as if they had truly gone insane.

"What is going on?" Luo Tang murmured to himself with a stunned expression.

"I feel like... they're running for their lives from something..." Hu Zhen said as a hint of fear flashed through his eyes.

Right at this moment, another feral roar rang out, and this time, it sounded as if it were coming from somewhere very close.

A giant black shadow suddenly sprang out of the dense mist, opening its cavernous mouth to swallow up around a dozen white ghosts at once before rapidly falling back.

Immediately thereafter, two more black shadows darted out of another part of the mist to devour several dozen more white ghosts.

Whatever the creature was, it was concealed within the mist and moving so quickly that Luo Tang was unable to catch a clear glimpse of it at all.

"What is that thing?" he exclaimed in a horrified voice, to which Hu Zhen shook his head silently in response.

"What do we do? If we keep retreating, the entire annual harvest of spirit medicines will be gone, and the sect will be sure to punish us severely," Luo Tang said with a grim expression.

Hu Zhen's brows were tightly furrowed as he took a glance upward, and he couldn't help but feel a little discontent toward Han Li.

"We can't keep retreating. Ignore those white ghosts and focus on dealing with that creature in the mist. All disciples, heed my call! Assemble right away and prepare to face the enemy!" Hu Zhen yelled.

At this point, many of the Blaze Dragon Dao disciples were already beginning to panic, but they still heeded Hu Zhen's call and began to converge toward him.

"Assemble the All-encompassing Sword Array!" Hu Zhen yelled.

Everyone immediately sprang into action without any hesitation, rising up into the air atop their flying swords, while those who didn't have any flying swords raised their hands to inject their magic power into the sword array.

The All-encompassing Sword Array was a type of basic sword array that didn't require any complex setup. Instead, it was capable of unleashing enormous power as long as there was a sufficient number of flying swords assembled.

Thousands of flying swords rose up into the air between the floating mountains, and an enormous sword array quickly took shape.

Hu Zhen's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this, clearly not expecting the sword array to be so formidable, and he was beginning to believe that perhaps they really would be able to slay the beast within the mist.

"Attack!" Hu Zhen yelled, and everyone instantly heeded his call as the thousands of flying swords gathered together before plunging down toward the dense mist below like a waterfall of swords.

Countless white ghosts that were rushing out of the mist were instantly slain by the swords, and all of a sudden, an earth-shattering roar rang out, following which the mist within the canyon began to rise up 10 times quicker than before, instantly swallowing up all of the oncoming flying swords.

A string of loud clangs rang out incessantly from within the mist as hundreds of flying swords were struck by a burst of tremendous force, sending them spiraling out of control and flying back out of the mist.

Some were even shattered outright, causing their wielders to throw up mouthfuls of blood from the resulting backlash.

Nine mountainous black serpentine heads emerged from the mist. Each head had a pair of golden eyes that were watching all of the disciples with cold disdain.

The heads were swaying slightly from side to side while flicking out their forked tongues repeatedly to produce a hissing sound.

All it took was a single glance from the serpentine beast for Hu Zhen to feel as if his entire body had been plunged into a glacial pit, and he couldn't muster up any courage to resist such a formidable creature.

The giant serpent was clearly below them, but he felt as if it were somehow looking down on them, and his heart was entirely filled with despair.

He wasn't the only one who felt this way. All of the other disciples were also in such a state of despair and horror that they had even forgotten to run away.

Moments later, the nine giant serpentine heads shrank back in unison, preparing to spring up at the Blaze Dragon Dao disciples above.

"Get back, foul beast!"

Right at this moment, an extremely authoritative voice suddenly rang out up above.

Before everyone even had a chance to look up, they saw a streak of azure light flash before their eyes, following which a humanoid figure appeared among them.

It was a tall and imposing azure-robed figure with a layer of azure light around his body, giving him the appearance of a true deity.

"Elder Li!" Hu Zhen exclaimed, and his cries were quickly echoed by everyone else.

They were like drowning swimmers who had suddenly been saved right on the verge of death, and the elation and relief that washed over their bodies was so immense that they felt as if they could cry.

Meanwhile, the nine serpentine heads had already opened their cavernous mouths while springing up from down below.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to release a gentle breeze that carried all of the surrounding disciples to a safe distance away.

After that, he thrust a palm downward, releasing a burst of azure light, within which nine azure flying swords were circling around incessantly. The nine azure swords were releasing countless streaks of azure sword light that formed an azure light barrier, which encompassed virtually the entire canyon.

These azure flying swords were none other than the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and in their current form, they were able to act independently as 72 swords, or combined to form nine swords, or just a single sword.

Chapter 263: Testing Out the Mantra Treasured Axis

A resounding boom rang out as the nine serpentine heads struck the azure light barrier in unison before being repelled, while the light barrier remained completely unmoved.

Han Li made a hand seal, and all of the streak of azure swordlight instantly turned their tips downward in a uniform manner, and a menacing aura of killing intent began to spread through the air.

Looking at the vast sword array that Han Li had conjured up, Hu Zhen and other disciples felt as if their All-encompassing Sword Array had been nothing more than a ragtag bunch of bandits compared with a formidable regular army.

All of the streaks of swordlight plummeted out of the heavens at Han Li's behest with glowing azure tails behind them, making it appear as if a spectacular storm of shooting stars were descending from above.

The nine serpentine heads had already retreated back into the dense mist, sensing the danger that was afoot.

However, the streaks of swordlight continued to pursue them, flying into the mist as well.

A string of earth-shattering booms rang out as several floating mountains were destroyed by the storm of swordlight, and there were naturally countless white ghosts that fell to the formidable barrage as well.

Moments later, a string of seven or eight agonized roars rang out from deep within the mist, and a cold smile appeared on Han Li's face as he descended toward the mist himself.

He had only just descended into the mist when his brows furrowed ever so slightly. As it turned out, this mist was capable of keeping out spiritual sense.

Up above, all of the disciples were feeling extremely reassured at the sight of Han Li descending gracefully into the mist, and Luo Tang couldn't help but praise, "Elder Li truly is a formidable sword immortal..."

For some reason, Hu Zhen was suddenly reminded of a rumor that had been spreading in the sect for many years.

Apparently, there had always been a mighty sword immortal who referred to themself as the "the number one sword cultivator of Heavenly South" hiding in the Blaze Dragon Dao.

However, this thought only flashed through his mind for a moment. After all, it was a completely unsubstantiated rumor, and most of the people in the sect regarded it as a tall tale as none of the immortals in the sect even had any idea of where this Heavenly South was.

Inside the dense mist, Han Li's eyes were flashing with blue light as he sped downward, quickly descending several hundred kilometers. There were countless massive chunks of rocks hovering in the air around him, all of which were mountains that had been destroyed by the storm of swordlight he had just unleashed.

The canyon was far deeper than he anticipated, and even after descending for another several hundred kilometers, he still wasn't able to see the bottom.

The surrounding area was extremely dim, and the mist was incredibly dense, severely limiting his spiritual sense so that he was only able to detect things in a radius of around 10,000 feet.

If it weren't for his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, he wouldn't have been able to see anything.

Looking at all of the massive blurry shadows around him, he realized that there were massive mountains floating in the mist as well. In fact, there seemed to have been even more mountains in the misty canyon than above it.

Even though the nearby mountains were completely enshrouded in mist, he could still see countless shadows scurrying over them, but he wasn't sure if those shadowy figures were the remaining white ghosts.

He continued to plunge downward, getting closer and closer to his flying swords, and finally, after passing by yet another huge mountain, he spotted a glimmer of azure light deep within the mist.

The nine azure flying swords were enshrouded within a massive azure sword projection, which had been plunged into a massive black mountain.

Before Han Li had a chance to get close, a low roar suddenly rang out, and Han Li took a closer look to find that rippling black light was being reflected from all of the azure flying swords.

Thanks to the azure light radiating from the swords, he was able to see that an enormous serpentine body had wound itself around the entire mountain, and the nine giant serpentine heads were all pressed against the ground in a submissive fashion with a flying sword protruding out of each of them.

Only then did Han Li discover that what he had been hunting was a nine-headed serpent, rather than nine individual serpents.

At this moment, all of the heads of the giant serpent had already been pierced by swords, and the light in all of its eyes had already faded with the exception of one pair of eyes, which were still giving off a faint golden glow, but it didn't appear as if it was going to last much longer, either.

Han Li made a beckoning motion with one hand, and the nine flying sword plunged into the serpentine heads instantly flew back, then combined into a single azure longsword in mid-air before returning to his side.

He grabbed onto the hilt of the sword as he descended in front of the serpentine head that still held some signs of life, and he peered into its eyes.

All of a sudden, Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he used the serpentine head as a launchpad to send himself flying back in retreat.

In the next instant, the serpentine head exploded violently, and a black shadow sprang out from within, closing in on Han Li at an incredible speed.

Han Li focused his gaze on the approaching assailant to find that it was a young man clad in a suit of black scale armor.

The young man had a pale face and a pair of extremely thin and long eyes that almost extended into the hair on his temples. He had a pair of pronounced cheekbones and only four sharp fangs in his mouth, nestled between which was a bright red forked tongue. Furthermore, there were four fist-sized fleshy lumps on each of his shoulders, giving it the appearance of a hideous demon beast that hadn't fully manifested a human form yet.

The creature was hurtling through the mist at an incredible speed, holding a white bone spike that it was driving directly toward Han Li's chest.

Han Li lashed out with his longsword at the white bone spike, and right as the two weapons were about to clash, the serpentine man suddenly sprang to the side, following which its neck elongated to over 10 times its original length, and it opened its mouth with the intention of sinking its fangs into Han Li's neck.

A crisp clang rang out as the white bone spike was shattered by Han Li's sword, but at the same time, the serpentine demon's fangs had also reached Han Li's throat.

Right as the creature was about to sink its fangs into Han Li's neck, Han Li's Mantra Treasured Axis suddenly appeared behind him amid a flash of golden light.

There were 24 semi-transparent Time Dao Runes glowing on the axis, and it was releasing a burst of extremely pronounced law fluctuations that instanty encompassed the entire surrounding area in a radius of 100 feet.

All of a sudden, everything in the surrounding area seemed to have fallen completely still, and even the dense mist seemed to have congealed.

A horrified look appeared in the serpentine demon's eyes. It didn't feel as if it were being bound in any way, but somehow, its movements had become extremely slow, and its fangs were inching toward Han Li's neck at an agonizingly slow rate. It could only watch helplessly as Han Li casually moved back to avoid the attack.

"Not bad," Han Li remarked to himself with a pleased smile, then closed a hand around the serpentine demon's neck while raising his other hand to deal the killing blow.

He had intentionally allowed the serpentine demon to get close to him as he wanted to test out the power of his Mantra Treasured Axis. Otherwise, if he had gone all-out from the beginning, the serpentine demon would've already been long dead.

A sound akin to a watermelon being smashed open rang out, and it was also significantly elongated.

Han Li pulled a black nascent soul that was still yet to be fully formed out of the serpentine demon's broken head, then crushed it in between his hands.

After that, the Mantra Treasured Axis behind him slowly fused back into his body amid a flash of golden light.

Only then did everything in the surrounding area return to normal. The dense mist began to flow at the same speed as before, and the serpentine demon's body also began to fall, but it was prevented from doing so as Han Li's hand was still locked around its neck.

"Looks like the 24 Time Dao Runes haven't affected the axis's effective range, but its slowing effect has become far more potent. I'd say it's currently able to slow things down to less than a tenth of their original speed," Han Li murmured to himself.

It had taken him a great deal of effort to open the twelfth acupoint, and it had taken as much time to open this single acupoint as it had taken him to open the 11 previous ones combined, and that that was only after he had taken a copious amount of precious pills to enhance his cultivation. Otherwise, it would've definitely taken at least 100 times the amount of time to achieve the same outcome.

Now that he had reached the mid-True Immortal Stage and mastered the first level of the Mantra Axis Scripture, he could finally begin trying to master the laws of time.

While these thoughts were running through his mind, Han Li made a beckoning motion to draw the serpentine demon's body to his side, then pulled a slightly rank and odorous dark golden bead out of its chest before stowing it away.

After that, he casually tossed the serpentine demon's body into the canyon, and it didn't take long before the sound of a fight began to ring out.

It seemed that there were even more living creatures lurking deeper in the canyon, and they were fighting over the serpentine demon's body.

Han Li peered into the depths of the canyon for a short while before withdrawing his gaze and making his way to the mountain that the nine-headed serpent was still coiled around. The carcass of the nine-headed serpent had already become dry and shriveled, transforming into a massive nine-headed slough.

By Han Li's estimates, the serpentine demon was already close to the early-True Immortal Stage, but for some reason, it had only recently begun to shed its skin and adopt a human form. In order to accomplish this, it had to devour a massive number of white ghosts for sustenance, and it had even come out of the canyon to hunt for Blaze Dragon Dao disciples.

After being wounded by Han Li's Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, it had no choice but to forcibly adopt a human form, following which it was slain.

With a sweep of Han Li's sleeve, the slough was drawn into his storage bracelet. The slough was extremely sturdy and had some medicinal properties, so it was going to be very useful for pill refinement or to be used as a material for a suit of armor.

With the slough removed, the floating mountain down below was revealed, and patches of blue light appeared on its surface.

Han Li flew in for a closer look, and he discovered that there were several dozen crystalline blue plants growing on the mountain. They were very similar in appearance to orchids, except their leaves and petals were glittering and translucent.

However, they weren't giving off any pronounced spiritual power fluctuations, and it seemed that they were only ordinary plants.

Right at this moment, the leaves of these glowing blue plants began to vibrate in unison, producing an extremely faint buzzing sound that was quickly growing louder and louder.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he suddenly recalled that each time the mist rose up from the canyon, it would always be accompanied by this strange sound.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he collected all of the blue spirit plants from the mountain, and after checking through the canyon briefly to ensure that there were no other spirit plants of the same type around, he turned and began flying back up through the mist.

However, right as he was about to fly out of the mist, he suddenly stopped in his tracks, then began flying toward the floating mountains that had been destroyed.

These mountains were originally outside of the mist with many spirit medicines growing on them, and now that they had been swallowed up by the mist, the spirit medicines on them would've gone to waste if he didn't collect them.

Chapter 264: Resolve

An hour later, Han Li returned to the mountain where his cave abode was situated.

At this moment, he was standing with his hands clasped behind his back on the stone steps in front of his cave abode.

The plaza in front of him was packed with Blaze Dragon Dao disciples, and upon his arrival, all of them turned to him in unison with different looks on their faces, including elation, unease, and admiration.

Even though new True Immortal Stage elders would be sent to oversee the secret area periodically, it was extremely rare that anything ever happened here, so the True Immortal Stage elders remained in seclusion the vast majority of their time here.

Hence, this was an extremely rare opportunity for the disciples to witness a True Immortal in action with their own eyes, and it instilled them with a great deal of motivation when it came to their own cultivation.

"All of you have done extremely well in the face of this unexpected disaster, severely mitigating losses despite the trying circumstances. I'll be sure to report this to the sect and request a reward for all of you," Han Li declared.

"Thank you, Elder Li!"

Everyone had thought that he would be unhappy about having his seclusion disturbed, so they were ecstatic to hear what he had to say.

"The mist in the canyon has already receded, and there's still some cleanup work that needs to be done. Tally all of the damage and report it to me so I can report to the sect. You can all go now," Han Li instructed.

"Yes, Elder Li!" everyone answered in unison before departing.

Han Li instructed Hu Zhen and the others to stay behind, and after rewarding them with some pills, he returned to his cave abode.

Inside his secret chamber, Han Li summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis amid a flash of golden light and the 24 Time Dao Runes on the axis were giving off bursts of law fluctuations.

For the average cultivator, even if they were to cultivate the Mantra Axis Scripture to the third level, there was still no guarantee that they would be able to manifest even 18 Time Dao Runes, yet Han Li had managed to manifest 24 Time Dao Runes at just the mid-True Immortal Stage, and he was extremely pleased with the power that it had displayed in the canyon.

With this Mantra Treasured Axis and his set of new Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, he was confident that he would be able to take on even the likes of Gu Jie's avatar on his own.

Of course, if Gu Jie himself were to come after him, then he would still have to run for his life.

According to the Mantra Axis Scripture, now that he had mastered the first level of the cultivation art, he could begin attempting to master the laws of time.

The time law powers imbued within the Mantra Treasured Axis was quite abundant at this point, but it was very scattered, and Han Li couldn't even manifest any law threads, so he was still severely lacking compared with those who had truly mastered the power of laws.

Otherwise, as one of the three paramount laws, the laws of time should've been capable of more than just slowing down enemy attacks.

With that in mind, he began to think back to how Gu Jie's avatar had used its power of wood laws in different ways, and a sense of envy and anticipation welled up in his heart.

If he could master the laws of time someday, then its power would definitely trump Gu Jie's laws of wood.

With that in mind, Han Li took a deep breath, then flipped a hand over to produce an Immortal Origin Stone. The Mantra Treasured Axis behind him then began to slowly revolve at his behest, and the Time Dao Runes on its surface flashed, releasing golden ripples that spread through the surrounding area in a radius of 100 feet.

After that, he closed his eyes to carefully sense the changes in the law powers around him.

The Mantra Axis Scripture hadn't laid out any specific method to observe the laws of time, so he would have to figure it out for himself.

Three to four months passed by in the blink of an eye, and Han Li remained seated with his legs crossed the entire time, as still as a statue.

All of a sudden, a flash of golden light appeared around him, and his eyes sprang open, while his brows furrowed slightly.

Even after several months, he was no closer at all to mastering the laws of time, and he felt as if he made no progress at all.

However, this wasn't a very surprising outcome.

If law powers were this easy to master, then True Immortals who had mastered the power of laws wouldn't have been so rare. On top of that, he was trying to master one of the three paramount laws, so the difficulty was only going to be heightened.

In order to master the power of laws, he had made extensive preparations.

All of a sudden, the eye of that one-eyed giant appeared on his hand amid a flash of gray light.

This was one of the things that he had prepared.

He cupped the eye in both hands, then drew upon the time law powers around him before slowly injecting it into the eye.

The eye began to emit a faint white glow, as well as a burst of peculiar time law fluctuations.

Han Li immediately closed his eyes to sense the laws of time within the eye, comparing it to the his own time law powers in the hope of making some type of breakthrough.

Several more months passed by in a flash, and Han Li slowly opened his eyes with a dark expression, once again, having made no progress at all.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he stowed the eye away before summoning his Heaven Controlling Vial, and there was a drop of green liquid rolling around inside.

Han Li was silent for a moment as he observed the vial, then grabbed onto the vial before injecting his immortal spiritual power into it.

All of the world's origin qi near his cave abode was instantly stirred up into a frenzy, forming an enormous vortex of spiritual power.

All of the Blaze Dragon Dao disciples were momentarily startled by this before paying no further heed to the phenomenon.

During the past two hundred years, similar phenomena had arisen countless times, so they were already accustomed to this.

Several days later.

Inside his cave abode, Han Li's face was slightly pale, and he was holding a crystal in his hand.

Having progressed to the mid-True Immortal Stage, his immortal spiritual power reserves had increased significantly, so manifesting these crystals no longer completely sucked him dry like it used to.

After consuming a recovery pill, his complexion quickly began to recover.

He then grabbed onto the crystal before injecting his spiritual sense into it, and the translucent golden thread within the crystal instantly lit up, as did the Mantra Treasured Axis behind him.

It seemed that the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis were resonating with the crystal, and Han Li was ecstatic to see this, hurriedly closing his eyes once again.

A month passed by in the blink of an eye, and the translucent golden thread in the crystal disappeared, while the crystal itself also shattered.

Han Li opened his eyes, and a hint of excitement appeared on his face.

He still hadn't mastered the laws of time, but unlike his previous few attempts, he had made some progress, finally getting ever so slightly closer to his target.

It was as if a glimmer of hope had appeared within a boundless void of darkness.

He flipped a hand over to produce his Heaven Controlling Vial, and a smile appeared on his face as he discovered that another drop of green liquid had already emerged within it.

The Heavenly Controlling Vial was a major contributing factor behind how he had been able to cultivate the Mantra Axis Scripture so smoothly, and it seemed that he would have to keep relying on the vial if he wanted to master the laws of time.

However...

A contemplative look appeared in his eyes.

Regardless of how he tried to observe the laws of time within the crystal, he was only able to sense the law powers encapsulated within, but unable to glean any deeper insights.

If he wanted those deeper insights, he had to take things a step further.

With that in mind, a determined look of resolve appeared on his face.

He flipped a hand over to produce a jade container the size of a washbasin, then filled it with spirit liquid before finally dripping the drop of green liquid in the Heaven Controlling Vial into the container.

The colorless spirit liquid inside instantly turned a light green color as a result.

After that, Han Li flipped a hand over to produce another bowl before making a beckoning motion, and a ball of green spirit liquid rose up from the container before dropping into the bowl, almost completely filling it.

His plan was to drink this green liquid so that he could intimately feel the time law powers imbued within.

Han Li set the jade bowl aside, then swept a sleeve through the air to release his 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords, and even though he hadn't injected any immortal spiritual power into them, they were already releasing formidable sword qi that was causing the nearby space to buzz incessantly.

He released a series of incantation seals, and the 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords fused as one into a single small azure sword.

Han Li then flipped a hand over to produce a silver talisman, which he adhered to the sword.

The sword qi emanating from the small azure sword instantly vanished, making it appear as if it were just an ordinary sword.

He set the Heaven Controlling vial down beside the small azure sword, then released the Essence Fire Raven amid a flash of silver light.

The Essence Fire Raven instantly transformed into a tiny fiery figure that danced around Han Li while crying out joyfully.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he played with the fiery silver figure for a while, then raised it up on the palm of his hand.

"Do you recall this person?" A burst of azure light appeared over his other hand, and an image of Nangong Wan emerged within the azure light.

The fiery silver figure took a glance at the image of Nangong Wan, then nodded in response.

Back in the Spirit Realm, the Essence Fire Raven hadn't attained intelligence as it had now, but it had developed a sufficient level of sentience to recall Nangong Wan.

"I'm leaving these two things to you for now. If something happens to me, take these two things and go search for this person. Make sure to find her and give her these two things no matter how long it takes," Han Li instructed.

The Essence Fire Raven looked at Han Li for a while, and it couldn't understand why Han Li was doing this, but it still did as it was told, nodding in response.

Han Li patted the tiny silver figure on the head, then set it aside as a serious look appeared on his face.

He could still clearly recall the pair of wild rabbits that had had their bodies imploded back when he first found the Heaven Controlling Vial.

After that, in the Scattered Star Sea, he had used the spirit liquid produced by the vial to trap the Nascent Soul Stage Windbreaker Beast, Feng Xi, almost killing it in the process.

Of course, his current cultivation base was orders of magnitude above Feng Xi's, and he had attained a Profound Immortal body, but he could sense that the special energy contained within the spirit liquid produced by the vial had also become countless times more powerful than back then.

Even in his current state, directly ingesting this spirit liquid was an extremely risky move, and it was not impossible for him to die from this.

However, he was willing to accept this level of risk, and if he couldn't withstand the spirit liquid's power, he would do everything he could to force it out of his body. He had even prepared himself to expel his nascent soul out of his own body if required.

At this point, he had come to understand that if he wanted to master the laws of time, he had to take some risk for any chance at success.

Chapter 265: Testing the Limits

Han Li cast a calm gaze toward the light green spirit liquid in the jade bowl, then took a deep breath, and all of the tension in his body instantly seeped away.

He then took a glance at the fiery silver figure, which was looking up at him with a hint of concern on its face, and he finally made up his mind, lifting up the bowl of spirit liquid before downing half of its contents in one go.

Upon entering his mouth, the spirit liquid was quite cool and a little bitter. After being swallowed, it transformed into a burst of heat that entered his dantian, and that burst of heat quickly swelled in temperature as if it had been set alight, surging through his meridians like scorching fire.

In this instant, Han Li could feel all of the meridians in his entire body expanding as bursts of indescribable power surged through his body. Even with his incredibly powerful physical body, he was in excruciating pain, and he felt as if he were about to explode.

However, a cool and refreshing sensation then welled up in his mind, restoring a sense of clarity and tranquility.

Han Li hurriedly composed himself, then conjured up a protective layer of azure light over his own body. At the same time, bursts of invisible power surged out of all parts of his body, and a string of cracks and pops rang out as he abruptly became noticeably taller. Furthermore, his limbs and torsos had also become thicker than before.

Shortly thereafter, his brows began to furrow slightly.

Some of the smaller meridians in his body had already been torn open, only for a rapid healing process to commence thanks to a vast injection of vitality.

This process of tearing and healing was unfolding in countless tiny parts all over his body, taking place thousands of times with each passing moment.

Even with Han Li's unfathomably powerful physical body and outstanding mental fortitude, the indescribable agony was beginning to take its toll.

To compound his woes even further, his mind was more conscious than ever, so the agony was even further exacerbated.

However, at the same time, he was also beginning to clearly sense the mysterious power imbued within the bursts of heat that were flowing throughout his entire body.

This mysterious power was causing his physical body to undergo some type of indescribable change, and the innate resistance of his body was currently fiercely clashing against this mysterious power.

This process wore on for two hours without displaying any signs of abating, but Han Li was feeling rather relieved as he had already grown accustomed to this feeling.

The spirit liquid was causing severe damage to his body, but it seemed that he wasn't in any life-threatening danger. In fact, he felt like he could even drink more.

With that in mind, Han Li immediately picked up the jade bowl, then gulped down the remaining half a bowl of spirit liquid.

An even more enormous burst of scorching heat surged into his body before spreading through his meridians, and he couldn't help but give a muffled groan as he shuddered involuntarily, and the azure light around him also flickered slightly.

Only after close to two more hours had passed by did the pain on Han Li's face fade slightly, and the azure light around him also returned to a stable state.

Just as he anticipated, he was able to withstand this additional influx of spirit liquid thanks to his powerful physical body and willpower. The agony he was experiencing was several times more severe than before, but this was exactly what he was looking for.

Only by pushing his own body to the limits could he better observe the laws of time.

With that in mind, he paid no further heed to his own internal condition as he began to focus solely on that burst of mysterious power flowing throughout his body.

At this moment, he could clearly hear the beating of his own heart, and every single one of his heartbeast was resonating in some way with the burst of mysterious power flowing through his meridians.

This was a sensation that was both alien and familiar to him.

It was the fluctuation of the power of time, the pulsing of the origin of life...

He felt as if there were something within his grasp, but he couldn't grab ahold of it no matter how hard he tried.

He felt as if he were gradually getting closer to grasping the laws of time, but it was an intangible entity. One moment, he would feel as if he had it tightly locked in his grasp, but in the next instant, it would be gone without a trace.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to him, and he summoned an Immortal Origin Stone that he held in his hand. At the same time, his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him amid a flash of golden light, and the Time Dao Runes on the axis released bursts of powerful fluctuations that enveloped his entire body. After that, he activated his Spirit Refinement Technique and tried to focus and immerse himself into this process as much as possible.

Thanks to the effects of the Mantra Treasured Axis, the burst of mysterious power flowing through his meridians seemed to have slowed down slightly, but it still remained as intangible and elusive as ever.

Time slowly passed by, and the heat formed by the spirit liquid was constantly being expended. After a few more hours, the heat finally completely disappeared along with the excruciating pain that came with it.

Han Li opened his eyes, and there was a combination of excitement and befuddlement on his face as he withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis back into his body.

Even though he hadn't managed to grasp the laws of time, he had clearly sensed the fluctuations of the power of time.

All of a sudden, his entire body shuddered, and blood began to trick down from the corner of his lips.

Even though he had forcibly withstood the effects of ingesting the spirit liquid, his entire body was currently riddled with injuries, and his meridians and bones were littered with countless tiny wounds.

Even the average True Immortal would've already had their body completely explode had they been in Han Li's place.

Thankfully, the regenerative ability of Han Li's Profound Immortal body coupled with his True Extreme Membrane had allowed him to survive this process.

Judging from this outcome, it seemed that he could ingest a bit more of the spirit liquid.

He felt as if he had been on the cusp of gleaning the secrets of the power of time just now. Perhaps he would only have a chance of succeeding in this endeavor by constantly pushing his own limits.

After taking a deep breath, he consumed a restorative pill, then closed his eyes and began to meditate.

Several days later.

Han Li slowly opened his eyes as he exhaled, and at this point, he had already recovered from all of his injuries.

He turned his gaze to the jade container beside him, then swept a sleeve toward it without any hesitation, and another stream of spirit liquid rose up out of the container before flying straight into his mouth.

Han Li gave a muffled groan as his complexion transitioned back and forth between green and white.

This time, he had ingested even more spirit liquid than last time, but with the experience of that previous experiment under his belt, he was no longer feeling as uneasy as before.

He slowly closed his eyes, paying no heed to his body's internal condition as he focused his attention on observing the power of laws contained within the spirit liquid.

Cracks and pops rang out incessantly from within his body, and this time, even the skin on some parts of his arms and shoulders had split open, but no blood flowed out of the gashes.

Han Li continued to remain completely still, and over an hour passed by in the blink of an eye.

All of a sudden, his eyes sprang open, and he threw up a mouthful of blood. His face was looking rather pale, but his eye were glowing with excitement.

Once again, he felt as if he had gotten a little closer to grasping the laws of time, but he was still not quite there yet.

He quickly consumed another pill, and a layer of green light appeared over his body.

Several days later, he was fully recovered from his injuries, and this time, he ingested all of the remaining spirit liquid in the jade container all at once.

He then summoned a pair of Immortal Origin Stones, holding one in each hand, before also summoning his Mantra Treasured Axis and closing his eyes.

Upon reopening his eyes, the excitement on his face had been replaced by a hint of befuddlement.

Why is it that each time, I feel as if I've gotten a little closer to grasping the power of time, but I always fall just a little short? In any case, this is the route that seems to have the highest likelihood of leading to success, so perhaps I just need to stick at it a little longer.

With that in mind, he flipped his hand over to produce another pill, which he swallowed before closing his eyes.

Close to a month later, another drop of green liquid had been manifested in the Heaven Controlling Vial.

Han Li picked up the vial, and after a brief moment of contemplation, he decided to directly ingest the drop of spirit liquid inside without diluting it at all.

A few seconds later, a string of cracks and pops began to ring out within Han Li's body, and a series of tiny gashes rapidly appeared over his skin. This time, even his True Extreme Membrane was unable to prevent blood from flowing out of the gashes, and it only took a moment for his entire body to be completely covered in blood.

Han Li's entire body was trembling, and it seemed that even the slightest lapse in concentration would lead to his body completely exploding.

This time, it took close to four hours before his condition gradually returned to normal, and the agonized look on his face also faded. He continued to pay no heed to his own internal condition, and the Mantra Treasured Axis behind him was revolving rapidly at his behest, while the Time Dao Runes on the axis were also glowing brightly.

Half a day later, Han Li opened his eyes as he threw up a mouthful of blood, and his face had turned extremely pale.

Having ingested two drops of spirit liquid in succession, he had developed a better grasp on the power of time, but once again, it remained just out of reach.

Perhaps one more drop will do the trick.

However, before that, he had to recover from his injuries, and with that in mind, he took another pill before closing his eyes to meditate.

A layer of azure light appeared over his body, and his complexion gradually began to improve, while the gashes on his body quickly healed.

A month later, Han Li picked up the Heaven Controlling Vial to find another drop of spirit liquid rolling around inside.

He took a deep breath as a solemn look appeared on his face, and just like last time, he drank the undiluted drop of spirit liquid in one go.

More cracks and pops rang out from within his body, and he adopted the same setup as last time, summoning his Mantra Treasured Axis while holding a pair of Immortal Origin Stones to replenish his immortal spiritual power.

As time passed by, bursts of time law powers began to surge out of the axis, and it was also beginning to revolve faster and faster while the golden light radiating from it grew steadily brighter.

Han Li's eyes were tightly shut, and he was making a constant string of hand seals.

The golden light radiating from his body was surging incessantly, and if one were to look closely, they would discover that the golden light was formed by countless tiny golden runes that resembled scorching flames.

The 24 Time Dao Runes were trembling while the golden flames were growing brighter and brighter, looking as if they were about to come together, but right at this moment, the golden light radiating from the Mantra Treasured Axis suddenly began to flash, and it slowed down in its rotation.

At the same time, cracks were beginning to appear on its surface, and the Time Dao Runes also settled down again.

Chapter 266: 5,000 Reward

With one final flash of golden light, the Mantra Treasured Axis vanished into Han Li's body, and Han Li gave a muffled groan as he threw up a mouthful of black blood.

He opened his eyes, and the protective azure light around him was trembling violently, looking as if it could shatter any moment.

All of his joints and meridians were also shuddering, and he hurriedly made a string of hand seals to stabilize the layer of protective azure light.

After that, he took another restorative pill as a contemplative look appeared on his face.

Just now, he felt as if he had gotten closer to grasping the power of time than ever before, and it had been so tantalizingly close that he could almost reach out and grab it, but in the end, he had failed once again.

He was infinitely approaching his target, but there was always this barrier that stood in his way, and it seemed impossible to bypass.

According to the Mantra Axis Scripture, those who had mastered the first level of the cultivation art could begin attempting to master the laws of time. Of course, whether the endeavor would be successful or not was a different matter entirely.

However, with the spirit liquid produced by the Heaven Controlling Vial to assist him, he should've been able to succeed more easily than others.

A month later, the Heaven Controlling Vial produced another drop of spirit liquid, and this time, Han Li immediately devoured the drop of spirit liquid without any hesitation.

In the next instant, his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him amid a flash of golden light, releasing dazzling golden radiance alongside powerful time law fluctuations.

Yet again, he was holding an Immortal Origin Stone in each hand, and the golden light radiating from his body was becoming brighter and brighter as the laws of time began to converge around him.

Right at this moment, the golden light on the Mantra Treasured Axis suddenly began to flash, and a series of cracks appeared on its surface.

All of the time law powers that had gathered around Han Li instantly faded, as did the Mantra Treasured Axis.

Han Li opened his eyes with a frustrated look on his face.

Perhaps the first time could be attributed to a chance occurrence, but this had happened twice in a row now, and the only explanation that he could think of for this was that he simply wasn't ready to master the laws of time yet.

Thus, he would have to turn his attention to securing the second level of the Mantra Axis Scripture.

With that in mind, he flipped a hand over to produce another pill before promptly swallowing it.

Several months later.

A prolonged snowstorm had fallen upon the eastern region of the Bell Toll Mountain Range, covering that entire area in a thick layer of snow. With the fire miasma gone, the Crimson Dawn Peak was also covered in snow.

At this moment, Meng Yungui was wearing a silver robe, and he was crouched down in front of a plot of spirit farmland in which several dozen spirit plants were growing, examining the nurturing array around the plot of land.

This type of spirit plant was one that grew naturally on the Crimson Dawn Peak, and it could only survive in warm conditions. Hence, without the natural protection of the fire miasma, a nurturing array was required to shield it from the elements.

Meng Qianqian was wearing a long green dress, and she was standing beside Meng Yungui with a rather absentminded look in her eyes as she asked, "When do you think Elder is going to come back, Brother?"

Meng Yungui feigned an angry expression as he turned to her and grumbled, "Are you really my sister? You didn't miss me anywhere near this much back when I was out searching for spirit seeds for Elder Li!"

Meng Qianqian giggled in amusement, then replied, "Of course I'm your sister, I'm just really eager to tell Elder Li that I've already progressed to the Deity Transformation Stage. You have to work hard as well, Brother."

Meng Yungui could only shake his head with a resigned expression. Ever since Meng Qianqian successfully manifested a nascent soul, her cultivation base had been rapidly progressing, and not only had she caught up to her brother, she had recently outstripped him, reaching the Deity Transformation Stage not long ago.

Of course, Meng Yungui was genuinely happy for his sister, but he didn't want to give her excessive praise in case she became too full of herself.

After all, even though she had already been cultivating for hundreds of years, she still had a very simple and naive personality, and he was worried that excessive praise would negatively affect her mindset when it came to cultivation.

Not far away from the plot of spirit farmland was Han Li's massive mountain guardian beast. It raised its two heads as it yawned in a lazy manner, then rested its heads back onto the ground with a bored expression.

However, just a few moments later, it suddenly raised its heads up high again to look up at the sky.

A streak of azure light was hurtling rapidly toward the Crimson Dawn Peak from the distant horizon, and the array that encompassed the entire mountain quickly faded away, following which the azure figure descended onto the Crimson Dawn Peak.

Meng Yungui and Meng Qianqian exchanged a glance, and each of them could see their own elation mirrored in one another's eyes as they hurriedly rushed toward the Crimson Dawn Peak.

By the time they arrived in Han Li's cave abode, Sun Buzheng had already summoned everyone else as well, and all of the servants were gathered in the main hall, awaiting instructions from Han Li.

In the end, he only briefly enquired about the situation on the Crimson Dawn Peak, then bestowed upon everyone some pills and treasures before quickly departing once again, and much to Meng Qianqian's dismay, she didn't even get a chance to tell Han Li about her latest breakthrough.

After leaving the Crimson Dawn Peak, Han Li flew to the nearby teleportation hall and went straight to the Cloud Piercing Peak.

In a side hall of the High Profound Palace, there was a portly elderly seated behind the table, and he accepted the elder badge that Han Li was offering to him with a smile on his face as he said, "Thank you for your hard work, Elder Li. The two elders sent to the floating mountain secret area to replace you have already reported back, and the situation is identical to what was described in your earlier report.

“The sect has deemed that you've made a significant contribution in protecting the spirit plants on the floating mountains during the crisis, and as a result, you'll be rewarded 500 additional merit points on top of your standard reward."

After that, Han Li exchanged some small talk with the portly elder before his elder badge was returned to him, and he departed from the hall.

After leaving the side hall, a contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face. He had already accumulated a sizable number of merit points from the missions that he had completed, and so far, he had saved up a total of over 4,000 merit points.

This appeared to have been quite a significant number, but it was still very far away from the 9,000 merit points required to exchange for the second level of the Mantra Treasured Axis.

Han Li was slowly making his way toward the main hall of the High Profound Palace while contemplating how he was going to earn 5,000 more merit points.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to him.

On the golden stone wall in the High Profound Palace was a mission that granted a reward of exactly 5,000 merit points for cultivating the Mantra Axis Scripture to the second level.

With that in mind, Han Li immediately sped up in his footsteps, arriving in the main hall of the High Profound Palace before making his way over to the golden stone wall.

The main hall was still as lively and bustling as usual, and even the golden stone wall had around a dozen inner sect elders gathered in front of it, all of whom were looking up at the missions on the wall.

Han Li ignored the other missions as he cast his gaze directly toward the missions on the top of the wall that were inscribed in red. Sure enough, the mission that he was looking for was still there, and it was extremely concise, but Han Li stood and stared at it for close to an hour.

His concern was that if others were to see him accepting this mission, then the progress that he had made in the Mantra Axis Scripture would be exposed.

After all, even though there were many people who had attempted to use this cultivation art, barely anyone had ever succeeded, and the progress that he had made was nothing short of outrageous. The average True Immortal could've easily spent hundreds of thousands of years toiling away without making even a tenth of the progress that he had made.

Hence, if it were to be revealed that he had mastered the first level of the cultivation art, then that would be sure to create a massive stir in the Blaze Dragon Dao, and he would most definitely become the center of attention of the entire sect.

The thought of these complications was giving Han Li a real headache. Even if he were somehow able to accept this mission and earn the 5,000 merit point reward without alerting anyone else, he would inevitably be exposed anyway once he went to the Merit Conveyance Palace to exchange for the second level of the Mantra Axis Arts.

That would be no different from telling everyone that he had mastered the first level of the Mantra Axis Scripture. After all, who would spend 9,000 merit points on the second part of the cultivation art if they hadn't mastered the first part?

Will I have to steal it?

As soon as this idea sprang into his mind, Han Li immediately shook his head to rid himself of the thought.

The Blaze Dragon Dao wasn't the Cold Flame Sect of the Spirit Domain Realm. Not only was it home to a whole host of formidable Golden Immortals, the Merit Conveyance Palace was clearly no ordinary place, so there had to have been powerful restrictions set up there, and attempting to steal the sect's most prized cultivation art from there would've been no different from committing suicide.

However, he couldn't just give up on the cultivation art, either. After all, the main reason he had joined the Blaze Dragon Dao was for the sake of this Mantra Axis Scripture.

After contemplating the matter for a long while, Han Li turned and began to make his way out of the palace.

Half a day later, a man dressed in a scholarly robe made his way into the High Profound Palace.

He casually strode over to the golden stone wall, and the other inner sect elders nearby turned to look at him in unison before quickly directing their attention back to the stone wall.

The scholarly-robed man stood on the spot for a long while, and after making sure that no one was paying any attention to him, he flipped a hand over to summon his elder badge before pointing it at a certain spot on the golden stone wall.

A burst of light immediately flew out of the wall before landing on his elder badge.

The scholarly-robed man was none other than Han Li, who had disguised himself using his Transient Guild mask.

After extensive consideration, he decided that he was going to claim the reward for this mission. The reward was a hefty 5,000 merit points, and there was no reason for him not to claim it.

He could sense that the number of merit points in his elder badge had increased to 9,132.

The top section of missions inscribed in red on the stone wall were ones that didn't garner much attention anyway, and at this moment, the elders gathered in front of the wall were either conversing with one another or searching for missions that were suitable for themselves, so no one had noticed exactly which mission Han Li had claimed.

Furthermore, given his current disguise, no one would be able to identify him anyway.

With that in mind, Han Li casually stowed his elder badge away, then heaved an internal sigh of relief as he turned to depart from the High Profound Palace.

However, right as he did so, his entire body suddenly stiffened. Out of the corner of his eye, he noticed that the line of red text on the stone wall had changed...

Chapter 267: White Finch Valley

Han Li stopped in his tracks before hurriedly turning around to find that a line of golden seal text had appeared after the red text.

"Show your axis in the White Finch Valley."

The line of golden seal text seemed to have been shrouded in layer of murky golden light, making it impossible to see it clearly.

After looking at the golden text for just a moment, Han Li immediately felt a dry and sore sensation in his eyes, and he hurriedly rubbed his eyes before casting his gaze toward the same spot on the stone wall, only to find that there was no longer anything there.

He hurriedly turned to look around him, and he discovered that everyone else was either still staring at the stone wall or conversing with one another, and it was clear that no one had seen what had happened just now.

White Finch Valley? Where's that?

Han Li couldn't recall such a place in the Blaze Dragon Dao.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he turned back to the stone wall, trying to see if anything had changed in the line of red text, but nothing was different about it.

It was as if that line of golden text had been nothing more than a figment of his imagination.

However, he knew that even though he had only seen it for an instant, there was no way that it was just his mind playing tricks on him.

In any case, he had to find this so-called White Finch Valley and pay it a visit. Otherwise, it would continue to weigh on his mind.

But where exactly was this place?

Han Li stood on the spot for a while longer, then made his way over to a corner of the hall before flipping a hand over to produce the map of the Bell Toll Mountain Range that he had obtained upon first entering the sect. After that, he injected his spiritual sense into the map and began to carefully search through it.'

He ended up standing in that corner of the hall for over two hours before opening his eyes and stowing the map away, but the befuddlement on his face had only become even more pronounced.

He had scoured the entire map with his spiritual sense several times over to ensure that he hadn't missed anything, but he still wasn't able to find any place by the name of White Finch Valley.

Could it be a certain secret area in the sect? Han Li thought to himself.

With that in mind, he made his way over to the stone wall and stared at it for a while longer before turning and departing from the High Profound Palace.

After that, he rose up into the air above the High Profound Palace with his hands clasped behind his back and a contemplative look on his face. A few moments later, he sped away toward a certain direction as a streak of azure light.

……

That night, in the secret chamber in the cave abode on the Crimson Dawn Peak.

On a square eight immortals table sat an antiquated azure lamp, and it was unclear what type of fuel was being burned in the lamp, but it wasn't releasing any smoke and was giving off a pleasant fragrance.

The flame on the wick was abnormally stable, not flicking even in the slightest, and it was only a tiny flame, but it was able to illuminate the entire room so that it was as bright as day.

On one corner of the table were several thick antiquated books, beside which sat three or jade slips. There was also a yellow scroll that was around seven feet in length draped over the edge of the table, with half of it still rolled up, while the other half was spread out on the floor.

A series of extremely life-like mountains had been painted onto the scroll with the names of the mountains marked out in annotations next to them in small text. As it turned out, the scroll contained an intricate map.

At this moment, Han Li was seated behind the table, holding an ancient scripture that he was reading with a look of concentration in his eyes.

These jade slips and books all contained historical records of the Bell Toll Mountain Range, and he had borrowed them from the inner tome library on the Imperial Dragon Peak.

Aside from those jade slips, those books and that scroll were all original copies. He could've purchased replicas of them, but in order to access the oldest map records available, he had decided to borrow these ancient scriptures, even though doing so had cost more merit points than it would've taken for him to purchase replicas.

Han Li carefully inspected all of the content in these historical records and maps, making sure to examine even the finest of details, but up to this point, he still hadn't found any place by the name of White Finch Valley.

There were several places that had similar names, but most of them clearly weren't important locations in the sect.

The main focal point of his attention was those black areas that he had seen on the Inkspirit Scenic Scroll. The majority of those places were restricted areas in the sect, and there were no annotations of them on most maps, but they were mentioned in some of the historical records.

Even after some extensive cross comparison, Han Li was disappointed to find that there were still no mentions of the White Finch Valley.

The Ancient Cloud Records that he was currently holding was already the final book out of the ones that he had borrowed.

Strictly speaking, this book didn't contain official historical records. Intead, it was a travel journal that detailed the layout of the Ancient Cloud Continent, and it had been written by a cultivator who had been struggling in his cultivation and had decided to go on a journey of self-discovery.

However, this book had been written in an extremely early time period, and it was perhaps even as old as the Blaze Dragon Dao itself. There was a restriction placed on the book, and if that restriction were to be removed, then the book would instantly disintegrate into dust.

Han Li gently flipped over to the next page before reading through its contents, and all of a sudden, he raised an eyebrow as he pulled the book slightly closer to himself to carefully examine one particular passage of text on the page.

"There is a valley in the western mountain where white finches flock in large numbers. Upon entering the valley, one won't see the valley. Instead, they'll be greeted by the sight of palaces and pavilions enshrouded in dense mist, feeling as if they had inadvertently stepped into another world..."

Han Li continued to read through this passage of text to find that the second half of the story was about a shepherd boy who had stumbled into the valley, where he was beaten with a whip by a deity clad in golden armor. All of a sudden, he had returned to his senses and found himself still standing in the valley, and it was as if everything that had just happened to him had been nothing more than a dream.

There were many strange places that harbored illusions and mirages detailed in the travel journal, and most of those places were glossed over without much description, but this valley where white finches flocked in large numbers was a place that the author seemed to have taken a particular interest in.

During his earlier readings, Han Li had come across birds like white orioles and snow pheasants, but this was the first time that he had seen mention of white finches.

After carefully reading through the entire travel journal, he was able to confirm that this was the only passage in the story where white finches had been explicitly mentioned.

Where is this west mountain supposed to be?

Han Li fell into deep thought as he absentmindedly drummed his fingers against the table.

Moments later, he suddenly dragged all of the books sitting on the corner of the table to himself, then flipped each one open to certain pages before laying them out on the table.

With his gaze focused on one of the pages, Han Li murmured to himself, "West Unitary Mountain, a long and narrow mountain that stretches from south to north, standing at a height of 72,570 feet... West Spring Mountain, standing at a height of 89,310 feet... West Luster Mountain..."

……

Before long, Han Li had already been reading well into the night, and he stood up from behind the table as he stretched lazily, then gently closed the books laid out before him one by one.

After that, he placed them back on the same corner of the table in an orderly fashion, and the only thing that was still spread open on the table was the scroll that contained the map.

However, only around a foot of the scroll was unfurled, and on that section of the scroll was a mountain by the name of West Forest Mountain.

This mountain was situated in the western region of the Bell Toll Mountain Range, and it was just an ordinary mountain with no remarkable traits, which was why it hadn't ever been inhabited by any elders or disciples.

The western part of the mountain was close to the Cattail Spirit Valley, while its eastern part was situated directly across from a side branch of the Bell Toll Mountain Range, with an extremely wide crescent-shaped valley standing between them.

After much deliberation, Han Li had determined this to be the west mountain described in the travel journal, and he believed the crescent-shaped valley known as Half Moon Valley was very likely to be the White Finch Valley that he was searching for.

With a sweep of his sleeve, the lamp sitting on the eight immortals table was snuffed out, and wisps of white smoke began to rise up from the wick of the lamp, releasing a pleasant fragrance that lingered in the air.

Han Li strode out of the room before closing the door and making his way toward the front yard, but he hadn't even made it out of the hall when he spotted Meng Qianqian rushing toward him.

As soon as she spotted Han Li, she immediately began to yell, "Elder Li, it's coming out!"

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly with befuddlement upon hearing this, but he then quickly realized what she had to have been referring to, and an elated look appeared on his face.

"Let's go take a look."

He made his way over to Meng Qianqian as he spoke, then gently grabbed onto her arm, and the two of them instantly vanished from the spot as a streak of azure light.

Moments later, Han Li and Meng Qianqian appeared in a stone chamber of the cave abode, at the center of the giant white egg.

The egg was situated atop the same spirit gathering array as before, constantly absorbing the world's origin qi while swaying slightly from side to side.

However, even after 15 minutes had passed by, the egg still showed no signs of hatching.

"It was shaking really violently just now, and I could hear tapping coming from inside the egg, so I thought it was about to hatch, and that's why I went to you in such a hurry..." Meng Qianqian said as an apologetic look appeared on her face.

Han Li took a closer look at the egg, and he noticed that a circle of extremely small cracks had appeared on the underside of the egg, and they would've been impossible to spot without careful examination.

"It's already hatched, but it must've been scared with no mother bird present, so it's gone back into the egg for shelter," Han Li speculated.

After that, he flipped a hand over to produce a shimmering azure feather, which he offered to Meng Qianqian.

Meng Qianqian didn't know why she was being given this feather, but she still accepted it as she turned to Han Li with a perplexed expression.

"You should be able to get it to come out now," Han Li said with a smile.

Meng Qianqian was feeling rather skeptical, but she still approached the egg before gently knocking on it with her hand.

There was no reaction from the egg at all.

After waiting for a moment, Meng Qianqian gently stroked the surface of the egg with the feather in her hand.

This time, the egg seemed to have sensed something, and it stopped moving entirely for a moment before beginning to sway from side to side once again, but still far less vigorously than before.

Meng Qianqian's eyes lit up slightly upon seeing this, and she continued to stroke the surface of the egg with the feather while simultaneously stroking the egg with her other hand.

All of a sudden, the egg stopped swaying and fell completely still.

Chapter 268: Featheryearn

"Elder Li..."

Meng Qianqian turned back to Han Li with a resigned expression, but all of a sudden, a faint crack rang out, and the circle of cracks on the underside of the egg began to bulge outward, following which a piece of eggshell the size of a human head fell out to create a hole in the egg.

Meng Qianqian hurriedly turned around upon hearing this, focusing her gaze on the hole in the egg with a hint of anticipation and anxiety in her eyes, and she was greeted by a sound much like the chirping of a chicken hatchling.

Immediately thereafter, a furry head that was roughly the same size as the hole in the egg poked out from within.

The eyes of the head were only half open, and the head itself was covered in a layer of shimmering azure feathers. It bore somewhat of a resemblance to a hen, with a short and straight beak, above which was a pair of nostrils, and its cheeks were rather bloated, giving it an adorably dopey appearance.

Only after turning its head side to side a few times did it completely open its eyes, and it took a glance at Han Li before turning its gaze to Meng Qianqian with its head cocked to the side.

After that, it emerged fully from the egg before stumbling unsteadily toward Meng Qianqian.

It had a long and thin neck connected to a rather frail and wiry body that was completely out of proportion with its large head. It was as if all of its nutrients had gone to growing its head, giving it a very unbalanced body.

Han Li wasn't exactly disappointed by the bird, he merely felt like it was a little... ugly.

He couldn't help but wonder where and for what purpose Fang Pan had obtained this egg.

In contrast with Han Li's reaction, Meng Qianqian's eyes were glowing as she watched the delicate hatchling stumbling toward her. At the same time, she couldn't help but feel a little concerned, fearing that its thin and frail neck wouldn't be able to support the weight of its large head.

She looked straight into the hatchling's eyes, and she didn't find it to be ugly at all. Instead, she felt like it was very adorable in a clumsy way.

At times when she had previously encountered cultivation bottlenecks or had something weighing on her mind that she didn't want to tell even her brother, she would come to this egg, treating it like a close friend that she could speak to in her time of need.

Before she knew it, the egg had become a close companion of hers on her cultivation journey, having been with her since she was at the Nascent Soul Stage.

It could even be said that without the companionship provided by this egg, perhaps she wouldn't have been able to reach the Deity Transformation Stage so quickly, so now that the egg had finally hatched, she was overcome by a sense of mixed emotions.

She slowly crouched down and picked up the hatchling, which had finally stumbled its way to her side, and gently stroked its soft feathers with her hand.

Meanwhile, the hatchling rested its head on the feather that she was holding, gently rubbing its head against it while chirping quietly to itself.

"Can you give it a name, Elder Li?" Meng Qianqian asked as she turned to Han Li with the hatchling cradled in her arms.

"That feather you're holding most likely belonged to its mother, so let's call it Featheryearn," Han Li said after a moment of contemplation.

"Featheryearn... That's a really nice name! I'll call it Featheryearn from now on," Meng Qianqian replied with a joyful smile.

Meng Qianqian raised the hatchling to her eye level, then said to it with a serious expression, "From now on, your name is Featheryearn!"

Only then did Han Li notice that there was a small fleshy growth concealed beneath the hatchling's feathers on the underside of its head.

His brows furrowed slightly as he approached Meng Qianqian and took the hatchling from her, and after carefully observing it for a while, he lifted the wings and the tail of the hatchling one by one. In doing so, he discovered a faintly shimmering feather under each of those places, and a contemplative look appeared on his face.

"Is there something wrong, Elder Li?" Meng Qianqian asked with a concerned expression.

"No, it's just that I've been trying to figure out what this egg is this entire time, but to no avail, and now that the egg has hatched, I've finally gotten an idea of what it could be," Han Li replied with a smile.

Meng Qianqian was rather intrigued to hear this, and she hurriedly asked, "Is Featheryearn supposed to be something special?"

"I can't say for sure right now, but what I can be certain of is that it's a wind-attribute spirit bird, and one with extremely high evolutionary potential, at that. Perhaps its body holds some type of true spirit bloodline," Han Li replied.

Meng Qianqian's eyes lit up even further upon hearing this, and she turned to the hatchling as she praised, "It sounds like you're destined for great things, Featheryearn!"

The hatchling naturally had no idea what was being said about it, and it was continuing to chirp incessantly, seemingly full of longing and curiosity toward the world around it.

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce an azure pill, following which a burst of azure light emerged over the palms of his hand to envelop the entire pill.

It didn't take long before the pill began to melt away within the azure light, transforming into a burst of azure qi that was imbued with rich spiritual power.

Han Li then guided the burst of azure qi into the hatchling's beak, and it slid down Featheryearn's long and thin neck, then flashed a few times in its belly before fading away.

Featheryearn immediately stopped chirping before burping in a very humanized fashion, much to Meng Qianqian's amusement, and she began to giggle with delight.

Right after it let loose that hearty burp, Featheryearn's eyelids instantly began to droop, and its head rolled to the side as it fell asleep.

"The wind-attribute spirit pill that I just fed it is still too much for it to process for now, even though I already used my magic power to make it easier to digest, but this is a good thing. Now that it's asleep, it'll be able to better digest the pill," Han Li explained with a smile.

Meng Qianqian nodded in response.

"Keep that feather for now. You were the one who looked after Featheryearn's egg all this time, so you can keep looking after it now that it's hatched," Han Li said as he passed the sleeping hatchling back to Meng Qianqian.

"Yes, Elder Li," Meng Qianqian replied as she eagerly took Featheryearn from him.

"I recall that there are quite a few wind-attribute spirit plants in the spirit fields on the mountain. You can use those to feed it, but make sure to only feed it 10-year-old plants in the beginning and only feed it older spirit plants when it's ready. Also, make sure you don't feed it any spirit plants or pills of any other attribute," Han Li cautioned.

"Yes, Elder Li," Meng Qianqian replied with a nod.

"Alright, you can go now," Han Li said with a dismissive wave of his hand.

Meng Qianqian did as she was told, turning to depart with Featheryearn in her arms, but right as she was about to step out of the stone chamber, Han Li called out to her again.

"What is it, Elder Li?" Meng Qianqian asked as she turned around with a puzzled expression.

"If I'm not mistaken, you've already reached the Deity Transformation Stage, right?" Han Li asked with a smile.

"Ah, I was meaning to tell you about that, but I never got a chance to do so, and I ended up forgetting after getting distracted by Featheryearn's egg," Meng Qianqian replied with a slightly embarrassed smile.

"You possess superior aptitude to your brother and the others, so it's no surprise that you've been able to make faster progress in your cultivation. Here are some Deity Transformation Stage pills as a congratulatory gift for your breakthrough," Han Li said with a smile as he tossed a white porcelain vial at Meng Qianqian, who hurriedly caught the vial and thanked Han Li earnestly before departing in an elated fashion.

Not long after she left, Han Li flew out of his cave abode as a streak of azure light and departed from the Crimson Dawn Peak.

The next day.

It was a bright and sunny day.

The western region of the Bell Toll Mountain Range was still covered in a layer of snow, with only certain areas, such as the palaces and the plazas, where the snow had been swept away.

Aside from that, there were also places with underground fire veins or hot springs that had managed to keep the snow at bay, and there was even some greenery present around those areas.

A streak of azure light flew through the air before descending toward the Half Moon Valley beside the West Forest Mountain.

After departing from the Crimson Dawn Peak, the previous night, Han Li had returned the Essence Fire Raven to the cave that contained the underground fire vein, then set off for what he speculated to have been the White Finch Valley.

The Essence Fire Raven had been very pleased to be back, and it circled around Han Li a few times before eagerly flying back into the cave.

After that, Han Li had traveled to the western region of the Bell Toll Mountain Range through a teleportation hall.

If he had chosen to teleport straight to the Cattail Spirit Valley before traveling to the West Forest Peak from there, he would've been able to save a lot of time, and that would've allowed him to reach the Half Moon Valley before first light.

However, the arrival of a True Immortal in the Cattail Spirit Valley would've created a massive stir, even if he had no intention of picking out any servants, and he didn't want to attract any attention.

Hence, he had chosen to take a slightly longer route, and that was why it had taken him so long to get to his destination.

The Half Moon Valley was just as unremarkable as the West Forest Mountain beside it, so neither of those places were held in very high regard by the sect. As such, the Half Moon Valley was still a completely untouched place.

Han Li descended upon the entrance of the valley, then made his way inside to discover a thick layer of snow stretching as far as the eyes could, interspersed only by some dark red rocks, presenting a rather barren sight to behold.

After making his way several thousand feet into the valley, the terrain was becoming wider and more open, but it was also noticeably lower than at the entrance of the valley, and Han Li could tell that he had been walking downhill this entire time.

After walking for around an hour, the valley up ahead suddenly became filled with mist, making it difficult for him to see his surroundings clearly.

Han Li skirted around a massive rock in the valley, and he discovered a large crescent-shaped lake behind it. There were plumes of steam rising up from the lake, clearly indicating that it was a geothermal hot spring.

The temperature around the hot spring was slightly higher than elsewhere in the valley, and an exposed dark red lake bank could be seen.

Han Li made his way over to the edge of the lake before stopping in his tracks and peering into the water with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes.

The surface of the lake was rippling slightly, and the water was very clear, allowing Han Li to see that the lakebed was riddled with countless rocks of different sizes, but he couldn't see any fish or living creatures inside.

Moments later, Han Li withdrew his gaze, then carefully released his spiritual sense to encompass the entire valley, but after some examination, he wasn't able to find anything of note, and it was as if this really was just a normal valley.

The mission was for him to show his Mantra Treasured Axis in the White Finch Valley, and with that in mind, Han Li sat down with his legs crossed.

Chapter 269: The Eye of Truth

If this really is the so-called White Finch Valley, then perhaps something will happen if I summon my Mantra Treasured Axis here.

With that in mind, Han Li made a hand seal and activated his Mantra Axis Scripture cultivation art.

His Mantra Treasured Axis then appeared behind him amid a flash of golden light, and it began to revolve slowly in mid-air.

The 24 semi-transparent Time Dao Runes on the axis were flashing incessantly while giving off bursts of powerful law fluctuations, causing everything in a radius of 100 feet to slow down to such a degree that it was as if everything had fallen still.

The wind had stagnated, and even the flow of air had become extremely slow. Similarly, the ripples on the surface of the lake also appeared to have been frozen solid.

The mist rising up from the surface of the lake resembled pillars of white smoke that were moving extremely slowly, and compared with the mist in the distance, which was moving at a normal speed, the mist affected by the Mantra Treasured Axis may as well have not been moving at all.

Han Li slowly spun around as he inspected his surroundings, trying to find abnormal change in the environment, but even after a lengthy period of observation, he wasn't able to spot anything.

Right as he was beginning to think that he was in the wrong place, something out of the ordinary finally happened.

A burst of white light suddenly appeared in front of him, and a palm sized white finch appeared out of thin air, flapping its wings as it flew toward the lake.

It was encompassed within the 100-foot effective radius of the Mantra Treasured Axis, but it seemed to have been completely unaffected as it descended gently onto the surface of the lake, sending ripples spreading in all directions around it.

Han Li was staring at the white finch, unsure of what to do next.

Right at this moment, the white finch suddenly turned back to take a glance at him, then gently pecked down onto the surface of the lake with its gray beak.

Han Li felt as if he could hear the chime of a bell ring out, immediately following which circles of ripples appeared on the surface of the lake before spreading outward in all directions.

The further outward the ripples spread, the larger the waves that they swept up were, and upon reaching the stone banks on either side of the lake, the waves had become so large that they were sending large volumes of water splashing in all directions.

A black hole around the same thickness as an adult human's torso had appeared at the center of the waves, and a glowing black octagonal array emerged above it, giving off powerful spatial fluctuations.

"There's a secret area here!" Han Li exclaimed as his brows furrowed slightly.

The white finch that had triggered all of this seemed to have been rather displeased by his hesitation, and it spread its wings and circled around in the air for a while before flying into the black hole, vanishing amid a flash of light.

Han Li didn't hesitate any longer as he withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis, then leaped up into the air before also falling into the black hole.

However, as soon as his feet landed upon the opening of the black hole, he appeared to have been kept out by an invisible barrier, unable to pass through the array.

Blue light flashed within his eyes as he attempted to find a way to bypass the array.

Some time later, his brows furrowed slightly as he raised his fist before punching down on the invisible barrier beneath him, he felt as if his fist had struck a wall of cotton, and most of its power was instantly nullified.

After that, Han Li attempted several more methods to try and break through the restriction, but all to no avail. The restriction was extremely profound and seemingly had no weaknesses at all.

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face as he pondered what to do next.

Judging from what had just happened, it seemed that he had guessed right, and that this was indeed the so-called White Finch Valley.

However, the white finch had already flown into the secret area, and it seemed to have been guiding him into it as well, so why was he unable to enter.

Could it be...

A thought suddenly occurred to him as he flipped a hand over to produce his elder badge, then pointed it at the octagonal array above the black hole.

A burst of black light flew out of the array and onto the badge, upon which 9,000 merit points were instantly deducted, leaving him with a measly 132 merit points.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this, following which an elated look appeared on his face.

Before he had a chance to think about anything else, light flashed from the array above the black hole, then swept up to envelop his entire body before dragging him straight into the hole.

After that, the black hole abruptly vanished.

The ripples surging across the surface of the lake still hadn't subsided, but the mist that was rising up from it had already returned to normal.

Han Li felt a brief rush of dizziness before finding himself standing on a white stone plaza.

He inspected his surroundings to find a cluster of mountains behind him, while there was a massive deity statue that was over 1,000 feet tall situated to both his left and to his right. Each of the deity statues was wielding a giant weapon that was resting on the ground, and both statues were glowering directly at Han Li.

Han Li only took a brief glance at the statues before directing his gaze directly up ahead.

At the end of the plaza was a golden palace with no end in sight, and above it was a layer of lustrous clouds that were glowing bright.

There was a pavilion with no walls in front of the palace, and a pair of sage-like figures were seated across from one another in the pavilion, playing a game of go. Behind each of them was a pair of celestial maidens in palatial dresses, holding incense burners and cups of tea, and none of them were looking in Han Li's direction.

At the gates of the palace were two teams of warriors clad in suits of golden armor, and as soon as they spotted Han Li, they immediately began rushing toward him with fierce killing intent.

Han Li gave a cold harrumph upon seeing this, and instead of stepping forward to meet the approaching assailants, he sat down with his legs crossed instead.

A burst of blue light then flashed within his eyes as he made a hand seal, then released his enormous spiritual sense in all directions without any restraint.

The sound of splashing waves rang out, and a formidable aura erupted in all directions with Han Li at the center.

Countless rifts were instantly torn into the white stone plaza beneath him, and the entire earth was peeled back before crumbling away. The two deity statues on either side of him collapsed violently before disintegrating into dust, while the cluster of mountains behind him also vanished without a trace.

Before the golden-armored warriors had a chance to reach him, they were also torn to shreds by this wave of destruction, and it didn't take long before the golden palace up ahead also crumbled away, along with the pavilion in front of it and the people situated in the pavilion.

The entire illusion around Han Li had been destroyed, while he remained seated on the ground.

However, the white stone plaza beneath him had turned into mossy dirt, and he was surrounded by lush mountains. It appeared that he was situated in a vast area, but he could clearly sense the presence of spatial barriers around him.

It seemed that this secret area was far smaller than he had imagined.

With that in mind, he slowly rose to his feet, then habitually dusted off his robes before casting his gaze directly forward.

There, he spotted a giant stone monument that was over 100 feet wide.

A strange beast that resembled both a dragon and a serpent was engraved on either side of the stone monument, but the monument was extremely severely damaged, and it was clearly missing a large chunk on top, so it was impossible to tell exactly what it was.

The fractured part of the stone monument was covered in moss, giving it a dilapidated appearance, but thankfully, the bottom half had been preserved very well, and it was riddled with golden seal text.

Han Li quickly made his way over to the base of the stone monument, and after just a single glance, he was immediately rooted to the spot.

This is the Mantra Axis Scripture!

The text recorded on the broken monument had clearly been split up into two parts, between which was a blank area.

The part of the monument near the ground was covered by some short weeds, and the recorded text was very familiar to Han Li. It was none other than the first level of the Mantra Axis Scripture, while the second level was recorded near the top of the monument.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he fell into deep thought.

If the Mantra Axis Scripture was in the sect's Merit Conveyance Palace, then why had this strange stone monument been erected here? And why was it so difficult to access? Could it be that the second level of the Mantra Axis Scripture in the Merit Conveyance Palace also had to be obtained from this place?

After all, it had cost him the same price of 9,000 merit points to enter this place, and this was something that he could perhaps indirectly enquire about the next time he went to the Merit Conveyance Palace.

At the same time, he couldn't help but wonder if it was a coincidence that he had noticed the fleeting line of text on the stone wall in the High Profound Palace that had led him to this place.

Right at this moment, a burst of white light suddenly appeared above him, and the white finch that had guided him into this place reappeared before descending onto the broken monument to nibble at the moss on its fractured surface.

Han Li cast his gaze toward the white finch to find that it had a slightly illusory appearance, making it impossible to see it clearly.

Right as he was observing the white finch, it suddenly stopped what it was doing, then turned to him and opened its beak to speak: "Why are you looking at me? You only have half a day here, so hurry up and memorize the cultivation art!"

Han Li was caught completely off guard by the fact that the white finch was able to speak. Its way of speech was slightly awkward, so it had clearly been granted the ability to speak by some type of restriction, but Han Li still found this to be quite surprising.

Thus, he couldn't help but look at the white finch for a moment longer.

"Stop looking at me!" the white finch protested.

Han Li hurriedly withdrew his gaze with a sheepish expression before focusing his attention on the stone monument.

Just like the first level of the Mantra Axis Scripture, the second level was also written in golden seal text, and an ancient method of language formulation was used, making it very difficult to understand.

Thankfully, given the foundation that he had established from the first level of the cultivation art, Han Li wasn't at a complete loss, but he was still only able to read through the text very slowly.

As he read through the text engraved on the stone monument, he was forcibly committing it to his memory using his formidable spiritual sense.

After about four hours, a faint sheen of sweat had already appeared on his forehead, and he exhaled deeply, having finally completely memorized the second level of the cultivation art.

Attached to the second level of the Mantra Axis Scripture was a secret technique known as the Eye of Truth, which apparently granted anyone that mastered it the ability to see through all illusions.

However, in order to cultivate this secret technique, one had to have already attained at least 12 Time Dao Runes on their Mantra Treasured Axis.

Chapter 270: Space-time Restoration

With that in mind, a peculiar look flashed through Han Li's eyes.

Even though he had only mastered the first level of the cultivation art, he had already manifested 24 Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis, so he was naturally able to cultivate the Eye of Truth secret technique.

He made a hand seal as he began to chant an incantation, and his Mantra Treasured Axis instantly appeared behind him amid a flash of golden light.

The white finch standing on the stone monument was still nibbling at the moss, but it immediately raised its head and turned to Han Li upon sensing the law fluctuations emanating from the Mantra Treasured Axis, and its movements weren't slowed down at all.

Han Li took another glance at the cultivation art recorded on the stone monument, and a determined look appeared in his eyes as he began to chant the mantra for the second level of the cultivation art.

Shortly thereafter, he suddenly switched to a different hand seal, and his chanting also grew faster.

Meanwhile, the Mantra Treasured Axis began to revolve at a higher speed behind him while radiating dazzling golden light.

Initially, only six of the Time Dao Runes on the axis had been glowing, but the rest of them were lighting up one after another.

With each Time Dao Rune that lit up, the flow of time within a radius of 100 feet around Han Li would slow down a bit further, while the rotation of the Mantra Treasured Axis became faster.

Before long, the axis was revolving so quickly that it had turned into a blur, and faint golden threads could be seen surging out of the axis before converging toward the hole at the center of the axis.

Han Li could feel the immortal spiritual power in his body being rapidly expended at twice the rate of expenditure that he experienced during pill refinement.

He immediately flipped a hand over to summon an Immortal Origin Stone, using it to replenish his immortal spiritual power.

Shortly thereafter, the 12th Time Dao Rune lit up, and the entire Mantra Treasured Axis began to emit a loud buzzing sound as it abruptly ceased in its rotation.

All of the golden threads that had converged in the hole at the center of the axis had intertwined to form a fist-sized golden ball, which was shimmering with golden radiance.

Han Li's chanting also ceased upon seeing this, and all of a sudden, the light radiating from the ball of golden threads became as bright and dazzling as the sun.

The light was too bright for Han Li to stare into, so he involuntarily closed his eyes.

Several seconds later, the dazzling golden light finally began to gradually dim.

Han Li massaged his own eyes for a moment, then turned to look at the Mantra Treasured Axis behind him.

The axis had originally only been around a foot in size, but it seemed to have swelled slightly in size, and there was a large vertical eye that was tightly shut situated in the hole at its center.

So this is the Eye of Truth...

Han Li made a hand seal according to the description in the secret technique to activate the Eye of Truth, and this time, there was no massive outflow of immortal spiritual power like before.

12 of the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis lit up in unison while releasing a burst of peculiar fluctuations, and the vertical golden eye shuddered, following which its golden eyelids parted down the center to the left and the right, revealing a golden eyeball.

The eyeball was completely golden in color, but its coloration wasn't even throughout. The golden hue at the center of the eye's pupil was clearly more vibrant, resembling a ball of molten gold.

The golden light radiating from the edge of the pupil was slightly less vibrant, and there was a concentrated circle of strange runes around it. Outside the circle of runes, the golden coloration was even fainter, and it wasn't even as pronounced as the golden color of the eyelids.

As soon as the Eye of Truth sprang open, the circle of runes around the pupils instantly began to rapidly revolve, while a burst of faint golden light was projected out of the pupil.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon seeing this, and he began to inspect his surroundings through the Eye of Truth instead of his physical eyes.

The surrounding mountains instantly fell away to reveal a series of semi-transparent spatial barriers, outside of which was a vast expanse of murky gray space, as if the entire area were enshrouded within a cloud of gray mist.

That's it?

If this were the extent of the power of the Eye of Truth, then it really wasn't much different from his Brightsight Spirit Eyes. It appeared that the Eye of Truth only allowed him to see some concealed things with a little more clarity, and that fell far short of his expectations.

He began to slowly turn around, and the Mantra Treasured Axis mirrored his movement, while the Eye of Truth also began to turn.

As Han Li turned to face the stone monument, the Eye of Truth did the same, and a layer of faint white light suddenly appeared over the monument.

The layer of light resembled a veil of thin smoke that obstructed his gaze, rendering him unable to clearly make out the text on the stone monument, and the white finch standing on the monument had also transformed into a ball of energy similar to the world's origin qi.

Han Li was very surprised to see this, and he began to activate his Mantra Treasured Axis to its full capacity.

Bright golden light emanated from the axis as the semi-transparent Time Dao Runes lit up one after another, and before long, all of them had been illuminated.

After all 24 Time Dao Runes had been activated, the golden light radiating from the Eye of Truth suddenly grew brighter, immediately following which a beam of golden light shot out of the eye's pupil, striking the layer of white light on the stone monument before instantly passing through.

The beam of white light was like a sharp blade that had sliced through the white light barrier and was beginning to tear it apart.

Right at this moment, the stone monument abruptly shuddered, startling the white finch and causing it to fly up into the air.

A burst of golden light appeared, and strange fluctuations began to surge out from within the stone monument. All of a sudden, Han Li was able to sense some rather faint yet familiar powers of time.

This stone monument is a treasure that contains the power of time!

Han Li was very much taken aback by this revelation, yet there were still more surprises to come.

A vast expanse of golden light began to surge out of the stone monument's fractured surface, and the broken section of the monument was rapidly being restored by the golden light.

Before long, the entire monument had been restored to its original state, looking as if it had been completely reconstructed, and even the damaged heads of the pair of beasts engraved on either side of the monument had been restored.

Could it be that this Eye of Truth is also able to repair objects and reconstruct treasures?

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li sprang up into the air, landing on top of the stone monument before reaching down to stroke the surface restored section of the monument.

However, as soon as his hand came into contact with the surface of the monument, it instantly passed right through.

So this is nothing more than a projection reflected by the Eye of Truth.

Han Li wasn't very surprised by this outcome, and he flew back down onto the ground before directing his gaze toward the restored section of the monument.

As soon as he did so, he was rooted to the spot once again.

As it turned out, another passage of golden seal text had appeared above the second passage, and the two of them were separated by another blank area.

This third passage of text was none other than the third level of the Mantra Axis Scripture!

Han Li was both astonished and ecstatic upon seeing this, and he knew that this was an immensely fortunate opportunity.

Right at this moment, a rather mechanical voice rang out from beside him. "You still have two hours left."

The voice belonged to none other than that white finch. Even with the assistance of the Eye of Truth, Han Li was unable to identify exactly what this white finch was.

He hurriedly focused his attention on the third passage of text upon hearing this, memorizing the third level of the Mantra Axis Scripture as quickly as he could.

With all 24 Time Dao Runes and the Eye of Truth activated at once, Han Li was rapidly burning through his immortal spiritual power reserves. Even though he was using an Immortal Origin Stone to replenish his energy, it still only took a few minutes for all of his immortal spiritual power to be depleted, rendering him unable to use the Eye of Truth any longer.

As the Eye of Truth faded away, the restored section of the stone monument also disintegrated into specks of golden light, while the Mantra Treasured Axis behind Han Li was withdrawn into his body.

Han Li gently exhaled as he flipped both hands over to summon a pair of Immortal Origin Stones, holding one in each hand to replenish his immortal spiritual power

There was a faint smile on his face, and the excitement in his heart refused to die down. He had only come to this place to try his luck, and he certainly wasn't expecting to have reaped such significant rewards from this trip.

Not only had he secured the second level of the Mantra Axis Scripture, he had managed to acquire the third level of the cultivation art as well, so he was naturally ecstatic.

"Time's up," the white finch declared as it flew back onto the stone monument.

"Thank you... Er... Senior," Han Li replied, deciding to refer to the white finch as senior after a moment of deliberation.

"I'm no senior, I'm nothing more than a manifestation of the restrictions in this secret area," the white finch replied.

Han Li still wanted to ask more questions, but the white finch didn't give him a chance to do so, spreading its wings and flying directly toward him. It appeared to have been moving very slowly, but it reached him in the blink of an eye.

Han Li was still holding the Immortal Origin Stones in his hands when felt the entire space moving toward him along with the white finch, and he was swallowed up before he had a chance to do anything.

In the next instant, the surface of the lake in the Half Moon Valley began to churn violently as if the water had been brought to a boil, and Han Li slowly emerged from the water onto the surface.

He looked down to find that the surface of the lake was already gradually returning to a tranquil state, with only faint ripples spreading through the water, and he could see a reflection of himself looking back at him.

The light in the valley was rather dim, and the snow was reflecting the light of the setting sun. It was already close to night time.

Chapter 271: The Function of the Eye of Truth

The next morning.

Han Li returned to the Crimson Dawn Peak without alerting anyone, and he quickly passed through the courtyard before entering his cave abode.

After activating all of the restrictions in the cave abode, he made his way into his secret chamber, then sat down with his legs crossed on a cushion before flipping a hand over to summon a white porcelain teacup.

This wasn't a treasure or artifact. Instead, it was just an ordinary cup, one that was commonly seen in wealthy mortal clans, and it was something that Han Li had taken from the table while passing through the hall.

He held the teacup in one hand as he gently flicked a finger against its rim.

A faint crack rang out as a piece of porcelain on the rim of the teacup was snapped off.

Han Li nodded to himself as he placed the broken teacup onto the ground in front of him, then made a hand seal, and his Mantra Treasured Axis immediately appeared behind him amid a flash of golden light.

The axis then began to slowly revolve, while a vertical golden eye appeared at its center.

Han Li began to chant an incantation, and the Mantra Treasured Axis instantly sped up in its rotation while emitting a faint buzzing sound.

The semi-transparent Time Dao Runes on the axis lit up one after another, and it didn't take long before all 24 Time Dao Runes were activating, releasing circles of golden ripples that illuminated the entire secret chamber.

The eyelids of the vertical eye at the center of the axis also peeled back to reveal the golden eyeball within.

The circle of runes at the center of the eyeball also began to rapidly revolve, following which a beam of faint golden light was projected out of the pupil.

Han Li directed his gaze toward the broken teacup, and the beam of golden light that was projected out of the Eye of Truth was also turned to the teacup.

The golden light illuminated the white teacup, giving the entire cup a translucent appearance.

However, the broken part of the teacup remained broken, not displaying any changes at all.

It looks like it can't restore ordinary items...

Han Li wasn't all that surprised by this outcome as he wasn't expecting the Eye of Truth to be able to work on ordinary items in the first place.

After a brief moment of contemplation, he flipped a hand over to produce a miniature black octagonal pagoda.

This pagoda was once a spirit treasure of quite a high caliber, possessing the ability to trap a target inside, but it was severely damaged, and as a result, its effectiveness was also severely diminished. However, there were some rather special runes engraved upon it that Han Li was rather interested in, and that was why he hadn't thrown the treasure away.

The pagoda was quite intricately crafted, and even though it was only around a foot tall, it was complete with pillars, doors, windows, and even plaques hanging above every single door, upon which were inscribed runes that spelled out profound mantras.

The pagoda was supposed to have seven levels, but due to the damage that it had sustained, the top level and the roof had both gone missing.

Han Li set the pagoda down onto the ground in front of him, then took a deep breath before activating his Eye of Truth again and directing its gaze toward the pagoda.

The pagoda was basked in golden radiance, and it began to glow with black light while releasing layers of peculiar fluctuations. A series of hidden runes concealed under the eaves of the pagoda and behind its pillars were also revealed.

However, just like with the teacup from before, its missing section remained missing.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he fell into deep thought.

Moments later, he swept a hand through the air to stow the pagoda away, then summoned a damaged red seal that he placed onto the ground before repeating the same process.

The Eye of Truth released another beam of golden light that encompassed the entire seal...

Close to a day later, Han Li was still seated with his legs crossed on his cushion, and he was holding an Immortal Origin Stone to replenish his immortal spiritual power.

There were 17 or 18 items littered on the ground in front of him, and all of them were treasures that were damaged in some way.

These were all of the damaged treasures that were currently in his possession, and they covered a wide array of attributes, such as wind, lightning, water, fire, etc. He had tested the Eye of Truth on every single one of these treasures one by one, but none of them were restored in the form of a projection as had been the case for the stone monument.

"How strange... What am I missing?" Han Li murmured to himself while replenishing his immortal spiritual power reserves.

The Eye of Truth has no effect on ordinary items, nor is it effective on spirit treasures that contain spiritual power, yet it works on that stone monument in the White Finch Valley secret area.. What's so special about that monument?

He refused to believe that the Eye of Truth could only be effective on certain items. Instead, there had to have been a certain classification of items that it could work on.

Could it be...

All of a sudden, a thought sprang into his mind, and he flipped a hand over to produce a rectangular white jade box, upon which was adhered an azure talisman that could preserve spiritual qi.

Han Li gently stroked his hand over the jade box, and the talisman instantly vanished amid a flash of azure light.

He then opened the jade box, and a rich medicinal aroma instantly wafted throughout the room.

Inside the jade box was a high-grade spirit plant that had light purple leaf veins and was giving off a faint glow.

This was a Night Cloud Herb that was around a foot in length, and it was a primary ingredient for refining a type of earthly pill. This particular Night Cloud Herb had been matured to an age in excess of 50,000 years by the spirit liquid from the Heaven Controlling Vial.

Han Li stowed the Immortal Origin Stone away, then made a hand seal to summon his Mantra Treasured Axis again.

With all 24 Time Dao Runes activated, the Eye of Truth released a beam of golden light that fell upon the purple spirit herb.

Purple light began to emanate from the Night Cloud Herb, and under the scrutiny of the Eye of Truth, it began to rapidly shrink, quickly reverting back to only around an inch in length. The specks of light emanating from its leaf veins that were an indication of maturity had also faded, and it had reverted back into the form of a tender seedling.

I was right! The Eye of Truth only works on things that contain the power of time.

A faint smile appeared on Han Li's face as he had his suspicions confirmed.

After a brief pause, he reached out a hand to touch the seedling, but his hand passed right through the projection, and what he was actually touching was the mature spirit herb underneath.

Judging from the effect of the Eye of Truth on this spirit herb, it seems like the stone monument wasn't restored. Instead, it was only reverted back to an older version of itself, back when it was still whole. If the Eye of Truth really is able to reveal the past forms of items that contain the power of time, then it should work on those things as well.

With that in mind, he flipped a hand over once again, and a rectangular green jade box appeared out of thin air amid a flash of light.

With a sweep of his sleeve, the jade box was opened, and a gray rocky ball flew out from within. It was none other than the lone eyeball of the Primordial Fei Beast.

Han Li directed the gaze of the Eye of Truth toward the eyeball, and as it was basked in golden light, the eyeball gradually began to transform.

Rays of golden light began to radiate from its surface, forming a series of golden threads that extended outward, then intertwined with one another to form a golden skeleton, followed by a giant body.

Before long, a projection of the Primordial Fei Beast had been conjured up, and it was laid out flat in mid-air inside the secret chamber.

Due to how massive the Primordial Fei Beast was, half of its body had already vanished into one of the walls of the secret chamber, so Han Li was unable to see it in its full glory.

Han Li rose to his feet and made his way over to the head of the Primordial Fei Beast projection, and only after some close examination did he withdraw the Eye of Truth.

The massive projection in the secret chamber instantly vanished, leaving only the lone eye hovering in mid-air.

Han Li exhaled as he stowed the eyeball away, then flipped a hand over to produce another item. This time, it was a semi-transparent crystal the size of a water droplet.

This crystal was none other than a crystal that contained the power of time manifested by the Heaven Controlling Vial.

Han Li directed the gaze of the Eye of Truth toward the crystal, and the crystal instantly became enshrouded within a beam of faint golden light, following which it began to release a burst of dazzling white light alongside tremendous spiritual power fluctuations.

Han Li was quite startled by this turn of events, and he hurriedly attempted to stow the crystal away, but it was already too late.

A faint crack rang out, and the crystal fell apart within the golden light.

Before Han Li had a chance to react, the golden law thread within the crystal shot out like a steel needle, passing straight through Han Li before piercing into the Eye of Truth within his Mantra Treasured Axis.

Han Li felt as if the Mantra Treasured Axis had been dealt a heavy blow, and as a result, he was sent stumbling back in an involuntary manner.

Immediately thereafter, he felt the axis behind him begin to tremble while releasing bursts of invisible fluctuations.

He hurriedly cut off the secret technique to close the Eye of Truth, yet even after doing that, the Mantra Treasured Axis continued to tremble.

A hesitant look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this. He didn't know how to intervene, nor did he dare to withdraw the axis back into his body in its current state, so he could only force himself to calm down as he carefully observed the axis.

Thankfully, the tremors running through the Mantra Treasured Axis subsided after only around 15 minutes.

All of a sudden, an incredulous look appeared on Han Li's face. He discovered that a new Time Dao Rune had appeared on the Mantra Treasured Axis.

Chapter 272: Reversal True Axis

A hint of bewilderment flashed through Han Li's eyes, and he began to scrutinize the Mantra Treasured Axis intently with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes. He carefully counted the Time Dao Runes on the axis to find that there were now indeed 25 of them.

Could it be that the Eye of Truth also has the ability to absorb the power of time?

Han Li didn't know whether this additional Time Dao Rune was temporary or permanent, but if it were the latter, then this would be an incredible turn of events.

With that in mind, Han Li was immediately tempted to try more, but unfortunately, he only had a single crystal on hand, so he would have to wait a month before he could try the same thing again.

As for his Earthly Deity Avatar, it would just have to do without the crystals for now.

Han Li heaved a faint sigh to suppress the excitement in his heart, then withdrew the Mantra Treasured Axis back into his body.

After that, he reached into the collar of his robes to pull out the Heaven Controlling Vial around his neck.

This was something that had been with him ever since the beginning of his cultivation journey. It contained the most tremendous power of time out of anything in his possession, and it was the treasure that he wanted to make sense of the most.

He brought the vial closer to his own eyes, and a look of focus appeared on his face as he scrutinized the leaf-shaped patterns on its surface.

The Heaven Controlling Vial was his most important treasure and one of his most well-kept secrets. What had happened with the crystal just now hadn't resulted in any detrimental outcomes, but he was still concerned that something bad could happen to the Heaven Controlling Vial.

After some careful consideration, he decided to try something. He had always really wanted to find out the origins of the Heaven Controlling Vial, and at this point, he was confident that a treasure of the Heaven Controlling Vial's caliber wouldn't be damaged so easily.

After making up his mind, he set the vial down onto the floor in front of him, then activated his Eye of Truth and directed its gaze toward the vial.

The eye projected a beam of golden light onto the vial, which immediately shuddered slightly before rising up into the air.

Han Li's entire body was tightly wound, and there was an anxious look on his face as he scrutinized the vial through his Eye of Truth.

Right at this moment, a speck of white light the size of a grain of rice appeared within the vial, illuminating it from the inside to give it a translucent appearance. All of the leaf-shaped patterns on its surface became extremely vibrant and life-like as a result.

Right as Han Li thought that a projection was going to appear, the light within the vial suddenly turned a dark green color, and it devoured the beam of golden light shining into it like a vortex.

Han Li was quite startled by this, and his first reaction was to close the Eye of Truth, but he then discovered that the vial wasn't displaying any further changes beyond what had just happened.

After waiting for a while longer, there was still nothing of interest happening, and Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief. Following a brief pause, he decided to activate his newly attained 25th Time Dao Rune as well.

With all 25 Time Dao Runes glowing in unison, the Eye of Truth projected another beam of golden light onto the Heaven Controlling Vial, and this time, something unexpected happened.

A flash of light appeared over the surface of the vial, and it devoured the beam of golden light before shooting out a beam of green light toward the Eye of Truth.

Han Li was stunned to discover that even though the beam of green light wasn't moving very quickly, for some reason, it felt completely unstoppable to him.

The beam of green light fell silently upon the Eye of Truth, turning it a bright green color. At the same time, the entire Mantra Treasured Axis began to tremble violently, and the golden light radiating from it began to warp and blur in an unstable fashion.

It was as if the entire axis were about to collapse!

Han Li hurriedly tried to stabilize the axis upon seeing this, but he quickly discovered that a burst of suction force had emerged in the axis out of nowhere, and it was rapidly drawing upon his immortal spiritual power.

This was a rather concerning turn of events, but Han Li didn't dare to stop as he could sense that the Mantra Treasured Axis was slowly being stabilized by the influx of his immortal spiritual power.

Around 15 minutes passed by, during which over two thirds of Han Li's immortal spiritual power had been depleted, and the tremors in the axis finally ceased, while the green light on its surface had also faded.

It seemed that the Eye of Truth had been forcibly shut.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief, and after verifying that the axis and the Eye of Truth were unscathed, he withdrew the axis into his body with a hint of lingering fear in his eyes. He then carefully examined the Heavenly Controlling Vial and was quite relieved to find that it was also unharmed.

"Looks like I've been underestimating you all this time. You're completely fine, whereas the majority of immortal spiritual power has been depleted. I should continue to conduct these experiments once I've further enhanced the Eye of Truth," Han Li murmured to himself with a wry smile.

After that, he stowed the Heaven Controlling Vial away, then sat down with his legs crossed and closed his eyes. At the same time, the image of the stone monument in the secret area sprang into his mind, particularly the section with the third level of the Mantra Axis Scripture inscribed upon it.

At this point, he was already extremely familiar with the first level of the cultivation art, so he was focusing solely on examining the second and third levels with his spiritual sense, trying to see if those two parts contained any information pertaining to the Eye of Truth.

He sat for seven days and seven nights, carefully reading through both of the latter parts of the cultivation art during this time.

However, in the end, he was unable to find anything. Aside from the records of the Eye of Truth secret technique, there was no further content regarding the Eye of Truth in the rest of the cultivation art.

Han Li slowly opened his eyes and stretched lazily as he rose to his feet.

Even though he hadn't found what he was looking for, he wasn't disappointed in the slightest. Instead, there was a hint of elation in his eyes.

This was because during the reading process, he had summoned the Mantra Treasured Axis on multiple occasions for reference, and he discovered that the 25th Time Dao Rune still remained without displaying any signs of fading away. It appeared to have been just as permanent as the 24 other Time Dao Runes.

Furthermore, he could sense that the flow of time in the area encompassed within the golden ripples had slowed down a little further. It wasn't a significant change, but a noticeable one, nonetheless.

This meant that the Time Dao Rune that had arisen after the Eye of Truth absorbed the crystal manifested by the Heaven Controlling Vial was most likely permanent, but further observation would be required to confirm this.

In any case, Han Li was very excited by this discovery.

Aside from that, he had also made another encouraging discovery while inspecting the third level of the cultivation art.

Attached to the mantra of the third level of the cultivation art was an ability called the Reversal True Axis, and this was an ability that had the completely opposite effect to the Mantra Treasured Axis, accelerating the flow of time rather than slowing it down.

However, this ability only applied to its user. According to the description of the ability, it required one to keep the Mantra Treasured Axis in their body and reverse it, thereby accelerating the flow of time for them and enhancing their speed.

There was a prerequisite to cultivating this ability as well, which was that one had to have manifested at least 18 Time Dao Runes on their Mantra Treasured Axis, and it had nothing to do with which level of the Mantra Treasured Axis that one had progressed to.

However, according to the description in the Mantra Axis Scripture, only after mastering the third level of the cultivation art was it possible for one to attain 18 Time Dao Runes, which meant that it should've been impossible to cultivate this ability at any point before that.

However, Han Li had already attained 25 Time Dao Runes, so theoretically speaking, he should've been able to attempt cultivating this ability.

His original plan was to go into seclusion to cultivate the second level of the Mantra Axis Scripture, but he decided to set that plan aside for now to focus on cultivating this ability instead.

If he could master this ability, then his combat prowess would immediately receive a significant boost.

With that in mind, Han Li sat down with his legs crossed once again before closing his eyes.

After taking several days to prime himself into the best possible condition, Han Li commenced his seclusion.

The Reversal True Axis appeared to have been quite a simple ability, but it was actually far from easy to cultivate.

It was the complete opposite of how one would normally use the Mantra Axis Scripture, so not only were all of the insights that had developed through cultivating the Mantra Axis Scripture completely useless, they were serving as obstacles to a certain extent.

Inside the secret chamber, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed while making a hand seal with both hands, and the Mantra Treasured Axis behind him was slowly revolving while releasing faint golden light. 18 of the Time Dao Runes on its surface had lit up in unison, and they were releasing bursts of peculiar fluctuations throughout the entire secret chamber.

Right at this moment, Han Li brought his palms together, then folded down two his fingers before turning both hands toward to make a strange hand seal while also chanting an incantation.

The Mantra Treasured Axis behind him shuddered slightly, and the buzzing sound that it was emitting gradually subsided. The speed of its rotation was also gradually decreasing, and it looked as if it were going to stop revolving altogether.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li switched to yet another different hand seal, and the Mantra Treasured Axis instantly began spinning rapidly once again, except in the complete opposite direction to before.

Han Li was quite elated to see this, and he was just about to attempt to withdraw the axis into his body when he felt some tightness in his chest, following which blood began to gush up toward the back of his throat.

He immediately stopped what he was doing, and the Mantra Treasured Axis reverted back to its original state before vanishing into his body on its own.

As expected, it's not that easy. Just the method of immortal spiritual power circulation alone is quite difficult to grasp. It appears I won't be able to successfully cultivate this ability without at least several hundred attempts while making adjustments along the way.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face as he wiped away the blood that was trickling down from the corner of his lips.

Just now, the immortal spiritual power had begun to circulate in opposite directions, thereby clashing against itself, and if he had continued in that fashion, he would've been sure to sustain internal injuries.

After taking a moment to rest and adjust the circulation of immortal spiritual power in his body, Han Li summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis once again.

Chapter 273: Shock

Three years later.

A streak of blurry golden light was flashing back and forth through the air within a valley in the Crimson Dawn Peak's territory. It was flying at an incredible speed, leaving trails of afterimages in its wake, and it was impossible to follow with the naked eye.

What was even more peculiar was that there was no rhyme or reason to the streak of golden light's movements. One moment, it would be whizzing directly forward, only to appear in the opposite direction the next instant.

All of a sudden, the streak of golden light drew to an abrupt halt, and Han Li was revealed.

At this moment, his face was slightly flushed, and there was an irrepressible look of joy in his eyes. His entire body was enveloped in a layer of faint golden light that was giving off bursts of strange fluctuations, and he murmured to himself, "If I activate all 25 Time Dao Runes at once, my speed is indeed enhanced. It looks like as I attain more and more Time Dao Runes, this ability will only be enhanced further. Having said that, it is also extremely taxing on my immortal spiritual power..."

The layer of golden light around him then began to gradually fade, but instead of disintegrating, it vanished into his body instead.

As it turned out, that layer of golden light had come from the Mantra Treasured Axis in his body.

During the first year or so in which he had been cultivating this ability, he wasn't even able to circulate his immortal spiritual power in the correct fashion, and that proved to have been a very difficult hurdle to overcome.

There were instances in the past where there had been a mountain no larger than the size of a grain of rice from his perspective, but after activating the cultivation art, he would reach the mountain in the blink of an eye and crash headfirst into it in an uncontrolled manner.

During this period of time, he had inadvertently smashed through several hundred mountains, severely ravaging the surrounding scenery in a radius of several thousand kilometers while also sustaining some minor injuries in the process.

Thankfully, this area was part of his territory, so there weren't any problems.

The silver lining on the dark cloud was that fundamentally speaking, this ability wasn't actually completely opposite to the original cultivation art. Instead, the two shared some similarities, so after failing over 100 times, Han Li was gradually able to master the process of reversing the axis before drawing it into his own body.

At this point, he had become so skilled at this process that he didn't even need to summon the Mantra Treasured Axis at all. Instead, he could reverse it while it was still in his body, thereby significantly enhancing how quickly he was able to unleash the ability, as well as making it much more covert.

Additionally, he was very excited by the fact that the 25th Time Dao Rune had remained all this time without displaying any signs of fading away.

With this ability up his sleeve in conjunction with his lightning teleportation array, he was confident that he would be able to escape even in the face of the average Golden Immortal.

I've spent a very long time mastering this cultivation art. It's time to move onto something else.

With that in mind, Han Li descended toward his cave abode down below.

Before long, he had reappeared in his secret chamber, and he sat down with his legs crossed, then summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis before opening its Eye of Truth.

Sitting on the palm of his hand was a small semi-transparent crystal, which was being basked in the golden light released by the Eye of Truth.

In order to focus on mastering the Reversal True Axis, all of the spirit liquid produced by the Heaven Controlling Vial during the past three years had been used to water spirit plants by Han Li's puppet, so he had only recently taken the time to manifest another crystal.

A faint crack rang out, and the golden thread flew out from within before shooting into the Eye of Truth.

Han Li's entire body shuddered violently as if he had been dealt a heavy blow, but this time, instead of closing the Eye of Truth, he allowed the golden thread to fuse into it.

Moments later, a 26th Time Dao Rune appeared on his Mantra Treasured Axis amid a flash of white light.

A relieved smile appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, and it was finally confirmed to him that the Eye of Truth could indeed add Time Dao Runes to his Mantra Treasured Axis by absorbing these crystals.

This meant that as long as he manifested a crystal each month, he would be able to attain a new Time Dao Rune every single month!

For the average immortal, the Mantra Axis Scripture was extremely difficult to cultivate, and it was often the case that two immortal acupoints had to be opened to attain a single Time Dao Rune, yet through this method, it would only take him a single month to attain each new Time Dao Rune, and there didn't appear to have been any upper limit to this!

24 Time Dao Runes were enough to slow time down to less than a 10th of its original speed, and with each cluster of six Time Dao Runes attained, this slowing effect would be noticeably enhanced, so what would happen once he attained 30 Time Dao Runes, 36, or even 60 or 108?

As long as he continued to cultivate the second level of the Mantra Axis Scripture while manifesting crystals every month, it wouldn't take long at all before he got there!

Han Li suppressed the excitement in his heart as he switched to a different hand seal and closed his Eye of Truth.

After that, he closed his eyes as well and began to chant an incantation, commencing his cultivation of the second level of the Mantra Axis Scripture.

……

10 years passed by in the blink of an eye.

During this time, Han Li had been cultivating the second level of the Mantra Axis Scripture while manifesting crystals for the Eye of Truth to absorb, and at this point, the number of Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis had already increased to 108.

For some reason, the number of Time Dao Runes refused to increase further from that point, and it appeared that some type of limit had been reached.

However, Han Li wasn't overly disappointed by this. After all, according to the Mantra Axis Scripture, even mastering the third level of the cultivation art should've only given rise to 18 Time Dao Runes, and up to this point, no one in the Blaze Dragon Dao had been able to accomplish that.

Compared with before, the Mantra Treasured Axis's effective range hadn't changed, but it was capable of slowing down the flow time within its effective area to an astonishing degree of less than one thousandth of its normal speed.

He had experimented by instructing a puppet of his to attack him, and as soon as its attack entered the effective area of the Mantra Treasured Axis, it was slowed down to the point that it appeared to have fallen completely still.

Additionally, the speed enhancement effect of his Reversal True Axis had also reached an extraordinary level, allowing him to fly through the air like a shooting star in a completely untraceable fashion.

However, activating either of the aforementioned abilities to their full extent was incredibly taxing on his immortal spiritual power, and his current immortal spiritual power reserves weren't able to support such an astonishing level of expenditure for long at all, so he was only going to use these abilities against extremely formidable opponents.

At this moment, his entire secret chamber was filled with dazzling golden radiance.

Han Li made a hand seal, and the Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him with all 108 of the Time Dao Runes on its surface radiating golden light, basking his entire body in a golden glow that made him resemble a Buddha statue.

As the Time Dao Runes lit up one after another, the Mantra Treasured Axis also began to slowly revolve, and all 108 Time Dao Runes had lit up within the span of just a few seconds.

Han Li's complexion had paled slightly, and he could sense his immortal spiritual power being rapidly expended, but he was already prepared for this, and he flipped both hands over to produce a pair of Immortal Origin Stones to replenish his energy.

He then began to chant an incantation, and the axis turned into a complete blur, while a series of golden threads emerged from its surface before converging toward the hole at its center.

These golden threads then intertwined to form a fist-sized golden ball that was flashing incessantly with golden light.

Immediately thereafter, the golden light radiating from the ball of golden threads brightened significantly, and it transformed into the Eye of Truth.

A beam of faint golden light was projected out of the Eye of Truth, and Han Li closed his eyes to inspect his surroundings through the Eye of Truth.

All of the restrictions that he had set up on the surrounding walls were instantly revealed in a transparent state, and there were countless spiritual power runes surging over them. Han Li could see all of the minute changes taking place in the restrictions as clearly as the back of his own hand.

The space up ahead had also turned into a vast expanse of murky grayness, and Meng Yungui, Meng Qianqian, and the others were all gradually revealed alongside the scenery outside the Crimson Dawn Peak.

It seemed that the Eye of Truth was able to peer directly through space itself, and Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon seeing this

The ability of the Eye of Truth to see through illusions wasn't much different from that of his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, but after the number of Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis had increased to 108, the Eye of Truth had become significantly more powerful, able to observe far more than his Brightsight Spirit Eyes.

He had an ability that could combine his Law Destruction Eye and his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, but even that was now severely lacking compared with his Eye of Truth.

Han Li gently exhaled as a solemn look appeared on his face, and he flipped a hand over to summon his Heaven Controlling Vial.

Right as he was about to observe the vial with his Eye of Truth, an unexpected turn of events suddenly unfolded.

The vial flew out of his hand before hovering mid-air, and dazzling light began to radiate from its surface, making it resemble a tiny green sun.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of tremendous force surged out of the green light, and Han Li was caught completely off guard, flying back involuntarily through the air until his back struck the wall behind him.

A surprised look appeared on his face, and before he had a chance to do anything, his Mantra Treasured Axis flew over to the Heaven Controlling Vial while radiating dazzling golden light that was several times brighter than normal.

In particular, the Eye of Truth was glowing extremely bright, and the circle of runes around the pupil were all squirming rapidly as if they had sprung to life.

It was as if the two were resonating with one another.

Han Li hurriedly set down the pair of Immortal Origin Stones in his hands so that he could make a hand seal, but to his surprise, both the Heaven Controlling Vial and the Mantra True Axis were no longer under his control.

All of a sudden, the Eye of Truth shot a beam of golden light into the Heaven Controlling Vial, and the vial began to rapidly swell in size, reaching the size of a human head in the blink of an eye.

Countless green runes then appeared on the surface of the vial, and they resembled countless swimming tadpoles.

A thick pillar of green light shot out of the vial, then tore through the space up ahead before vanishing into it.

Instead of closing over, the torn space began to warp violently, resembling a large black mouth that convulsing incessantly.

In the next instant, a vast expanse of light erupted out of the spatial rift.

The light was very radiant, but not blindingly so, and it was flowing out of the spatial rift like a gentle stream of water.

At this point, Han Li had already risen to his feet and was observing the scene unfolding before him with a bewildered expression, unsure of whether this was going to spell fortune or disaster.

Even though the Mantra Treasured Axis was currently out of his control, he could still make it disappear by cutting off the immortal spiritual power flowing out of his body, but he wasn't sure if he wanted to do that.

Right as Han Li was hesitating about how to proceed, the situation took another turn.

Chapter 274: Lecture From the Big-eared Monk

All of a sudden, the spatial rift began to tremble violently before extending toward both the left and the right, forming an opening that was constantly growing wider.

As the opening continued to expand, more and more light came surging out of it like turbulent waves of the sea, and a translucent wall of light that was around 50 to 60 feet in size took shape in front of Han Li.

The Mantra Treasured Axis brightened even further while beginning to rapidly revolve, and the Time Dao Runes on its surface were also trembling violently, causing the nearby space to twist and warp.

An indecisive look appeared on Han Li's face at the sight of the unfolding phenomenon, but in the end, he decided to wait and observe for now.

There were countless specks of light that were surging incessantly over the wall of light, and the things depicted on its surface were rapidly changing.

Initially, everything was flashing extremely quickly, and it was impossible to make out exactly what was being depicted on the wall of light, but it didn't take long before the image began to stabilize, forming a few concrete outlines.

Han Li was able to tell from these outlines that he seemed to have been looking at a group of people.

Right at this moment, a dull fizzling sound rang out, and one of the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis quickly dimmed before turning a dull gray color.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this.

Even though the axis was currently out of his control, his spiritual connection with it was still intact,and just now, he could feel that his connection to that gray Time Dao Rune had been severed.

It felt like some type of mysterious power had sucked something out of his body, leaving him with a sense of emptiness, and this was something that had never happened before.

However, instead of immediately withdrawing the Mantra Treasured Axis, he forced himself to remain calm and continue observing as he had a feeling that there was something special about this wall of light.

With the dimming of that Time Dao Rune, the scene depicted on the wall of light gradually became a little clearer, and it seemed to have been depicting a mountaintop with a large object at the center, surrounded by several blurry figures of different statures.

Furthermore, there were also some colorful things flashing over the sky above.

Right as Han Li was about to activate his Brightsight Spirit Eyes to take a closer look, a dull fizzling sound rang out once again, and another one of the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis turned gray.

Han Li's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, but a contemplative look had also appeared in his eyes.

Immediately thereafter, one more Time Dao Rune turned dark.

It seemed that the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis were progressively dimming at set intervals, and an enlightened look appeared in his eyes as he hurriedly turned his gaze back to the wall of light.

Sure enough, with the dimming of those two Time Dao Runes, the image on the wall of light had become clearer once again.

After around five or six more Time Dao Runes turned gray, Han Li discovered that he was able to make out a mountain summit with a forest of lush trees around a strange rock.

The mountain summit was enshrouded within a boundless sea of clouds, and at the center of the scene was a round stone platform that was around 10,000 feet in radius and roughly 1,000 feet tall.

The platform had an azure coloration, and it was connected to the mountain below it, appearing to have been a naturally formed structure.

There were several cracks on the surface of the stone platform, and it was covered in moss and vines, indicating that it was a very old structure.

At this moment, there were five or six figures spread around the stone platform, and all of them were extremely strange in appearance.

One of them was very tall, but he was as thin as a bamboo stick, and he was wearing an extremely loose-fitting yellow robe that draped down all around him.

Additionally, his hair resembled a mop of withered yellow wheat, and his face was also extremely yellow and uneven, riddled with pockmarks like the bark of an old tree, as was the case with the skin on his hands, and he resembled a being from the Wood Tribe of the Spirit Realm.

Beside him was a very short figure that was no more than five foot tall, and he was also very thin and. Compared with the extraordinarily tall man beside him, he resembled a small child, yet his head was as large as a water vat, making him appear extremely unbalanced, as if he could fall flat on his face at any moment.

The third person had a set of remarkably long arms and legs, as well as huge hands and feet the size of banana leaves. The skin of his bared upper body was a fiery red color, as if he had been roasted, and there were circles of extremely strange patterns inscribed upon his skin. There was also a tuft of fiery red hair on the top of his head, with tiny flames springing out occasionally from within.

The fourth person was a child that appeared to have been around five or six years of age. He had a round body and a round head, resembling a small ball stacked onto a larger ball. He was wearing a dudou, as one would expect of an ordinary child, but his arms were twice the length of the average person's, hanging down to his knees, and they also each had an extra joint, giving them an extremely strange appearance.

The final person was enormous in stature, several times larger than everyone else, and he was wearing some type of demon beasthide garment. His skin was a dark green color, and he stood like a metal tower on the mountaintop.

None of these strange beings appeared to have been humans, yet their facial features somehow resembled human ones.

The five of them formed a circle with several thousand feet separating each of them, and they were either standing, sitting, or kneeling on the ground, while their eyes were collectively focused on a portly red-robed monk seated with his legs crossed at the center of the platform.

The folds of fat on the monk's face compressed his eyes to a pair of tiny slits, and his earlobes were so long that they draped all the way down to his shoulders. Below his head was an extremely rotund body, to the point that his already extremely large red kasaya robe wasn't even able to cover it entirely. As a result, his enormous belly was exposed, and it hung all the way down onto the ground, making him resemble a mountain of flesh.

At first glance, a strange thought sprang into Han Li's mind.

Is this person able to walk or even stand up?

However, that thought only flashed through his mind for a moment before he spotted several interesting details about the rotund monk.

Firstly, the kasaya robe that he was wearing was no ordinary garment. There were many gemstones of different colors attached to it, all of which were glowing brightly. Furthermore, he was holding a string of jade prayer beads, and all of the beads were glittering and translucent in appearance, releasing a faint azure glow that disoriented the senses, while runes could be seen dancing inside the beads.

As for the monk himself, while it was true that he was extraordinarily fat, his entire body was giving off a faint sheen, and it was as if he were the center of the entire world.

The monk's lips were moving, and he seemed to have been speaking.

However, instead of sounds, a string of five-colored runes was flowing out from between his lips, forming a stream of five-colored light that spread through the surrounding area before rising up into the air and disintegrating, seemingly resonating with heaven and earth.

Countless specks of light emerged from the stream of light before transforming into gusts of fierce wind that formed several massive tornadoes.

However, these tornados would instantly fade away as soon as they took shape, transforming into a storm of fire that came raining down from the heavens.

Before the rain of fire had a chance to descend onto the ground, it transformed into a storm of ice that froze the surrounding air...

All of these phenomena were extremely life-like, but every single one of them would vanish as soon as they appeared, causing the nearby space to tremble incessantly, while the sea of clouds surged and churned.

Han Li was very much intrigued by what he was seeing.

He noticed that regardless of what phenomena were being conjured up, the stone platform and the environment around it remained completely unaffected, and even the leaves on the surrounding trees remained completely still.

At the same time, there were countless golden lotus flowers blooming behind the portly monk's head, forming a huge golden cloud that was extremely profound in appearance.

As the cloud gently swayed from side to side, ripples that were visible even to the naked eye could be seen surging through the space around it.

The strange-looking figures around the stone platform paid no heed to the phenomena taking place up above, and they continued to stare intently at the portly monk, listening to him speak in a completely enraptured state.

After speaking for a while, the portly monk paused for a moment, and the streak of five-colored light surging through the air faded alongside all of the phenomena.

The trembling space and the churning sea of clouds gradually settled down as well, and the tall yellow-robed figure suddenly rose to his feet before extending a salute toward the monk.

The monk and the other figures all turned to him, and the yellow-robed figure began to speak while making a series of hand gestures, seemingly raising a question to the monk.

All of the other figures were nodding along unconsciously as they listened to him speak, as if they shared the same question, and all of them then turned to the portly monk with expectant expressions.

The portly monk threw his head back and burst into laughter upon hearing the yellow-robed figure's question, causing all of the flabby rolls over his body to tremble with mirth.

The space around the mountain also began to rumble with the portly monk's laughter, while the sea of louds churned and the mountain trembled.

A stunned look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this. Who exactly was this portly monk to be able to affect the environment around him so severely with just his laughter alone?

After his laughter subsided, the portly monk began to speak again while making a series of gestures with his rotund hands, seemingly answering the yellow-robed man's question.

An enlightened look appeared on the yellow-robed man's face as he listened to the portly monk's answer, and he extended a respectful bow to the monk before sitting down again.

Everyone else was enlightened by the answer provided, and they all bowed to the portly monk as well before sitting back down.

The portly monk lowered his hands as he continued his lecture, and the five figures around him began to listen intently with enraptured looks on their faces.

Looking at the intoxicated expressions on everyone's faces, Han Li was suddenly overcome by a strong desire to hear what the monk was saying. However, even the image displayed on the wall of light had become countless times clearer than before, he was unable to hear anything at all, so he could only look on in dismay.

Chapter 275: The Price of Eavesdropping

As time passed, the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis continued to fade one after another, while the image being depicted on the wall of light became more and more stable.

To Han Li's elation, as the image stabilized, he began to be able to hear some sound from the wall of light, but it was very muffled and staggered, making it impossible for him to make out what was being said.

During this time, the portly monk said some other things, and just like before, a stream of five-colored runes surged out of his mouth as he spoke. These runes rose up into the air before transforming into a five-colored stream of light, which then transformed into a series of strange-looking plants and ferocious beasts that Han Li had never seen before, presenting a kaleidoscope of fascinating sights to behold.

The five figures seated around the stone platform occasionally raised some questions before sitting back down with enlightened expressions after hearing the monk's answers.

Han Li was becoming really agitated about not being able to hear what was being said, but he could only force himself to remain calm. As opposed to being concerned about the rate at which the Time Dao Runes were fading, he was now beginning to hope that they would dim faster.

A short while later, the image on the wall of light was finally completely stabilized, and the sound coming from the image became a little louder.

It was still rather muffled and unclear, but Han Li was able to make out some of the things that were being said.

Han Li immediately flew over to the wall of light until he was no more than a foot away from it, then sat down with his legs crossed before making a hand seal. All of the immortal spiritual power in his body was injected into his ears at his behest, and he activated an auditory enhancement ability that he had learned by chance in the past before listening intently to the sound coming from the image.

Thanks to this ability, the sound coming from the wall of light instantly became clearer.

The monk's voice was warm and ethereal, striking the listener with a sense of awe and veneration, and even though he was speaking in an unfamiliar language, Han Li's eyes quickly lit up as he listened to the monk's lecture.

He couldn't understand what was being said, but just hearing the voice of the monk alone was giving him an extremely profound sensation, as if he had attained some type of enlightenment, but he couldn't tell exactly what he had been enlightened to.

Even so, he was still feeling ecstatic, and he carefully memorized everything that he was hearing.

After only listening to a single sentence, lights of all types of different colors, including gold, azure, and silver, emerged from his body one after another. All of the cultivation arts and abilities in his body were being activated by the monk's voice!

Han Li was astonished by this turn of events, and he began to listen even more intently.

He still couldn't understand what was being said, but the same enraptured look on the faces of the five figures in the image had appeared on his face as well.

As time passed, the lights flashing from his body were becoming brighter and brighter, and arcs of silver lightning emerged alongside a projection of a Lightning Bird.

A projection of a giant azure bird emerged within a flash of azure light.

A giant golden ape then appeared amid a flash of golden light, pounding its chest as it roared to the heavens.

One true spirit projection after another emerged from his body, and in the blink of an eye, all of Han Li's current true spirit forms had appeared around him before revolving around his body.

The same applied to all of his other cultivation arts as well, and the circulation of immortal spiritual power in his body was becoming faster and more forceful by the second.

Right after the portly monk uttered his eighth sentence, a completely inexplicable turn of events began to unfold.

Han Li's entire body shuddered, immediately following which he was struck by a numb sensation. His dantian had also become scorching hot, but it was a very warm and comfortable sensation.

In the next instant, a clear thud rang out from within his body, and Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, following which an elated look appeared in his eyes.

Before he had a chance to do anything, seven more thuds rang out in succession within his body.

In the next instant, eight specks of light emerged on his body, and they were identical to the 12 existing ones.

He had just opened eight immortal acupoints in one go!

Immediately thereafter, he felt the surrounding world's origin qi surging toward him in a frenzy, forming an enormous vortex of spiritual qi, and the immortal spiritual power in his dantian was rapidly elevating!

Han Li was ecstatic to sense these changes in his body, and he took a glance at the Mantra Treasured Axis in the air to find that over half of the 108 Time Dao Runes had already been snuffed out.

He still had some time left, and he was determined to take full advantage of it. Hence, he continued to listen intently to the portly monk's ninth sentence.

The eight sentences that he had heard up to this point had allowed him to open up eight immortal acupoints, and he felt as if he were in a dream.

He couldn't help but wonder what was going to happen upon hearing the ninth and tenth sentences, and his heart was brimming with excitement.

However, it seemed that his luck had finally run out.

The portly monk was halfway through his ninth sentence, and Han Li could sense that his ninth immortal acupoint was beginning to budge, but all of a sudden, the portly monk stopped talking as he turned to Han Li's direction with a surprised look on his face.

The other five figures also turned to the same direction, and the tall yellow-robed figure instantly rose to his feet before yelling something in an enraged voice. He was speaking in the same language as the portly monk, but his words didn't seem profound to Han Li in the slightest.

The other four figures exchanged a few glances with different looks on their faces, and they remained silent, but it was clear that they weren't very happy.

I've been caught!

Han Li's heart instantly tensed up in anxiety, but before he had a chance to do anything, the portly monk suddenly said something, and the wall of light exploded into countless specks of light that quickly faded away.

The spatial rift was also instantly closed, while the Mantra Treasured Axis flashed erratically with golden light, and all of the Time Dao Runes that remained lit were instantly snuffed out amid a string of faint cracks.

Han Li's entire body shuddered as he threw up a mouthful of blood, and his face instantly turned extremely pale, while the immortal spiritual power in his body was thrown into complete disarray,surging chaotically in all directions.

An alarmed look appeared on his face as he hurriedly summoned a white pill vial, within which was a batch of white pills, and he didn't have time to count them before tipping them all into his own mouth and swallowing them. After that, he immediately closed his eyes to digest the pills.

A string of dull thumps rang out incessantly from within his body, while lights of different colors flashed over his body, clashing and conflicting with one another.

One moment, the azure light suppressed all of the other lights, but in the next instant, the golden light overwhelmed the azure light, following which the silver lightning rose to the fore.

Han Li's face was also alternating rapidly between purple and blue, presenting a harrowing sight to behold.

However, as time slowly passed by, the lights surging over his body gradually faded, and his complexion slowly returned to normal as well.

Only after close to a day had passed did he slowly open his eyes, and his face was still rather pale, but his aura had already stabilized.

Fortunately, he had reacted very quickly, devouring those meridian stabilization pills in a timely fashion. Otherwise, he would've most likely suffered from qi deviation.

Han Li gently exhaled, and an elated look reappeared on his face as he felt the eight newly opened immortal acupoints in his body.

Even though the situation just now had been an extremely perilous one, he had also reaped tremendous rewards, opening up eight immortal acupoints just by hearing the portly monk's lecture through the wall of light.

The ninth acupoint wasn't completely opened, but it was already beginning to budge, and he was certain that he would be able to open it given some time.

Due to the fact that he had focused primarily on attaining additional Time Dao Runes during the past 10 years of cultivation, he hadn't been able to open any new immortal acupoints, yet he had managed to open eight in what was virtually the blink of an eye!

Perhaps it was because these breakthroughs hadn't been attained through cultivating the Mantra Axis Scripture, or perhaps it was because there were already 108 Time Dao Runes on the axis. In any case, he hadn't attained any additional Time Dao Runes as a result of these breakthroughs.

He was naturally ecstatic to have made such significant progress in such a short time, but what excited him the most was the eight and half sentences that he had heard from the portly monk.

The more he thought back to those eight and half sentences, the more profound and unfathomable he felt them to be, and it seemed to him like they were part of the mantra for a certain cultivation art.

To think that that monk was able to help me open up multiple acupoints just by speaking alone... Could it be that he's a Dao Ancestor?

Han Li sat down with his legs crossed as a contemplative look appeared on his face, but in the next instant, a thought suddenly occurred to him, and he hurriedly summoned his Mantra Treasured Axis amid a flash of golden light.

All 108 of the Time Dao Runes on the axis had become dull and gray, seemingly having lost all of their vitality.

It seems like this was both a blessing and a curse. In order to hear that monk's preaching, I've had to let all of my Time Dao Runes go dark.

Han Li heaved a faint sigh, then consumed a restorative pill before closing his eyes.

Three days and three nights later.

Han Li opened his eyes, and at this point, he had already fully recovered from his injuries, but as he turned to his Mantra Treasured Axis, he discovered that the 108 Time Dao Runes on its surface were still completely dark.

How could this be?

It suddenly occurred to him that that final glance from that portly monk may have harmed the foundation of the Mantra Treasured Axis.

With that in mind, he hurriedly tried to unleash the axis's time-slowing effect, but it was completely unresponsive.

He then tried to unleash his Reversal True Axis ability, but the outcome was identical, and a grim look appeared on his face.

The Mantra Axis Scripture was currently his main cultivation method, and if the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis had been permanently destroyed, then he wouldn't be able to cultivate the Mantra Axis Scripture any longer.

He shook his head and forcibly composed himself, then activated the Mantra Axis Scripture to try and sense the Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis.

Moments later, his eyes sprang open as a hint of elation appeared on his face.

It was very faint, but he could still sense some power of time within the Time Dao Runes, and his spiritual connection to them hadn't been severed, either.

This was quite a relief. As long as the spiritual connection still remained, there was a chance that the Time Dao Runes on the axis could be restored.

With that in mind, Han Li continued to cultivate the Mantra Axis Scripture, attempting to recover his Time Dao Runes while also pondering the eight and a half sentences that he had heard from the portly monk.

Chapter 276: Century-long Seclusion

A year flew by in the blink of an eye.

Inside his secret chamber, Han Li sat with his legs crossed, and his Mantra Treasured Axis was slowly revolving behind him while radiating dazzling golden light, and there were countless golden runes surging rapidly over its surface.

One of the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis suddenly began to flash, and all of the golden runes around it lit up before converging into the Time Dao Rune.

The dull Time Dao Rune immediately began to light up at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye, and after just a few seconds, it was restored to its former state, but the other Time Dao Runes were still a dull gray color.

Han Li opened his eyes, and he was overcome by a sense of relief at the sight of the recovered Dao Rune.

Just as he anticipated, it was possible to recover his Time Dao Runes, but it seemed that every single one of these Time Dao Runes was going to take around a year to recover, which meant that it was would take over a century to recover all 108 of the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis.

His cultivation was most likely going to be severely hampered during this time, but that couldn't be helped.

In any case, a century was nothing more than the blink of an eye to Han Li, and he could take this time to carefully ponder the eight-and-a-half-sentence mantra that he had heard.

During this past year, he wasn't able to make much progress in this endeavor, but he was becoming more and more confident that he would be able to glean some useful things from the mantra given sufficient time.

Additionally, he could also use this time to nurture some pill refinement ingredients.

With that in mind, he flipped a hand over to produce a jade box, which contained the six or seven pill recipes that he had obtained from Ping Yaozi. Two of those recipes were for pills that were fit for mid-True Immortal cultivators to consume, one of which was for the Growth Bearing Pill, while the other one was for a pill called the Jade Balance Pill.

After examining the ingredients on the pill recipes, he discovered that none of them were all that precious or rare, but they had to have been very advanced in age before they could be used in the recipes.

He had already spent the majority of the Immortal Origin Stones and spirit stones that he had saved up from completing Transient Guild missions on pill refinement, and even though he still had some left, it was nowhere near enough to purchase sufficient pill refinement ingredients for both recipes.

My priority is to restore my Time Dao Runes, so for now, I'll use the spirit liquid produced by the Heaven Controlling Vial to mature spirit plants instead of using them to manifest crystals.

Han Li's Mantra Treasured Axis had been severely affected by the event that had taken place a year ago, but his Heaven Controlling Vial hadn't been impacted at all, so he could still use it to mature spirit plants as usual.

With that in mind, Han Li rose to his feet and emerged from his secret chamber, then summoned a communication array plate before casting an incantation seal onto it.

Moments later, Meng Yungui and Sun Buzheng arrived in the main hall of the cave abode, then extended a collective salute toward Han Li, who was seated beside the stone table.

"We pay our respects to Elder Li!"

"I will be going into seclusion for some time. During this time, I need you two to go out and secure some ingredients for me. Here is a list of the ingredients I want."

Han Li handed each of them a jade slip that contained a list of ingredients from the two pill recipes as he spoke.

The two of them accepted the jade slips, then inspected its contents with their spiritual sense, upon which surprised looks appeared on both of their faces.

Most of the ingredients listed in the jade slip were very precious, and they weren't going to be easy to find.

"I know that the ingredients won't be easy to collect, but this is not an urgent matter, so take your time. All you need to do is find me a sufficient amount within the next century, and if you make any progress during that time, you can bring what you've collected back to me at any time."

Han Li pulled out a pair of storage pouches that were filled with spirit stones as he spoke.

The two servants were quite relieved to hear this, and they accepted the storage pouches before promptly departing.

Following their departure, Han Li also returned to his secret chamber.

Over 100 years passed by in the blink of an eye.

During this time, some events had taken place in the Bell Toll Mountain Range, and there were some new arrivals, while others had departed, but this was nothing out of the ordinary for the Bell Toll Mountain Range. As long as the 13 Golden Immortals of the sect were still present, the foundation of the sect would still be intact.

The Crimson Dawn Peak was quite a secluded place to begin with, and it was becoming more and more dormant. Additionally, Han Li always liked to keep a low profile, so everyone eventually forgot about him, and he barely received any visitors.

Of course, even if anyone did come to visit Han Li, they would discover that the Crimson Dawn Peak was closed to all visitors.

It was very common to see a True Immortal going into seclusion for centuries, and for some True Immortals who were attempting to make important breakthroughs, even seclusions that lasted thousands or tens of thousands of years were quite commonplace.

During his seclusion, Han Li barely left his cave abode at all, spending the majority of his time pondering the eight-and-a-half-sentence mantra that he had heard from the portly monk over and over again.

The only times that he would stop to take a break were when Sun Buzheng or Meng Yungui returned with seeds of certain ingredients listed on the two pill recipes, and Han Li would instruct his giant ape puppet to plant those seeds according to his needs.

Inside the secret chamber, the air had become stagnant, and even the tiny dust particles in the air seemed to have become completely still.

Han Li was seated with his legs crossed, and his Mantra Treasured Axis was slowly revolving behind him. All 108 of the Time Dao Runes on its surface had lit up, and they were giving off powerful law fluctuations.

Moments later, he withdrew his hand seal, and the Mantra Treasured Axis behind him vanished into his body amid a flash of golden light.

It was as if some type of restriction had suddenly been lifted, and speed of the air flow in the secret chamber returned to normal, while all of the dust particles also began to drift freely again.

"It's finally all recovered," Han Li murmured to himself, then rose to his feet and made his way out of his secret chamber.

The sky above the Crimson Dawn Peak was bright and clear, just like his current mood, and the sun was hanging high up in the sky, basking the snow-covered mountain in a warm glow.

Han Li emerged from his cave abode, then flew up into the air as a streak of azure light, intending to travel to the valley that he often frequented to test out the new abilities that he had gleaned from the eight-and-a-half-sentence mantra, but he noticed out of the corner of his eye that Meng Qianqian and few of his other servants were gathered on the spirit fields on the mountain.

Thus, he flew over to them before descending out of the sky, and the group of servants hurriedly extended respectful salutes upon spotting him.

Han Li waved a dismissive hand in response, then cast his gaze toward his mountain guardian beast up ahead.

Ever since he adopted this beast, he hadn't paid it much attention, mostly leaving it to be looked after by his servants, but to his surprise, it had reached the mid-Body Integration Stage.

However, what had caught his attention wasn't the Two-headed Griffin. Intead, it was the strange azure bird straddled atop one of its necks.

The bird had a huge head and a disproportionately slender neck. Its body was close to 20 feet in length and covered in countless arrow-like feathers, and there was a fleshy pouch that was over five feet in size hanging in front of its chest.

It was casually straddled atop the Two-headed Griffin, which was countless times more massive than itself, looking around like a proud general riding atop his noble steed.

However, the bird seemed to have been startled by Han Li's arrival, and it flapped its wings in alarm as a hint of fear flashed through its eyes.

Only after receiving a reassuring glance from Meng Qianqian did it settle down, but it was laying itself flat against the Two-headed Griffin's back while covering its head with its wings, peeking out at Han Li through its feathers.

"Is that Featheryearn?" Han Li asked as he turned to Meng Qianqian.

"That's right," Meng Qianqian replied with a smile.

"It's only been 100 years since I last saw it, and it's already close to the Nascent Soul Stage," Han Li remarked with an impressed look in his eyes.

"Indeed. Its appetite is absolutely enormous, and that probably has something to do with its fast progress. I haven't fed it any spirit plants or pills outside of the wind-attribute spirit plants from the fields, but it would occasionally sneak out of the Crimson Dawn Peak, and I don't know what it's been eating during its outings," Meng Qianqian said as she took a glance at Featheryearn.

Han Li pointed at the Two-headed Griffin, which was laying on the ground with a rather bored look on its faces, and he asked, "What's the deal with these two?"

"Featheryearn once snuck out of the Crimson Dawn Peak two years ago, and as it was coming back, it was being hunted by a Deity Transformation Stage demon beast. At the time, the mountain guardian beast swooped in to eat that demon beast and save Featheryearn, and the two of them seemed to have become friends after that," Meng Qianqian explained.

"I bet it went out to hunt for other demon beasts, but ended up biting off more than it could chew and almost became prey for something else instead," Han Li remarked with an amused smile. "By the way, have your brother and Sun Buzheng not returned yet?"

"They already came back seven or eight years ago, but both of them seemed to have encountered some opportunities during their outing, and not long after they came back, they went into seclusion to attempt breakthroughs to the Deity Transformation Stage.

“Both of them are still in seclusion right now, and all of the spirit plants they brought back have already been planted in the fields. Oh, I almost forgot, they also brought back these seeds as well," Meng Qianqian replied as she handed a storage pouch to Han Li.

Han Li accepted the storage pouches and inspected their contents with his spiritual sense. He then made his way over to the spirit fields and was quite pleased by what he saw.

Meng Yungui and Sun Buzheng had brought back a lot of seeds and spirit plants during their outings, enough for several dozen batches' worth of pill refinement ingredients.

This was not an easy task for them at their current cultivation bases, so it was clear that they had been very diligent.

"They did a good job. I may be going into seclusion after this, so they may not get to see me when they come out of seclusion. Here are two vials of pills for cultivation base stabilization, make sure to give these to them in my stead," Han Li said as he tossed a pair of pill vials to Meng Qianqian.

Meng Qianqian hurriedly caught the vials before extending a grateful curtsey toward Han Li as she said, "Thank you, Elder Li."

Han Li gave her a dismissive wave, then reached toward the spirit fields with azure light glowing from his hands.

The earth began to tremble slightly, and over 100 spirit plants of different colors were enveloped by azure light before being uprooted from the ground. There were still droplets of dew on their leaves and dirt clinging to their roots as they rose up into the air before flying toward his cave abode.

These spirit plants weren't of a sufficient age to be used, so they had to be transferred to the medicine garden in his cave abode to be matured using the spirit liquid from the Heaven Controlling Vial.

Chapter 277: Mantra Domain

An hour later, in the territory of the Crimson Dawn Peak.

A streak of azure light flew onto a plain that was riddled with scattered rocks, then faded to reveal Han Li.

This place was actually once a scenic valley, but while cultivating the Reversal True Axis a over a century ago, Han Li had inadvertently toppled all of the mountains on either side of the valley, thereby completely filling the valley to create this rocky plain.

Han Li was hovering in mid-air with a solemn look on his face, and there was a burst of peculiar fluctuations emanating from his body.

Right at this moment, a burst of golden light suddenly appeared in his eyes, and he released his vast spiritual sense to encompass the entire surrounding area in a radius of dozens of kilometers.

A circle of extremely tiny runes then appeared within his pupils, spelling out the mantra that he had heard from the portly monk, but not in its entirety. Instead, it was only three and a half sentences of the mantra.

These three and a half sentences were depicted in the form of runes, but not displayed in the order in which they had been uttered by the monk. One of the sentences had been completely scattered before having all of its characters rearranged, seemingly in a completely haphazard fashion.

It seemed that the meaning of the mantra wasn't all that important. Instead, what was important were these characters, which innately contained some type of special power. After studying them extensively, Han Li had been successfully able to integrate them with his tremendous spiritual sense to develop a unique ability that he named the Mantra Domain.

"Let there be wind," Han Li declared.

The complexion of the entire plain was instantly altered as dense dark clouds came drifting in out of nowhere to obscure the formerly bright and clear sky. As a result of the converging clouds, the entire sky instantly darkened.

A gust of fierce wind blew past, sweeping the snow on the plain into the heavens, and a vast expanse of yellow sand was also swept up by the wind, while huge rocks began to roll and tumble over the ground, crashing against one another to produce a string of resounding booms.

"Let there be lightning," Han Li called out, and the dark clouds in the sky were swept up into a frenzy to form a massive vortex.

Bursts of rumbling were ringing out incessantly deep within the vortex alongside flashes of blue lightning.

All of a sudden, a pillar of blue lightning that was as thick as a water vat came crashing down from the heavens before striking the ground, instantly causing the giant rocks down below to explode into a massive cloud of dust and rock shards.

Immediately thereafter, more pillars of lightning came raining down incessantly from the heavens amid rumbling thunderclaps, severely ravaging the entire plain.

The earth was charred black and littered with countless rock fragments, while arcs of blue lightning danced over its surface, and there was an acrid charred odor wafting through the air.

"Let heaven and earth be turned on their heads!" Han Li commanded, and the world around him instantly complied.

A burst of indescribably formidable power was unfurled, encompassing the entire surrounding area.

Han Li felt a blue flash before his eyes, and he was struck by a rush of dizziness. By the time he was able to see clearly again, he discovered a vast expanse of dark clouds that was rumbling incessantly with thunder beneath his feet.

He then looked up to find that a vast expanse of earth that stretched as far as the eyes could see in all directions had appeared above his head.

Up close, he could see countless scattered rocks, as well as a layer of dust that enshrouded the surface of the ground, while in the distance were a series of upside-down mountains that resembled enormous stalactites, the closest of which was none other than his Crimson Dawn Peak.

However, what was quite interesting was that despite the fact that everything had been flipped upside-down, none of it was displaying any signs of falling, not even the layer of dust that was hanging over the entire surface of the earth.

Han Li looked around for a long while before a smile appeared on his face, and he gently clapped his hands together, upon which heaven and earth were instantly restored to their correct configuration, and all of the dust, dark clouds, lightning, wind, and scattered rocks instantly vanished.

The entire area returned to normal in the blink of an eye, and it was as if nothing had ever happened.

The circle of runes in Han Li's eyes had also vanished, and his pupils had returned to their normal state.

That worked even better than I expected. Looks like I now have another trump card against formidable enemies in the future.

At its core, this Mantra Domain ability was actually just an extremely powerful illusory technique, but it didn't require any array or cultivation art to unleash.

All he had to do was spread his spiritual sense over an area around him, and he would be able to manipulate the entire area in any way that he saw fit, creating an illusion that he could trap his opponent in.

As long as his opponent didn't possess superior spiritual sense or any special treasures capable of counteracting illusions, they would inevitably be disrupted by this ability, but to varying extents.

If Han Li were facing an opponent of a similar level to himself, then this Mantra Domain could very well catch them completely off guard, and they would only have to reveal the slightest of openings for their defeat to be sealed.

Around 15 minutes later, Han Li returned to his cave abode.

Inside his secret chamber, he sat down with his legs crossed with a purple jade board sitting on his lap. There was a floral design that was comprised of countless extremely thin patterns engraved onto the surface of the jade board, presenting a beautiful sight to behold.

This was the jade board that he had found in Ping Yaozi's purple jade box, and he had been unable to bypass the spiritual sense restriction on it, so he had left it up to this point.

He had chosen to bring it out again on this day as all of the Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis had already recovered, so he was able to use his Eye of Truth again.

With all 108 Time Dao Runes activated, the Eye of Truth was currently already over 10 times more effective than his Brightsight Spirit Eyes when it came to seeing through illusions and restrictions.

Han Li made a hand seal with both hands, and his Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him amid a flash of golden light.

He then began to chant an incantation, and the Eye of Truth at the center of the Mantra Treasured Axis slowly opened before projecting a beam of golden light onto the purple jade board.

The floral design on the jade board also flashed with golden light before releasing a series of golden runes to obstruct the beam of light projected by the Eye of Truth.

However, the beam of light was able to bypass the runes with ease before shining down upon the jade board.

Instead of seeing the jade board with his eyes, he began to view it through his Eye of Truth.

Golden light was rippling like water on the surface of the board, and the flower design was hovering above the rippling light.

However, Han Li was able to completely disregard it to see what was under the layer of rippling golden light.

It was like he was seeing through a golden river straight to the riverbed, where there was a fine layer of golden sand, upon which was a passage of golden seal text.

Han Li swept his gaze over the passage of text, and a hint of elation instantly welled up in his heart.

Just as he anticipated, the passage of golden text was none other than a recipe for a dao pill!

His heart was brimming with excitement, but his elation began to fade a little as he looked at all of the extremely unfamiliar ingredient names listed on the recipe. It was most likely going to be an extremely difficult task to gather all of these ingredients.

The main ingredient for the recipe, Lightning Pond Golden Elixir, was an extremely rare natural treasure, and there was only a chance for it to arise in the body of a Lightning Devouring Beast that was over 100,000 years of age after devouring a vast amount of Nine Heavens True Lightning.

It was also exactly because of this that this Lightning Pond Golden Elixir contained traces of lightning law powers.

It was no longer just a matter of time for spirit ingredients of this caliber to emerge. Instead, there were many more factors that had to align, and obtaining such ingredients was almost entirely a matter of luck.

However, Han Li had already anticipated that this would be the case, so he wasn't all that disheartened. Instead, this only bolstered his confidence in just how incredible the dao pill was going to be if he could successfully refine it.

He read through the list of ingredients, then turned his attention to the refinement method listed below, memorizing everything that he read. As he reached the final passage of text, a surprised look appeared on his face.

The passage read: "When it comes to the refinement of the dao pill, the supplementary ingredients form the foundation, determining the grade of the pill, while the primary ingredient serves as the catalyst, determining the attribute of the pill. As long as the foundation remains the same, the grade of the pill won't change, but the attribute of the pill hinges entirely on the primary ingredient used..."

An enlightened look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

This passage of text was telling him that in all dao pill recipes, the supplementary ingredients could remain the same, but the attribute of the pill could be altered depending on the primary ingredient used.

In other words, if he were to replace the Lightning Pond Golden Elixir in the recipe with heavy water, which contained water law powers, then he would be able to refine a water-attribute dao pill. while a time-attribute dao pill would arise if he used a crystal manifested by the Heaven Controlling Vial as the primary ingredient.

However, the second half of that passage also stated that ingredient compatibility was an important factor to consider in pill refinement, so if one were to use a different primary ingredient, they would still be able to refine a dao pill, but the chances of success could vary drastically.

However, Han Li wasn't too fazed by this. He had been trying to glean the laws of time through the Mantra Treasured Axis, but hadn't been able to make any progress. Hence, it was already enough for him to know that this pill recipe could allow him to refine a time-attribute dao pill.

He suppressed the elation in his heart as he withdrew his Mantra Treasured Axis into his body, then stowed the jade board away as well before flipping a hand over to produce his Transient Guild mask, which he promptly put on.

All of the spirit medicines listed on the pill recipe were extremely difficult to find, and he wasn't going to be able to gather everything in a short time. Hence, he decided to conduct a search through the Transient Guild first, and if he could find some of the required ingredients, that would naturally be ideal, but if not, then he would just have to release some missions to search for them.

At this point, he had already spent virtually all of his spirit stones, and he did have some Immortal Origin Stones left, but not a whole lot, either. Hence, he didn't have very high requirements for the spirit medicines. As long as the species was correct, he was willing to purchase even seeds.

A burst of azure light was projected from the mask, forming a massive array plate on the wall, and Han Li immediately focused his gaze on the exchange column...

Several days later, several new spirit medicines had appeared in the spirit medicine garden in Han Li's cave abode. Most of them were seedlings that were no more than 10 years of age, while the two exceptions were seeds that were still yet to germinate.

Chapter 278: Reversal

Half a day later.

Han Li's secret chamber was filled with bright golden light, and he was standing beside his cushion with a rather tense look on his face.

His Mantra Treasured Axis was rapidly revolving behind him while glowing radiantly, and the Eye of Truth at its center was opened while projecting a beam of golden light forward.

Now that all of the Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasure Axis had recovered, he had naturally thought of the portly monk that he had seen in that wall of light again.

Even though the portly monk seemed to have caught him eavesdropping last time, surely there was no way that he could attack Han Li through the projection, even with his unfathomable power.

With that in mind, Han Li took a deep breath, then pulled out his Heaven Controlling Vial before placing it into the beam of golden light.

As soon as the golden light came into contact with the vial, the latter immediately rose up into the air on its own, radiating dazzling green light while releasing a burst of tremendous force.

This time, Han Li was prepared, and he crossed his arms in front of himself as a barrier. As a result, he was only blown back by about 10 feet before drawing to a halt.

All 108 of the Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis were glowing brightly, while the Heaven Controlling Vial was also shining like a green sun as it hovered in mid-air.

It didn't take long before a pillar of green light erupted out of the Heaven Controlling Vial to tear open a spatial rift.

A vast expanse of translucent light surged out of the spatial rift, and the same wall of light as before quickly appeared in front of Han Li.

The scene displayed on the wall of light was extremely blurry and completely silent, but Han Li was already prepared for this, so he naturally wasn't worried at all, waiting patiently as the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis were snuffed out one after another.

As the image became clearer and clearer, Han Li's breathing began to accelerate involuntarily.

However, after just a few seconds, a bewildered look appeared on Han Li's face.

The image depicted on the wall of light this time was completely different from last time.

On this occasion, he was greeted by the sight of a vast landscape that was riddled with massive volcanoes.

There was a dense blanket of inky-black clouds hanging in the sky, within which crimson light was flashing incessantly, while all of the enormous volcanoes down below were erupting with full force, releasing vast plumes of black smoke that were almost connected to the dark clouds up above.

Scorching red lava was surging out of the volcanic craters, forming a series of molten rivers that were over 1,000 feet wide. The molten rivers flowed in all directions before converging at the lowest point in the terrain to form a massive lake of lava.

Bursts of loud rumbling were ringing out from within the wall of light, and the entire landscape was quaking violently. A series of massive trenches were appearing in the earth like cobwebs before extending and widening to split the ground up into massive chunks.

Countless thick and burly worm-like beasts with red skin were constantly being flung to the surface by the churning earth before digging into the soil in a frenzy, attempting to return to their burrows beneath the earth.

There were too many of these creatures to count, and all of them were squirming desperately in an attempt to burrow themselves back into the earth, but they were being crushed by the rocks that were constantly tumbling down from above, splitting their bodies into countless chunks.

These creatures seemed to have possessed extraordinary vitality, and even after their bodies had been split apart, they were still attempting to burrow into the earth with resilience and tenacity.

However, the flow of lava had already seeped into all of the rifts in the earth, drowning all of these creatures and incinerating them into nothingness.

Han Li was rooted to the spot, staring at this doomsday-like scene with astonishment in his heart. His hands were clenched into tight fists, and his palms were sweating profusely.

Right at this moment, a dull thud suddenly rang out, and one of the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis shuddered before quickly fading into a dull gray color.

At this point, around half of the Time Dao Runes had already been snuffed out.

Han Li instantly snapped back to his senses and recalled his objective for conjuring up this wall of light in the first place.

However, the scene depicted in the wall of light was completely different from last time, and that had caught him off guard.

There's something that I've been meaning to try...

With that in mind, Han Li patted the spirit beast pouch on his waist, and a demonic wolf with strands of spittle hanging down from its mouth appeared out of thin air amid a flash of azure light.

As soon as the demonic wolf appeared, it immediately tried to escape, but Han Li was able to grab onto the scruff of its neck with ease before hurling it toward the wall of light.

The demonic wolf was writhing and twisting with all its might as it flew through the air, but it was unable to stop itself from crashing into the wall of light. Upon making contact with the wall of light, its body seemed to have passed through some type of invisible barrier, and it appeared on the other side.

As soon as it landed, it immediately turned around and lowered its center of gravity while snarling at Han Li with its fangs bared.

It worked!

Han Li was ecstatic to find that it really was possible to pass through the wall of light.

However, in the next instant, he noticed that the demonic wolf's fur was beginning to turn a lifeless gray color, and the light in its eyes was also rapidly fading.

Taking into account the demonic wolf's lifespan, it was as if it had aged close to 1,000 years in the blink of an eye.

Immediately thereafter, the pelt and flesh of the demonic wolf rotted away to reveal a complete skeleton, which was then reduced to ashes before being swept away by the wind.

Another dull thud rang out as one more Time Dao Rune on the Mantra Treasured Axis was snuffed out.

This time, Han Li didn't turn his gaze to the Mantra Treasured Axis. Instead, he was staring at the spot where the demonic wolf had just disappeared with a contemplative look on his face.

Moments later, he flipped a hand over to produce a palm-sized mirror that was azure on one side and red on the other.

This wasn't a particularly powerful treasure. Instead, it was only a low-grade treasure that was capable of releasing waves and flames. He couldn't even recall when he had obtained it, and he hadn't gotten around to selling it yet.

Just like with the demonic wolf, he tossed the mirror at the wall of light, and it was also able to pass through without any trouble.

Han Li immediately activated his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, trying to see through the wall of light to find out exactly what was happening.

He watched as the mirror reached the other side, and even before it landed on the ground, azure and red light began to radiate from its surface, as if it had been activated by someone and was about to unleash its waves and flames.

In the next instant, a quiet thud rang out, and the light radiating from the mirror flashed momentarily before the entire mirror exploded.

To Han Li's surprise, the mirror hadn't exploded into shards or pieces. Instead, it had disintegrated into a cloud of colorful mist that was rising up into the air before quickly converging to form around a dozen types of ore of different colors, all of which then fell toward the ground.

Han Li wasn't unfamiliar with these materials. Among them, the ones that could be seen in the largest quantities were the red Flame Spirit Rock and the azure Origin Water Rock.

These two types of ore were the primary materials for refining the mirror, while the other types of ore were all supplementary materials for refining the same treasure.

A hint of intrigue appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this, yet before he had a chance to do anything else, all of the chunks of ore quickly began to take on a transparent form before vanishing entirely.

At this point, over half of the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis had already faded.

After that, he continued his experiments, tossing things like spirit stones and even Immortal Origin Stones into the wall of light, and he discovered that as soon as those objects landed on the ground, they would quickly fuse as one with the earth, following which the spiritual power inside them faded away, and they were completely assimilated with the earth before also vanishing into thin air.

As time passed, the rate at which the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis were fading seemed to have been growing faster and faster.

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed as he stared at the wall of light and the doomsday-like scene displayed upon it. All of a sudden, he flipped a hand over to produce an azure longsword, which he held in his hand.

He then took a step back before raising the longsword and slashing it down upon the wall of light.

A draconic roar rang out as a burst of rippling swordlight emerged over the surface of the azure longsword, then swept directly toward the wall of light up ahead.

After swinging the sword through the air, Han Li bent his knees slightly while holding the sword horizontally in front of himself in a defensive stance. At the same time, he was making a hand seal with one hand, and golden lightning was flashing from his fingertips as he braced himself for any potential backlash.

The sound of a gentle breeze blowing past rang out as the streak of swordlight landed upon the wall of light.

However, contrary to Han Li's expectations, the wall of light wasn't destroyed, nor was there any spatial collapse. Instead, a burst of faint ripples swept over the surface of the wall of light, following which the streak of sword light disintegrated into nothingness.

At the same time, a string of dull thuds rang out from the Mantra Treasured Axis in a rapid succession, and in the instant that the ripples on the surface of the wall of light subsided, the final Time Dao Rune on the axis faded.

A burst of five-colored light emerged from the wall of light amid a faint thump, and the wall of light disintegrated into countless specks of light, while the spatial rift also sealed over.

With all of the Time Dao Runes snuffed out, the Mantra Treasured Axis had also dimmed slightly, and it vanished into Han Li's body.

The light radiating from the Heaven Controlling Vial also faded, and it reverted back to its original size before falling out of the air.

Han Li reached out to catch the vial, then placed it back around his own neck before tucking it into the collar of his robes.

Everything had returned to normal in the secret chamber.

Han Li sat down with his legs crossed, then flipped a hand over to produce a yellow pill. After swallowing the pill, he closed his eyes to meditate.

Maintaining the Mantra Treasured Axis and the Eye of Truth had been extremely taxing on his immortal spiritual power, leaving him feeling quite depleted, but he had naturally fared far better than last time.

Some time later, Han Li slowly opened his eyes, and a wry smile appeared on his face as he offered some words of consolation to himself.

"It looks like I was merely lucky to have seen what I did last time, and that luck isn't necessarily guaranteed every time. For now, I should just focus on collecting pill refinement ingredients and cultivating while recovering my Time Dao Runes."

As soon as his voice trailed off, he rose to his feet and exited his secret chamber.

Chapter 279: Sprouting of the Primary Bean

One day, several years later.

Above the frozen sea to the north of the Ancient Cloud Continent, gusts of fierce wind were howling, while countless snowflakes were fluttering through the air.

The sound of the wind was virtually deafening, and the drifting snow had inundated the entire area.

Han Li was hovering in mid-air beneath the dark clouds in the sky with his Transient Guild mask on.

"This should be the place," Han Li murmured to himself, but his voice was drowned out by the howling wind.

He swept a sleeve through the air to release a streak of azure light, which transformed into an azure longsword that plunged down directly toward the frozen sea below.

As soon as the flying sword descended out of the sky, Han Li also swooped down right behind it.

A sharp clang rang out as the azure longsword pierced into the surface of the ice, plunging through it with ease before drilling into the water.

Han Li immediately followed along, plunging into the sea as well.

A string of loud cracks that even the sound of the wind couldn't drown out rang out across the entire area, and a massive chasm that extended for hundreds of kilometers appeared in the ice, and it was only continuing to extend even further.

Meanwhile, Han Li cast a simple water repulsion restriction onto himself as he entered the water, then sped along behind the azure flying sword toward the seabed with a faint blue light barrier around his body.

Only around 15 minutes later did he draw to a halt, having landed beside a volcanic crater on the seabed. The azure flying sword was plunged into a large rock up ahead, and it was flashing with blue light.

The volcanic crater was completely gray and wasn't giving off even the slightest bit of heat, indicating that this was either an extinct volcano, or one that had been dormant for many years.

Han Li approached the volcanic crater, pulling the azure longsword out of the ground along the way.

As the sword was pulled out, the rock beside the volcanic crater split apart slightly, and a faint glimmer of golden radiance shone out from within the crack.

Han Li lowered his head to take a closer look while slashing his longsword through the water, releasing a burst of azure light. Countless tiny glowing azure sword projections instantly surged forth, slicing into all of the rocks around the volcanic crater.

After the entire layer of rock around the volcanic crater was stripped away, a vast expanse of golden radiance was revealed, instantly illuminating the pitch-black seabed.

As it turned out, there were numerous fist-sized ovular golden balls that resembled some type of egg littered around the volcanic crater.

These things were called Golden Dragon Urchins, and it was a very special type of pill refinement material that wasn't a plant, a type of ore, or any living creature. Instead, it was a combination of the three.

Originally, it was a living creature by the name of the Sea Dragon Urchin, and after its death, a layer of moss would gradually grow over its carcass. After that, the carcass had to be covered in molten lava, and only after these conditions were satisfied could it turn into Golden Dragon Urchin after at least 10,000 years.

Due to the fact that this ingredient contained powers of three different attributes, it was often used to harmonize medicines, so it was present in many pill recipes.

Normally, Han Li wouldn't have accepted an ordinary ingredient collection mission like this one. However, this ingredient was required in the earthly pills that he was planning to refine, so he decided to take on this mission. Not only would he be securing an ingredient that he needed, he would be receiving a reward for completing the mission as well, so it was killing two birds with one stone.

Not only did he have to gather ingredients for the earthly pills that he was going to refine, he had to make preparations for dao pill refinement as well. To say that the amount of spirit stones and Immortal Origin Stones required for this was astronomical would be a complete understatement, so he had no choice but to begin taking on as many Transient Guild missions as he could again.

This mission was already the fourth one that he had completed in the past few months, and after completing this mission, he immediately began rising up toward the surface of the sea without pause.

……

10 years later.

In a nameless long valley, three figures with animal masks on their faces jumped down from the rock faces on either side of the valley. They looked at the dead beast in the valley, then glanced at the tall figure standing beside it, and all of them were at a loss for words.

None of them had anticipated that this mission to kill an early-True Immortal Stage demon beast would've been completed so easily.

On the way here, they had been a little disdainful of the tall man who had always liked to keep to himself and was unwilling to participate in their strategic planning process. However, to their astonishment, as soon as they arrived in this place, the tall man had immediately displayed incredible combat prowess.

He was able to take down the demon beast on his own, making all of the plans that they had made on the way here seem like a complete joke.

After witnessing the fearsome power displayed by the tall man with the title of Wyrm 15, all of their prior disdain had been completely replaced with awe and veneration.

Han Li wasn't a fan of showing off, and under normal circumstances, he would've kept a much lower profile, but he didn't want to waste any time here as he had to go on another mission elsewhere in a month.

……

30 years flew by in the blink of an eye.

On this day, the light of the rising sun was basking the Crimson Dawn Peak in a warm glow, but Han Li's cave abode was looking rather cold and bleak.

Not long after Sun Buzheng and Meng Yungui successfully progressed to the Deity Transformation Stage, they were sent out by Han Li to search for spirit medicine seeds, and shortly thereafter, Meng Qianqian had also left the Crimson Dawn Peak on a journey of her own.

She had taken Featheryearn with her on her journey, and the mountain guardian beast had been left feeling depressed for a very long time in the wake of their departure.

Inside the secret chamber of the cave abode, Han Li emerged amid a flash of azure light, then slowly took off his Transient Guild mask before stowing it away.

He had just completed a mission that had earned him a reward of over 100 Immortal Origin Stones, but that was only a trifling amount compared with his current needs.

After emerging from the secret chamber, he went to the spirit medicine garden in the cave abode.

At this point, the garden had already been virtually completely filled with all types of spirit plants. Planted in an area to the left were several spirit vines that were crawling up a wooden frame, and they would be able to bear fruits once they reached a sufficient age. In another area to the right were countless tiny little flowers that were releasing a cloud of purple qi alongside a strong floral aroma.

The entire spirit garden was thriving and brimming with vitality, with the only exception being the southwestern corner.

That part of the spirit garden was completely empty, and it was as if nothing had ever been planted there.

Whenever Han Li inspected his spirit garden, his gaze would only linger in the southwestern corner for a moment before quickly moving on.

However, on this day, something caught his attention as he swept his gaze over that corner, and he noticed that something seemed to have changed.

He raised an eyebrow as he walked along the edge of the garden to make his way to the southwestern corner. After taking a brief glance, he stepped onto the soft and loamy soil of the garden before crouching down.

Nestled beneath a fist-sized chunk of gray soil right in front of him was a delicate green seedling that was even thinner than a bean sprout, and it was raising up one corner of that chunk of soil, causing it to tilt to the side.

The seedling appeared to have been quite frail, but it was filled with abundant life energy, and it had come from none other than that primary bean.

It sprouted!

Han Li was rather taken aback to see this.

During the first century after he planted the primary bean, he had occasionally watered it with the spirit liquid from the Heaven Controlling Vial, but the primary bean showed no signs of germinating, so he began prioritizing other spirit plants, as well as on manifesting crystals. Hence, he wasn't expecting it to have suddenly germinated on its own.

After carefully examining the seedling for a moment, he noticed that its two delicate leaves bore circles of indistinct dark golden patterns, giving them a rather peculiar appearance.

His brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he flipped a hand over to produce a thin yellow book.

After carefully reading through the book for a moment, the befuddlement on his face only became more pronounced, and he murmured to himself, "Why is it different from this description in Elder Hu Yan's book?"

Even after some extensive examination, he was unable to come up with an answer. In the end, he moved the chunk of soil above the seedling side, then drew out a picture of the golden patterns on its leaves before departing from his cave abode.

Around two hours later.

A streak of azure light descended from the heavens toward a mountain down below.

Upon its landing, the azure light faded to reveal Han Li, and not far in front of him was a large estate with a large red gate, above which was a plaque that carried the words "Hundred Wine Cottage" in free-flowing characters.

Han Li took a glance at the wobbly and inebriated-looking characters on the plaque, and he was just about to step forward when the gate was suddenly opened from the inside.

A voluptuous woman in a white dress then emerged from the estate. The woman was wearing some light makeup, and her hair was arranged into a tall bun, while her entire body was giving off a breathtaking aura of seduction.

The woman was none other than Bai Suyuan's mistress and one of the 13 Golden Immortal dao lords, Yun Ni.

At this moment, there was an enraged look on her face as she hurriedly emerged from inside the estate.

Elder Hu Yan was trailing along behind her in a gray Daoist robe with a pair of gourds hanging from his belt, and he seemed to have wanted to say something, but was also too embarrassed to say it, so he was looking rather awkward.

Upon spotting Han Li outside the estate, the awkward look on his face became even more pronounced, and he stopped in his tracks, not following Yun Ni any further.

As for Yun Ni, she stormed right past Han Li in a fit of rage without even taking a glance at him, then flew away as a streak of white light.

Elder Hu Yan was left looking up at the departing streak of white light with a slightly dazed look on his face, so Han Li could only gently clear his throat to catch his attention.

Elder Hu Yan immediately snapped back to his senses, and he was trying to put on a composed façade while unnecessarily explaining himself, "I've been really busy with official sect duties recently..."

"Indeed, you've always been extremely diligent, and I'm sure Dao Lord Yun came to see you just now for official matters," Han Li replied with a smile and a nod.

Elder Hu Yan gave a pleased nod upon hearing this, then asked, "What brings you here all of a sudden? Let me make this clear in advance: I don't have wine for you to drink!"

"I was out on a mission recently, and I just so happened to have obtained a jar of fine wine that's said to have been brewed using 67 different precious spirit medicines, and I immediately thought of you," Han Li replied with a smile, then flipped a hand over to produce a red jar of wine that he offered to Elder Hu Yan.

Elder Hu Yan's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this, but he immediately put on a composed and restrained façade as he said, "So you do have a conscience, after all! Come in."

Chapter 280: Dao Warrior Mutation

Han Li and Elder Hu Yan entered the estate together, and they passed through the verandah beside the front yard before arriving in the guest hall. Not long after the two of them sat down, a young servant entered the hall to present them each with a cup of tea.

Elder Hu Yan didn't even take a glance at the cup of tea as he swept a sleeve through the air to summon a wine cup, then filled with the contents of the red jar that Han Li had brought him before downing the entire cup of wine in one go.

He then smacked his lips together for a long while with an enraptured expression, as if he were carefully savoring the wine's flavor, then exhaled as he praised, "This Red Fur wine really is one of the fiercest wines out there!"

"You know of this wine, Senior?" Han Li asked with a slightly surprised expression.

"I drank this wine once while I was exploring the northern region of the Primordial Wave Continent, so I have some recollection of it. This wine is brewed by soaking the bones and blood essence of many types of demon beasts and sealing them in jars for hundreds of years.

“Its color is as red as blood, and it's far too strong for mortals to consume. Even for cultivators, this wine is lethal poison to all those below the Deity Transformation Stage, but of course, it's harmless to immortals like ourselves," Elder Hu Yan explained.

"You are by far the most knowledgeable wine enthusiast I've ever met, Senior. For that, you have my utmost admiration," Han Li said with a faint smile.

"Stop trying to flatter me, kid. If you have something to say, then say it. Seeing as you did bring me this jar of Red Fur Wine, I'll agree to any request of yours as long as it's not too unreasonable," Elder Hu Yan said with a smile.

"While inspecting my spirit medicine garden today, I noticed by chance that the Dao Warrior that I had planted earlier had sprouted. However, its seedling doesn't quite match the description in the book that you gave me, so I came to you to be enlightened on this matter," Han Li said.

Elder Hu Yan's interest was instantly piqued at the mention of Dao Warriors, and he asked, "Oh? In what way is it different?"

"Some strange golden patterns have appeared on my Dao Warrior seedling," Han Li replied.

"What type of patterns? I'll come with you to take a look," Elder Hu Yan said as he raised an eyebrow.

"I made a drawing of the patterns, please take a look at them, Senior."

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a sheet of paper as he spoke, then offered it to Elder Hu Yan.

Elder Hu Yan accepted the piece of paper, and after looking at it for only a short while, a smile appeared on his face as he said, "You may be in luck, kid. It looks like your Dao Warrior has undergone a mutation."

"How?" Han Li asked with a puzzled expression.

"There are many factors that could cause a Dao Warrior to mutate, including the type of soil it's planted in, the spirit liquid used to water it, and the properties of the Dao Warrior itself. A multitude of factors have to be taken into account before the reason can be pinpointed," Elder Hu Yan explained.

A contemplative look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this, and he couldn't help but wonder if the mutation had been brought on by the spirit liquid from the Heaven Controlling Vial or perhaps the underground fire veins.

"Having said that, don't thank your lucky stars just yet. Dao Warrior mutation is something that can't be controlled, and it could change the Dao Warrior for the better or for the worse. It all depends entirely on luck," Elder Hu Yan added after downing another cup of wine.

Han Li could tell that there seemed to have been something on Elder Hu Yan's mind, so he decided not to interrupt him any longer.

"In that case, I'll just have to let the Dao Warrior develop as normal and examine the changes when they arise. Thank you for enlightening me, Senior, I'll be taking my leave now," Han Li said as he extended a parting salute.

"Go on, I'll have a few more cups of wine by myself," Elder Hu Yan replied with a dismissive wave.

......

Two days later, in the secret chamber of Han Li's cave abode.

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce his Transient Guild mask before putting it on, and a massive azure array plate was projected onto the wall from the mask.

After ensuring that no adverse changes had taken place in the Dao Warrior, he decided to continue going on Transient Guild missions to earn more spirit stones.

The missions column on the left was constantly being updated with new missions added and completed missions removed, and the mission turnover rate was usually quite high with the exception of some special missions.

Han Li's gaze traveled down the missions column until he spotted a very special mission.

The reason why this mission was special was because the missions released in the Transient Guild generally didn't have any specific details attached. Only after all of the people required for the mission were assembled were the finer details revealed, yet this mission had bucked that trend, having been released with all specific details and mission requirements enclosed.

The mission required one to go to an important place in the Holy Puppet Sect and defend it from an enemy invasion.

Han Li had seen some records of the Holy Puppet sect, and he knew that it was situated in the northwestern part of the Thunderstorm Sea. It was a medium-sized sect that wasn't too far away from the Ancient Cloud Continent, and it was renowned for crafting and selling all types of puppets.

It was naturally unable to compare with the Blaze Dragon Dao when it came to overall size, but due to its special nature, it had always had financial dealings with many immortal sects and clans looking to purchase its puppets, so it was far wealthier than other sects of the same caliber.

Furthermore, the mission could only be taken on by Transient Guild members who held azure masks or above, and that was a clear indication that this was most definitely going to be quite a perilous mission.

However, the reward offered by the Holy Puppet Sect was also extremely handsome, equivalent to over 10 times the reward offered in other normal missions. Han Li was currently in desperate need of spirit stones, and after some deliberation, he decided to accept this mission.

There was still some time left until the assembly date for the mission, so Han Li refined the spirit ingredients that he had acquired up to this point into two batches of pills, then also made some further preparations for the upcoming journey to the Holy Puppet Sect.

Several months later.

In the southwestern region of the Ancient Cloud Continent was a small coastal city by the Windview City. Due to its close proximity to the Thunderstorm Sea in the south, it had a slightly warmer climate and was one of the few places on the entire Ancient Cloud Continent where one could experience all four seasons.

There was an official road that was around 50 to 60 feet wide leading out of the city to the coast, and it passed through a lush forest of willow and elm trees.

Inside the forest, there was a wooden pavilion constructed every few kilometers along the official road, serving as resting spots for those traveling along the official road.

At this moment, everything in a radius of several kilometers around the third pavilion in the forest was enshrouded within a cloud of dense white mist, and within the mist, visibility was limited to only around a foot.

However, the area directly surrounding the third pavilion was completely unaffected by the mist, and there were around a dozen figures seated on the long benches inside. Each of these figures was wearing an azure animal mask with no exception, but in contrast with everyone else, there was a voluptuous woman standing outside the pavilion with a crimson fox mask on her face, and her entire body was giving off a mysterious and seductive aura.

Not far away from her was a slender woman in a pink dress, and she was wearing an azure rabbit mask that was riddled with spirit patterns.

Even though both of them had their faces concealed, the feminine auras that they were giving off were still a sight for sore eyes, and many of the people inside the pavilion were sneaking furtive glances at the two of them.

Right at this moment, a streak of golden light appeared above the forest before descending toward the pavilion.

The golden light pierced straight into the dense mist before landing outside the pavilion, then faded to reveal a tall male figure wearing a black cloak and an azure deer mask. It was none other than Qilin 9.

As soon as he landed on the ground, he immediately approached the voluptuous woman before extending a respectful bow, to which the woman nodded in response.

Immediately thereafter, a streak of azure light flew into the mist as well, then also landed outside the pavilion before fading to reveal the cow-masked Wyrm 15.

Both of the new arrivals attracted a few glances from those who were already seated in the pavilion, but the arrival of Wyrm 15 in particular had caught everyone's attention.

After all, he had become extremely renowned for the frequency at which he was completing Transient Guild missions.

Han Li paid no heed to everyone's prying eyes, but he was rather surprised to have noticed the presence of the woman with the azure rabbit mask that bore the number of "11".

This was because he knew that the owner of this mask was none other than Bai Suyuan.

The mask had concealed her aura, making it impossible to detect her exact cultivation base, but given her Moonlight Immortal Physique, it was safe to assume that she was most likely already a Grand Ascension cultivator.

There was no way that someone of her cultivation base should've been allowed to come on this mission, and that was why Han Li was particularly surprised by her presence here.

However, he didn't display any overt reaction to this, and he approached the fox-masked woman who was clearly the leader of the group before extending a respectful salute, then nodded at Qilin 9, who he had completed a mission with in the past. After that, he made his way into the pavilion before sitting down with his legs crossed, taking no further glances at Bai Suyuan.

Bai Suyuan hadn't managed to identify Han Li. After all, she had only ever seen Han Li adopt disguises using his Transient Guild mask, but she had never seen the mask itself. However, she was somewhat familiar with his reputation for completing guild missions at an extraordinary rate, and thus, she took a few extra glances at Han Li out of curiosity.

Around 15 minutes later, two more people arrived one after the other.

Following their arrival, Qilin 3 turned to everyone in the pavilion as she declared, "Time is of the essence, so now that everyone has arrived, let's set off to the Holy Puppet Sect right away. I'll explain the finer details of the mission to everyone along the way."

Everyone immediately rose to their feet and emerged from the pavilion upon hearing this.

Han Li noticed that aside from Qilin 9, there were several other Transient Guild members that he had previously completed missions with, and they all exchanged slight nods with one another as a form of greeting.

Qilin 3 swept a hand through the air, releasing a sparkling expanse of silver light, which transformed into a crescent-shaped spirit boat in the blink of an eye.

The boat was around 300 to 400 feet in length with rings of profound runes engraved all over its surface. It was also radiating a bright silver glow, and it was clear that this was a flying spirit treasure of quite a high caliber.

Qilin 3 flew onto the deck of the spirit boat, and everyone else quickly followed suit, with a few of them inspecting the spirit boat with envy in their eyes as they flew onto it.

Chapter 281: Holy Puppet Sect

On the silver crescent-shaped spirit boat was a three-pavilion that was entirely white in color, looking as if it had been chiseled out of a chunk of jade, and there were also all types of beautiful diagrams and hidden runes engraved upon its surface.

"The first floor had resting chambers that each of you can choose one of. We'll assemble here again in three days, and I'll explain the mission to all of you then. However, I don't know too much myself, and all of the details will be revealed once we get to the Holy Puppet Sect," Qilin 3 said to everyone, then rose up into the air.

With each step that she took through the air, a projection of a snow lotus flower would bloom beneath her feet, forming a staircase that led to the third floor of the pavilion, where she opened the door before stepping inside.

Han Li was looking up at the third floor of the pavilion with a perplexed look on his face.

Qilin 3 was wearing a crimson mask, just like the one worn by Wyrm 3, so she was clearly a higher level member than Transient Guild members with azure masks. Even though he was unable to detect her cultivation base, he had a feeling that there was a very good chance that she was a Golden Immortal.

If this mission really were being led by a Golden Immortal cultivator, then it was most likely going to be a very difficult one, so he had to be very careful.

Right at this moment, he was approached by Qilin 9, who smiled as he said, "I didn't think that you would've also accepted this mission, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15. It looks like we'll be working together again."

"The reward offered is quite substantial, so I couldn't not be tempted," Han Li replied with a smile.

"This mission is a rather special one. I'm sure you've also noticed that, right, Fellow Daoist?" Qilin 9 asked.

Han Li nodded in response. "You're referring to the circumstances surrounding the mission and the inexplicably high reward being offered, right?"

"Precisely. The puppets created by the Holy Puppet Sect have always been exceptional and possess remarkable spiritual nature, making them extremely popular among many sects. Hence, they're on very good terms with a large number of sects, and I've heard that the sect master of the Spirit Taste Sect and the mountain master of Lurking Armor Mountain share extremely close personal ties with the sect master of the Holy Puppet Sect.

“However, according to my knowledge, the Holy Puppet Sect hasn't turned to either of these sects to ward off the enemies described in the mission. Instead, they've turned exclusively to the Transient Guild," Qilin 9 mused.

"Perhaps the Holy Puppet Sect has encountered some severe trouble on this occasion, so those smaller sects may not have sufficient power to help them. In any case, that's not something for us to worry about. All we need to do is complete the mission for the reward," Han Li replied with a nonchalant smile.

"That's true. In any case, the Holy Puppet Sect is extremely wealthy, so I'm sure they'll be able to afford the offered reward. I've been running a bit short on Immortal Origin Stones recently," Qilin 9 chuckled.

Both of them already had an idea of one another's identities, but neither of them chose to voice their suspicions. Instead, they began to chat about some inconsequential subjects, and there even seemed to have been some type of tacit understanding between them not to discuss the previous mission.

Moments later, the spirit boat began to tremble slightly as all of the runes all over its surface lit up, it set off from the coast of the Ancient Cloud Continent, flying in the southwestern direction.

Everyone one spirit boat quickly made their way to the first floor of the pavilion before each selecting a room for themselves and going inside.

Qilin 9 also did the same, and it didn't take long before Han Li was the only one left on the deck, looking out into the distance.

The slightly murky seawater near the coastline was crashing against all of the jagged rocks on the shore, sending clumps of white foam splashing in all directions.

……

Several months later.

In the southeastern corner of the Infernal Frost Continent was a vast blue sea with rippling waves and a light breeze blowing over its surface.

In the clear, blue sky above, a crescent-shaped spirit boat was rapidly approaching from afar with about a dozen people standing on its deck, peering into the distance, where a gray smudge could be seen on the horizon.

As the spirit boat drew closer and closer, the gray began to expand before its full appearance was finally revealed.

It was a massive ovular island that was riddled with rocks and some sparse vegetation, and even from a very long distance away, one could see the stone halls littered throughout the island.

Around the island were seven or eight smaller islands that surrounded it like guards, and it didn't take long before the spirit boat arrived in the sky directly above the island.

Han Li was standing to the left of the spirit boat next to the railing, peering at the island down below with blue light flashing in his eyes, and he suddenly raised an eyebrow.

He had discovered that the entire island and the surrounding smaller islands were all encompassed under a near-transparent semi-spherical light barrier with wave-like ripples constantly surging over its surface.

All of the giant rocks on the island had been sliced into even and uniform shapes before being piled up along the coastline in a way that appeared to have been completely without rhyme or reason, but was actually meticulously thought out.

For those who weren't proficient in the art of arrays, they would've most likely thought that these rocks had been piled up to form a rather uneven defensive wall, but Han Li could tell that these rocks were the foundation of the array that protected the island, while the surrounding islands were important points in the array.

He directed his gaze toward the smaller island that was nearest to him, and he noticed that at the center of the island was a round pagoda, which was surrounded by a series of wide paths that were interconnected to form an array.

Right at this moment, the island down below suddenly began to tremble violently amid a loud buzzing sound.

Wary looks appeared on the faces of everyone on the spirit boat upon seeing this, and they looked down to find that seawater surrounding the island had begun churning violently as if it had been brought to a boil, sweeping up massive waves that were hundreds of feet tall.

The seawater was relatively clear a moment ago, but it had become quite murky in the wake of this disturbance.

A series of uniform rifts that were each several dozen feet wide opened up on the island, and they continued to expand further and further, slowly opening up the entire island like a box.

Amid the loud rumbling, many large sections of the island began to slowly rise up from the ground into the air before shifting horizontally to reveal the areas down below.

The area of the entire island was instantly significantly increased, and with the sections that were hovering in mid-air, it had turned into a three-tier island.

In contrast with the gray and barren top layer, the two lower layers were lush and vibrant with far more beautiful environments.

Those layers were riddled with forests and rivers, one of which flowed from the second layer to the bottom layer, forming a vertical waterfall in mid-air that presented a uniquely stunning sight to behold.

Even all the Transient Guild members on the spirit boat couldn't help but be surprised by what they were seeing, clearly impressed with the mechanisms set up on the island.

Right at this moment, the protective array above the island flashed, and an opening appeared in its center that was just large enough to accommodate the spirit boat.

The spirit boat passed through the array, then slowly descended toward a white stone plaza on the first level of the island.

After everyone had disembarked from the boat, Qilin 3 stowed it away with a sweep of her hand.

At this point, there were already around a dozen people waiting on the plaza, led by a woman in a blue palace dress. She wasn't very tall, but she had a very curvaceous figure, and even through the thin veil that obscured her face, one could still see the outlines of a set of gorgeous facial features, leaving much to the imagination.

Han Li quickly noticed that the woman was a late-True Immortal cultivator, and her aura was very stable and condensed, indicating that she had already been at the late-True Immortal Stage for many years.

The dozen or so people standing behind her were also True Immortal cultivators, but most of them were only at the early-True Immortal Stage.

There were no particularly noteworthy expressions on any of their faces, but for some reason, all of them seemed to have been harboring hints of concern deep in their eyes.

"You must be tired from your travels, fellow daoists. Please take a rest in the hall, and I'll disclose the details of the mission to all of you soon," the woman in the palace dress said as she extended a slight curtsey.

Qilin 3 nodded in response, and the woman in the palace dress led everyone into the hall.

The terrain around the plaza varied quite drastically, and the entire landscape was riddled with round or square gray stone pillars, upon which were engraved all types of hidden runes and strange lines, while the ground was also covered in complex array patterns.

Han Li could even detect hints of array fluctuation from the antiquated buildings that were concealed among the trees in the surrounding forest.

He wasn't surprised in the slightest to make this observation. Most cultivators who were adept in the art of puppetry also held considerable degrees of expertise in arrays, given that a high level of mastery in arrays was required for puppet refinement.

Back in the Spirit Realm, Han Li had become quite an expert in the art of puppetry, but ever since his arrival in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, he had constantly been busy with cultivation and hadn't dabbled in the art of puppetry for quite some time.

Now that he had come to the renowned Holy Puppet Sect of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, he was going to try and find an opportunity to ask about how he could refine a suitable new vessel for Daoist Xie.

However, for now, his priority was to help the sect overcome its current crisis first.

With that in mind, he couldn't help but wonder who their enemies were going to be.

Everyone walked along the plaza for a long while before finally arriving at a slightly antiquated-looking red hall.

During this time, Han Li noticed that the woman in the palace dress had turned around on several occasions, and on every single one of those occasions, her gaze had landed upon the rabbit-masked Bai Suyuan.

After entering the hall, the woman in the palace dress and Qilin 3 sat down onto the two main seats, while the elders of the Holy Puppet Sect and the rest of the Transient Guild members sat down on either side of them.

The servants waiting by the entrance of the hall had already brewed some spirit tea, which was offered to everyone as soon as they sat down.

The translucent green tea was poured into cups, sending clouds of white steam rising up into the air, and the entire hall was filled with a fragrant aroma.

Han Li raised an eyebrow as he looked down into his teacup to find a series of tea leaves that were as green and vibrant as jade unfurling in the water. Furthermore, they were releasing abundant spiritual qi, indicating that this was an extremely high-quality spirit tea.

He was just about to pick up his teacup when he noticed out of the corner of his eye that there were some faint circles of golden patterns on the fingers of their teapot-bearing hand.

He was rather taken aback to see this, and he immediately looked up to discover that these servants were all puppets, despite the fact that appearance and the smoothness of their movements were no different from a normal person, and they were giving off auras that were identical to low-grade cultivators.

The devil was always in the details, and from this alone, Han Li could tell that the Holy Puppet Sect truly did have some unique expertise in the art of puppet refinement, and that only made him more curious about the sect's puppetry techniques.

Chapter 282: Stationed for Three Years

"Thank you all for coming all this way to our Holy Puppet Sect. Please take a rest and enjoy some spirit tea. I am the deputy sect master of the Holy Puppet Sect, and I will be overseeing proceedings in this defensive battle. I hope that all of you can assist me in the upcoming battle, and all of you will be rewarded if we can ward off the enemy," the woman in the palace dress said.

"We came here to carry out our mission, so don't hesitate to call on us. What my fellow daoists from the Transient Guild and I are most worried about is the current situation of the Holy Puppet Sect, as well as who our enemies are going to be, when they'll be coming, and how many of them we'll have to face," Qilin 3 said in a direct and straightforward manner.

All of the Transient Guild members, including Han Li, turned to the woman in the palace dress upon hearing this.

"To tell you all the truth, I don't have answers to any of those questions," the woman in the palace dress replied with a wry smile after a brief hesitation.

"What?"

"You don't even know who your enemies are? Is this a joke?"

"We have no intention of fighting a battle that we'll know nothing about!"

"If no one comes to attack the sect, does that mean we'll just have to stay here indefinitely?"

Many of the Transient Guild members immediately began to voice their protests upon hearing this, clearly not satisfied with the answer being provided.

Their mission was to protect the Holy Puppet Sect, and the identity of the enemy wasn't explicitly stated, so they were taking a risk by accepting this mission. Of course, they were lured in by the substantial reward being promised, and they were also quite confident in their own powers, but they still had to know who their enemies were so they could weigh up the risks and rewards to devise the best possible strategy.

If the mission were too difficult or dangerous to complete, then they would rather abandon the mission at the cost of having to pay the penalty rather than risk their own lives. Of course, that was only the worst case scenario.

Qilin 3 had disclosed some details of the mission to everyone on the way to the Holy Puppet Sect, but she had left out many key pieces of information, and everyone had thought that all of their questions would be answered upon arriving at the Holy Puppet Sect. However, the deputy sect master appeared to have been completely in the dark as well, and that was naturally not a very encouraging sign.

Qilin 9 and the others weren't saying anything, but all of them were looking expectantly at Qilin 3, waiting for her to speak up.

As for Han Li, his expression remained unchanged, but he was also feeling rather speechless.

However, prior to setting off, he had evaluated the power of the Holy Puppet Sect, and his conclusion was that even if there were Golden Immortal Stage beings among the enemy invaders, given his current power and abilities, he would've still been able to ensure self-preservation, so he was one of the few Transient Guild members present who remained calm and collected.

"Please remain calm, everyone. All of us have already accepted this mission, so our priority should be to consider how to complete it as best as possible. Of course, if you want to withdraw now, you can do so, but according to the guild's rules, you'll have to pay a penalty of three times the Immortal Origin Stone reward being offered," Qilin 3 said in an unhurried manner.

Her voice wasn't very loud, but it carried an innate sense of authority, and all of the Transient Guild members who were raising complaints exchanged a few glances upon hearing this before falling silent.

"Deputy Sect Master, while it's true that we accepted this mission for the reward on offer, so we're bound by duty to complete it, but there's only so much that we can do. If you do not know who your enemy is, then I presume your sect must've made ample preparations, right?" Qilin 3 asked as she turned to the woman in the palace dress.

"Please bear with me, I'm not intentionally trying to withhold any information. Instead, I truly don't have the answers to your questions. Our sect only learned through some reliable avenues not long ago that some forces were being assembled to target our Holy Puppet Sect. Our sect master is currently on another continent and unable to get back in time, and that's why I've turned to recruiting external allies.

“I've already stated in the mission that all you need to do is help our sect weather this storm, and the mission duration is three years. During this time, all of you are free to cultivate in our sect as you please, and even if no enemy invasion occurs during those three years, you'll still receive your rewards in full," the woman in the palace dress explained.

The expression of all of the Transient Guild members eased slightly upon hearing this.

"Additionally, our sect may be small, but it's been standing for many years, and it certainly won't be brought down easily. Even though we do not know who our enemies are going to be, if they dare to invade, then we'll be sure to give them a good taste of our sects countless restrictions, and arrays, and puppets.

“Having said that, excessive confidence is never a good thing, so as a safety precaution, some of our sect's core disciples have already been evacuated, and all of the 3,000 or so sect members who remain on the island are ones who have vowed to defend our sect with their lives," the woman in the palace dress continued.

Han Li nodded in response with a contemplative look on his face upon hearing this. It was no wonder that he hadn't seen many cultivators on such a large island.

"How many of those 3,000 sect members are True Immortal cultivators?" Qilin 9 asked.

Everyone else immediately turned to the deputy sect master as well, and it was clear that they were also very interested to hear the answer to this question.

This was a very understandable reaction. In battles of this level, Golden Immortal cultivators were going to be the most powerful beings on the battlefield, but they were often subjected to many restraints, so more often than not, the number of True Immortal cultivators that each side possessed was the main factor that decided the outcomes of the battles.

"At the moment, we have over 30 True Immortal cultivators. Aside from these elders with us right now, there are also some other elders who are stationed at key points on the islands, and I'm sure you'll be meeting all of them in due time," the woman in the palace dress explained.

The Holy Puppet Sect wasn't a first-rate sect, and it naturally couldn't compare with the Blaze Dragon Dao, so it was already quite remarkable that it had a Golden Immortal Stage sect master and over 30 True Immortal Stage elders. Among sects of the same caliber, it had to have already been considered to be quite the powerhouse.

"In that case, in addition to all of our Transient Guild members, there are at least 50 True Immortal cultivators on the island. With such a formidable lineup and the whole host of restrictions and defensive measures set up on the island, we should be well-equipped to deal with most enemy invasions," Qilin 3 remarked.

Her words instantly instilled a sense of reassurance into the hearts of most of the Transient Guild members present. After all, she was the leader of this mission, and her crimson mask reflected both her power and her status in the Transient Guild. Many of the Transient Guild members present had worked with crimson-masked members in the past, so they were aware of just how formidable and experienced those higher-ranking members were.

Hence, her judgment was one that everyone was willing to support.

Han Li didn't share the same sentiment. Instead of trusting in the judgment of others, he was placing his trust in his own power.

"Alright, so the mission objective is clear: all we have to do is protect the sect for three years. If you wish to withdraw from the mission, this is your final chance to do so," Qilin 3 declared.

At this point, the commotion had already died down. Most of the Transient Guild members had already committed themselves to seeing the mission through for the sake of the reward, and the hesitant minority ultimately also decided not to withdraw.

"Very Good," Qilin 3 remarked with a slight nod, then turned to the woman in the palace dress again as she asked, "Is there anything in particular that we need to do?"

"All of our sect's elders are stationed on this island, so we're stretched a little thin when it comes to defense of the other eight islands. At the moment, there's only a single True Immortal cultivator or some Grand Ascension cultivators stationed on each of those islands. Hence, we'll be requiring your services in assisting with defending those islands," the woman in the palace dress replied.

All of the Transient Guild members' expressions changed once again upon hearing this.

"If we don't have enough numbers, then why don't we focus all of our forces on defending this island and simply abandon the other islands, then reclaim them once the crisis is over?" Qilin 9 asked, raising a question that was shared by everyone.

The main island was clearly the likeliest focal point of the enemy attack, so everyone couldn't help but feel a little suspicious about this arrangement.

However, Han Li didn't feel this to be strange in the slightest. Essentially, they were like mercenaries to the Holy Puppet Sect, so they were naturally going to be stationed on the front lines. There was no way that they could just expect to nestle down in cozy bunkers on the main island and earn such a massive reward.

Of course, the deputy sect master definitely had other reasons for making this arrangement as well.

"To tell you all the truth, the eight array islands form the most formidable defensive line of our sect, and if we can keep them defended, then we'll be able to maintain an upper hand over the enemy to a certain extent. Hence, those islands require extra protection. Besides, even if I were to assign all of you with the task of controlling all of the arrays and restrictions on the main island, you may not necessarily be up to the task," the woman in the palace dress explained.

Everyone was enlightened upon hearing this.

"There are 16 of us in total, how do you plan to distribute us?" Qilin 3 asked.

The woman in the palace dress seemed to have already anticipated this question, and she replied, "Out of the eight array islands, only one is being defended by two True Immortal Stage elders, while the other seven islands will all require extra reinforcement. As for how everyone is to be distributed, I'll leave that up to you, Fellow Daoist Qilin 3."

After some contemplation, Qilin 3 said, "In that case, all of you can form groups of two and pick an island to defend, while Qilin 11 will remain on the main island with me."

Everyone immediately accepted this arrangement with no objections, including Han Li, but his heart stirred slightly upon hearing this.

It seemed that Qilin 3 was going out of her way to look out for Bai Suyuan, so could it be that she was aware of Bai Suyuan's true cultivation base? Alternatively, could it be that the two of them knew each other outside of the Transient Guild?

With that in mind, a bold theory about Qilin 3's identity began to take shape in his mind.

Right at this moment, a familiar voice rang out in Han Li's mind. As it turned out, Xiong Shan had reached out to him through voice transmission.

"How about you and I form a team to defend one of the islands, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15?"

"I was just about to propose the same thing."

Having previously worked with Qilin 9, Han Li was naturally aware of his power, and he was more than happy to accept this arrangement.

……

A few minutes later, everyone emerged from the hall in teams of two before being led toward the surrounding islands by the elders of the Holy Puppet Sect.

"Let's go, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15," Qilin 9 said as he approached Han Li, to which Han Li nodded in response without saying anything.

With that, the two of them were led toward the southwest by an elderly man with a white beard.

Chapter 283: Ancestor of the Bai Clan

Shortly thereafter, Han Li's trio arrived in the air above a circular island before descending toward it.

The island wasn't very large, with a radius of only several hundred kilometers, and the only noteworthy landmarks on it were several short mountains and a small lake, giving it a slightly barren appearance.

Some sparse red buildings could be seen on those mountains and beside the lake, and the ground at the central area of the island was quite uneven, riddled with troughs that were each around 10 feet wide.

These troughs were interconnected with one another to form a complete set of patterns, at the center of which stood a round white pagoda that was around 1,000 feet tall with the same patterns engraved on its surface.

The old man with the white beard led Han Li's duo to the pagoda, which was surrounded by over 100 cultivators that were split up into three teams to patrol the area in shifts, and all of those cultivators stopped in their tracks to extend respectful salutes at the sight of the old man.

At the entrance of the pagoda was a semi-transparent light barrier, and the bearded old man pulled out a Holy Puppet Sect badge to release a burst of white light. Only then did the light barrier fade away, granting the trio entry.

Only after entering the pagoda did Han Li come to discover that it was larger than it appeared on the outside.

The entire interior of the pagoda was hollowed out, and there were around a dozen massive water-droplet-shaped runes engraved onto the surrounding walls. At the center of each rune was embedded a translucent blue spirit stone, all of which were high-grade spirit stones or above.

All of the runes on the walls were connected to a square stone platform that was around half the height of a grown man situated at the center of the pagoda on the ground. There was an array plate engraved onto the platform's surface, and it was giving off a gentle white glow.

Around the stone platform were eight shorter stone platforms situated right up against the walls, upon each of which sat a Grand Ascension cultivator. All of these Grand Ascension cultivators were seated with their legs crossed and their eyes closed, displaying no reaction to the arrival of Han Li's trio.

Beside the main stone platform was a young man dressed like a lumberjack. He seemed to have also been a Grand Ascension cultivator, and at this moment, he was staring at the array plate with his brows tightly furrowed and a rather dazed look on his face. Only upon sensing the arrival of Han Li's trio did he return to his senses before asking, "What are you doing here, Elder Chu? Aren't you overseeing the restricted area behind the mountain?"

"Elder Qi, these two fellow daoists are allies recruited by our deputy sect master. They'll be stationed here with you, and I was instructed to bring them here," the bearded old man replied.

"I see," the young man replied with a nod.

With that, the bearded old man departed, while the young man extended a salute toward Han Li's duo as he said, "My name is Qi Heng. May I ask your names, seniors?"

"I am Qilin 9," Qilin 9 replied as he pointed at the number on his mask.

Han Li also responded in kind. "I am Wyrm 15."

He had actually already been looking at this young man for quite some time, and he felt a very faint sense of familiarity at the sight of him, but he was unable to recall whether they had ever met before.

The three of them briefly exchanged some small talk, following which Qi Heng said, "There are some vacant cave abodes beside the lake on the island that the two of you can stay in. During your time here, you can go anywhere on the island as you please, but do take care not to trigger any of the restrictions. I still have to keep an eye on things over here, so I won't accompany you to the lake."

Han Li's duo nodded in response, then departed from the pagoda to make their way to the lake together.

In the end, they intentionally chose cave abodes quite far away from one another's, with one situated to the west of the lake, while the other was in the east.

The eastern side of the lake was slightly more abundant with vegetation, and a courtyard with red walls and black roof tiles was situated there. Upon arriving at the entrance of the courtyard, Han Li discovered that there were runes engraved onto the gates, clearly indicating that there were restrictions set up here as well.

However, the fact that Qi Heng hadn't accompanied them here indicated that they should've been able to bypass these restrictions without assistance. With that in mind, he made his way over to the gate before pushing on them, and sure enough, they swung open without posing any resistance.

Upon entering the courtyard, Han Li discovered that its furnishings and layout weren't much different from mortal courtyards, but there were some tiny arrays littered throughout the courtyard in discreet places.

For example, there was a small cleansing array beneath the stone table at the center of the courtyard, and it would be activated on its own every once in a while to clear up all of the dust and the fallen leaves and branches in the courtyard.

Inside the hall was a pair of servants, one male and one female. Both of them appeared to have been quite young with delicate skin and rosy lips, presenting a very pleasant sight to behold, but Han Li could tell just from a single glance that they were just puppets rather than living people.

They were just a pair of servants, so they naturally weren't puppets of a particularly high caliber, but there were still some unique aspects in the way that they were crafted that were quite intriguing to Han Li.

He was already quite an expert in the art of puppetry, but most of his knowledge in this field had been accumulated in the Spirit Realm. The puppets of the Immortal Realm were quite different from those of the Spirit Realm both in terms of the materials used and the craftsmanship, so this was a good opportunity for him to learn some new things.

After all, if he wanted to restore Daoist Xie to its former state, his current puppetry expertise most likely wasn't going to be enough.

…..

Over two years passed by in the blink of an eye.

During this time, everything was quite peaceful in the Holy Puppet Sect, and no enemies showed up. However, the entire sect was still in a state of high alert, but the mindsets of all of the Transient Guild members had already somewhat changed.

Han Li and Qilin 9 were walking side by side on the small path along the lake, making their way toward the nearby mountain.

"It's been over two years, yet nothing has happened. Perhaps we'll be able to complete this mission with unexpected ease, Fellow Daoist Wyrm 15," Qilin 9 said in a relaxed voice with a smile on his face.

"It would naturally be ideal if the rest of the mission duration can pass by just as peacefully," Han Li replied with a smile of his own as he took a glance up at the clear, blue sky.

During these past two years, he had explored every single inch of this entire island, tracking down all of the hidden arrays and puppets before carefully examining them multiple times.

He would also occasionally go to the round pagoda to observe the runes on its surface. As a result, he had become quite familiar with Qi Heng, and the two of them would discuss some matters related to puppetry from time to time.

Qi Heng's cultivation base wasn't particularly advanced, but he was quite an expert in the art of puppetry, and he was happy to speak to Han Li, but he was extremely tight-lipped when it came to any matters that were related to the secrets of the sect.

Meanwhile, in a secret chamber on the main island of the Holy Puppet Sect.

The deputy sect master was seated on a stone chair in a blue palace dress. The veil on her face had been removed to reveal her gorgeous features, and there was a gentle look in her eyes.

Seated before her was none other than Bai Suyuan, but she had removed her rabbit mask as well to face the deputy sect master in her true appearance.

"Suyuan, you may think that I'm cruel for abandoning our clan, but I have my reasons. Ever since I left the Blaze Dragon Dao and the Ancient Cloud Continent, I had cut all ties with everything there, and I haven't been back even once all this time," the deputy sect master said with a hint of apology in her voice.

"If you've cut off all ties, then why did you send someone to come after me?" Bai Suyuan asked in an indifferent voice.

It had been revealed to her that this woman was none other than her ancestor, Bai Fengyi, but she couldn't bring herself to feel any intimacy toward this person. Whenever she thought of how her grandfather had been killed by that heavenly devil so she could escape, she would find herself struggling to forgive Bai Fengyi for abandoning their clan.

If Bai Fengyi hadn't disappeared without a trace, perhaps she would've been able to save their clan and prevent all of the tragedies that had ensued.

Right at this moment, Qilin 3, who was also present in the room, heaved a faint sigh. "Fengyi is not to blame for all of this. The circumstances that led to her departure all those years ago were very complicated, and as her mistress, I should bear the brunt of the blame."

Just like Bai Suyuan, she had also removed her Transient Guild mask to reveal her stunning features, and she was none other than one of the 13 Golden Immortal Stage dao lords of the Blaze Dragon Dao, Yun Ni.

"Mistress..."

Both Bai Fengyi and Bai Suyuan called out in unison.

"How foolish you are, my disciple. You thought that the two of us would come together after you left, but you failed to account for the fact that he's a bastard and a coward. I asked him to come with me to help you on this occasion, but he said that he didn't know how to face you and didn't dare to come and see you," Yun Ni said with a wry smile.

"That does seem like something he would do," Bai Fengyi chuckled.

"Who are you talking about, Mistress?" Bai Suyuan couldn't help but ask.

"He was once a dashing and handsome immortal, but now, he's nothing more than a sloppy old drunkard, so there's no need to waste our time talking about him," Yun Ni scoffed, but there was the faintest trace of a smile playing on her lips as she spoke.

Despite what she's saying, she still can't help but smile whenever she thinks of him. Looks like Mistress's feelings toward him haven't changed at all, Bai Fengyi sighed to herself upon seeing this.

"By the way, it's already been over two years, yet nothing has happened. Could it be that something's changed?" Yun Ni suddenly asked.

"The information that we received is definitely reliable. I fear that the longer the enemy spends in preparation, the more ferocious their assault will be when they do finally come," Bai Fengyi replied as her brows furrowed slightly.

"If they happen to attack exactly a year later, you most likely won't be able to assemble so many True Immortal cultivators on such short notice, even through the Transient Guild. What will you do then?" Yun Ni asked.

"Our sect master should be back by then, and with his cultivation base and that immortal puppet, we should be able to deal with this crisis even without the assistance of the Transient Guild," Bai Fengyi replied.

Yun Ni nodded in response, and she was just about to say something when her expression suddenly changed slightly.

Immediately thereafter, a resounding boom rang out, and the entire secret chamber began to tremble violently.

Yun Ni and Bai Fengyi exchanged a glance, and the former immediately put on her Transient Guild mask. Bai Suyuan hurriedly did the same upon seeing this, and the three of them rushed out of the secret chamber together.

Chapter 284: Another Hidden Force

The weather was originally quite clear and fine, yet all of a sudden, a vast blanket of dark clouds suddenly converged in the sky above the main island of the Holy Puppet Sect. The dark clouds stretched for thousands of kilometers, and they descended to such a low altitude that they had virtually come into contact with the sea down below.

All of a sudden, it was as if night had descended upon the island, and gusts of howling wind swept over the sea, raising massive waves.

Yun Ni's trio arrived on the plaza outside the secret chamber to find that the dark clouds up above were churning incessantly with lightning flashing within them, and there were several dozen massive golden and black spirit boats that were laden with people hanging in the sky, resembling a series of floating fortresses.

In contrast with normal flying spirit boats, every single one of these spirit boats was carrying a black platform that was over 100 feet tall, upon which were engraved all types of runes, giving them the appearance of altars.

Bai Fengyi's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and she swept a hand through the air to summon a stone slab array plate, then swiped a finger over it a few times as she instructed, "Activate all restrictions and prepare for battle!"

As soon as this instruction was issued, a sharp screeching sound rang out across the entire main island and the eight surrounding islands.

Immediately thereafter, the spirit patterns on all of the gray stone pillars on the island lit up, and all of the arrays engraved onto the ground and the buildings on the entire island were also activated.

Bursts of loud rumbling rang out as the entire main island began to tremble violently, and its terrain began to undergo drastic changes.

A dense cloud of smoke rose up from the peak of the tallest mountain on the island, and the entire mountain summit slowly descended into the belly of the mountain to reveal a massive hole. Hundreds of flying boats that were riddled with golden spirit patterns rose up out of the hole in unison, hovering in mid-air in anticipation for battle.

At the bend in the river, the flow of water was drawn below the island by a massive passageway that had suddenly appeared, and bursts of golden light emerged on the riverbed as a series of massive turtle-like puppets were revealed. The runes on the bodies of these puppets began to glow with dazzling radiance while releasing bursts of formidable water-attribute spiritual power fluctuations.

In the forest on the second level of the island, the sound of snapping trees rang out incessantly as a series of tiger and leopard-like puppets rushed out into the open. Every single one of these puppets was around 10 feet tall, and they assembled themselves on the edge of the second level of the island as they roared soundlessly up at the sky.

Several True Immortal Stage elders flew onto the plaza from all parts of the island, and each of them was followed by several dozen disciples and hundreds of humanoid puppets.

Some of the important areas on the island had also come under the protection of armies of disciples and puppets, led by more True Immortal Stage elders.

Within a span of no more than 10 seconds after the first sign of disturbance, all of the restrictions on the main island had been activated, and everyone was prepared for battle.

Meanwhile, the sea around the main island was churning violently while swirling around the eight smaller islands, forming a series of massive vortexes.

White light was glowing radiantly within the vortexes, and the white pagodas standing on those islands resembled beacons on the surface of the sea, releasing halos of dazzling light that illuminated the entire surrounding area.

Han Li and Qilin 9 had already returned to the plaza outside of the pagoda and were standing among the Holy Puppet Sect cultivators stationed on the island.

Blue light was flashing in Han Li's eyes as he looked up at the dark clouds in the sky, and he could clearly see some humanoid figures standing above the clouds.

These people all had pieces of black cloth concealing their faces, and they were dressed in black cloaks rather similar to the one that Qilin 9 was wearing. However, there was golden golden embroidery on the edges of their sleeves and collars, and there was a cross-shaped design emblazoned on each of their chests.

This design was not unfamiliar to Han Li as he had previously seen it on the Ubiquitous Pavilion badge that he had obtained from Ping Yaozi.

"I didn't think we'd be facing people from the Ubiquitous Pavilion," Han Li murmured to himself.

"Strictly speaking, they're not from the Ubiquitous Pavilion. Instead, they were merely assembled by the Ubiquitous Kill Order," Qilin 9 corrected.

"Oh? What do you mean by that, Fellow Daoist Qilin 9?" Han Li asked with a puzzled expression.

"As one of the most powerful hidden forces in the Northern Glacial Immortal Region, the Ubiquitous Pavilion is actually rather similar in nature to our Transient Guild, except they mostly focus on the fields of intelligence and assassination. Furthermore, the missions that they accept and release are open to everyone, not just members of the organization.

“In other words, anyone can release missions as long as they have enough money, and anyone can accept their missions as long as they're confident in their own powers. Anyone that releases or accepts a Ubiquitous Pavilion mission counts as an elementary member, so their organization isn't as strict and rigorous as our Transient Guild. As a result, its internal relations are far more complicated and convoluted," Qilin 9 explained.

"So you're saying that even Transient Guild members could release and accept Ubiquitous Pavilion missions, and that these people were assembled by something called a Ubiquitous Kill Order?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. The Ubiquitous Kill Order is an order that's issued to eradicate an entire sect or clan, and it's very expensive to release. It gathers power from an entire immortal region to target a sect or clan, and all those who participate in the mission will be able to keep all of the spoils that they reap during the eradication operation without any fear of repercussions," Qilin 9 explained.

Han Li was enlightened upon hearing this. The most fearsome thing about such an order was how much allure it posed to the enormous number of itinerant cultivators in an immortal region, particularly those who were at or below the Grand Ascension Stage and were stuck at bottlenecks, but were also lacking in cultivation resources. If they didn't do anything, their lifespans would eventually run out anyway, so it made sense for them to take risks and grasp onto any opportunities that they could.

Once people like them accepted a Ubiquitous Pavilion mission, their identities would be protected by the Ubiquitous Pavilion, and that allowed them to act without any inhibitions, so they were often far crueler and more brutal in their assault against the sect or clan that they were targeting, both to secure more cultivation resources and to vent the resentment and envy that they harbored toward these establishments.

Throughout its long history, the Holy Puppet Sect had accumulated an astronomical amount of wealth just from selling puppets alone, making it an extremely alluring target for these desperate cultivators.

While the two of them were speaking with one another, the ground beneath their feet suddenly began to tremble violently, and the troughs in the ground were quickly being filled with white light that was flowing like molten silver.

Bursts of rumbling rang out from beneath the entire island, and a circle of massive rifts began to appear on the ground surrounding the plaza, separating the area around the pagoda from the rest of the island.

Immediately thereafter, this isolated area was rapidly elevated by several thousand feet.

Han Li rose up into the air before casting his gaze toward the island to find that the entire central area of the island had risen up from the rest of the island, having transformed into a massive stone puppet.

The puppet resembled an enormous warrior that was constructed from a material that resembled white jade, but was as hard as steel, and it was wielding a giant silver saber that was several thousand feet in length and was riddled with spirit patterns that were giving off astonishing sharp fluctuations.

The same thing had taken place on all of the other array islands, and some of the giant puppets resembled primordial giant apes, some resembled giants clad in stone armor, and some were similar in appearance to massive wolves. In any case, all of them had different forms, and in addition to that, the colors and shapes of the spirit patterns on their bodies were also different.

Some were dark yellow and formed circles around the torso of the puppet, some were crimson and draped over the arms and body of the puppet like strips of red silk, and some were black and emblazoned on the chest of the puppet like tattoos.

At this moment, there were three figures standing side by side on an inky-black spirit boat high up in the sky within the dark clouds.

One of them had an extremely long and deep scar on their face, running across the left side of their forehead to their right eye, then down their cheek, where the rest of it was concealed by the black cloth covering their face.

To their right was a young man with a slender build and a sword strapped to his waist. Half of his face was also concealed behind a black cloth, but the skin on the exposed half of his face was as fair as jade, and beneath his bushy eyebrows was a pair of bright and piercing eyes.

Both of them possessed incredibly formidable auras that indicated that they were Golden Immortal cultivators.

The third figure was a burly man with a slightly yellow complexion. He was standing at close to 10 feet tall, and even though he was wearing a hooded cloak, a dark azure metallic gleam could be seen in front of his forehead, indicating that he was wearing some type of metallic headgear.

He was only at the pinnacle of the True Immortal Stage, yet he was able to stand alongside this pair of Golden Immortals, and that was a clear indication that he was no ordinary True Immortal.

"Are you satisfied with the arrangements made by our Ubiquitous Pavilion, Fellow Daoist Lu Ji?" the man with the scar on his face asked as he turned to the fair-skinned young man beside him.

"I paid such a heavy price to employ the services of your Ubiquitous Pavilion precisely because of your organization's vast influence, but I'm still quite surprised that you were able to gather so many people. Having said that, aren't the cultivation bases of these people a little too varied? How much power could such a ragtag bunch of cultivators possibly possess?" the young man by the name of Lu Ji replied.

While it was true that these spirit boats were carrying 2,000 to 3,000 cultivators, there were only fewer than 50 True Immortal cultivators among them, while the rest consisted of Grand Ascension cultivators and even quite a large number of Body Integration and Spatial Tempering cultivators, so it wasn't incorrect to refer to them as a ragtag bunch.

"These people are all itinerant cultivators, and all of them had to fight their way up the ranks to get to their current cultivation bases, so among those of the same cultivation base, there's no way they'd be inferior to these weaklings of the Holy Puppet Sect who only know how to make puppets," the man with the scar on his face replied with a smile.

"I don't believe this is the right time to be chatting among ourselves, fellow daoists. I've come to the Ancient Cloud Continent with a mission from my master, so let's finish things here as quickly as possible, Fellow Daoist Xue Han," the yellow-faced man suddenly said.

"There's no need to be in such a hurry, Fellow Daoist Zhong Luan. We've only done some light probing up to this point. Now that they've revealed all of their defenses and we can confirm that their defensive measures are identical to what's laid out in the intelligence that we've collected, we can proceed according to our original plan. However, don't forget what we agreed on earlier once we get into the Holy Puppet Sect," the scar-faced man by the name of Xue Han chuckled.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist," Zhong Luan replied in an indifferent voice.

Chapter 285: Breached Array

The scar-faced man by the name of Xue Han slowly turned around upon hearing this, then ordered, "Get into formation and attack!"

The group of figures behind him gave a collective affirmative response before flying away, and it didn't take long before all of the dozens of spirit boats hanging suspended within the dark clouds to abruptly swoop down.

At the same time, they were moving in all directions, forward, backward, to the left, and to the right, as if they were soldiers adopting their positions in a pre-set formation, and all of the spirit boats quickly arranged themselves into a ring-shaped array.

Immediately thereafter, a burst of thunderous chanting rang out, and the dozens of black platforms on the spirit boats began to tremble in unison. The golden patterns engraved upon them also lit up with dazzling radiance while giving off powerful energy fluctuations.

A resounding boom rang out as all of the platforms on the spirit boats shuddered in unison, following which a golden pillar of light erupted from each of them directly into the sea of dark clouds up above.

The sea of clouds instantly began to churn violently with traces of golden light shimmering within them, immediately following which an enormous projection of a round plate appeared. The projection was over 10,000 feet in radius and was riddled with strange patterns that were radiating dazzling golden light.

All of a sudden, a burst of rumbling that resembled a string of thunderclaps rang out, and the entire sea of clouds began to surge like boiling water.

A series of giant millstone-sized fireballs shot out of the projection with scorching golden flames burning on their surfaces, then came crashing down toward the main island of the Holy Puppet Sect and the eight islands around it.

Thousands of golden fireballs were crashing down with long fiery tails behind them, resembling an almighty meteor shower.

It was as if the entire sky had been set alight with golden radiance, and even the dark clouds had been given a golden lining.

However, all of these fireballs were stopped cold in their tracks close to 100,000 feet above the main island, as if they had suddenly crashed into an invisible wall, and they exploded violently to send countless golden sparks flying in all directions.

As the explosions rang out one after another, a near-transparent semi-spherical light barrier was revealed. Azure light was flashing over its surface, and the constant barrage of exploding fireballs were sending ripples surging incessantly over the light barrier.

One massive crater after another appeared on the light barrier, only for it to bounce back and revert back to its original form amid flashes of azure light, and it was able to keep itself intact against the barrage of fireballs.

On the plaza on the main island of the Holy Puppet Sect, everyone was looking up at the sky with tense expressions.

"They won't be able to keep up an assault this ferocious for too long. How much longer can your defensive array last? " Yun Ni asked as she stood beside Bai Fengyi.

Bai Fengyi considered the question for a moment, then replied, "If this is all that we have to deal with, then we shouldn't have any problems. However..."

Before she had a chance to finish her sentence, the spirit patterns on the massive plate projection within the dark clouds faded, and the storm of golden fireballs subsided.

That's it?

Everyone was rather perplexed by this turn of events.

However, the golden plate projection then immediately began operating once again, and this time, it was releasing even larger golden fireballs that were falling twice as fast as before, building up tremendous downward momentum.

A resounding boom rang out as the golden fireball came crashing down.

The defensive light barrier shuddered violently as an enormous indentation appeared on its surface, and as opposed to light ripples, there were now turbulent waves surging over the light barrier.

Before the light barrier had a chance to recover, several hundred more golden fireballs came crashing down in rapid succession, and the entire light barrier was completely warped, looking as if it were going to collapse at any moment.

"It looks like the array won't be able to last much longer. Once the battle begins, I'll only be able to take on one of the two enemy Golden Immortals. What are you going to do about the other one?" Yun Ni asked.

"I'll think of a way to keep the other Golden Immortal at bay. Our cultivators and puppets outnumber them, so if we can quickly kill as many of their True Immortal cultivators as possible, we'll be able to severely dent their morale," Bai Fengyi replied.

"Indeed. These people have banded together solely for profit, so if we can force them onto the back foot, they'll immediately fall apart like sand. Hence, we have to go all-out from the outset and crush them from the get-go. Only then will we have a chance of securing victory," Yun Ni said.

Bai Fengyi nodded in response, then summoned an array plate before issuing a series of verbal instructions into it.

On the spirit boat high up in the sky, Xue Han was looking down at the array on the island with a hint of surprise on his face. "This array is more sturdy than I anticipated. Fellow Daoist Lu Ji, looks like we'll have to trouble you to do the honors."

Lu Ji offered no reply, merely nodding silently in response before flying out of the spirit boat, where he hovered in mid-air.

He then removed the silver longsword that was strapped to his waist, holding the scabbard in one hand while gently sweeping the index and middle fingers of his other hand over the hilt of the sword.

A sharp clang rang out as the silver longsword flew out of its scabbard before rising up toward the dark clouds above.

A circle of white sword qi that was visible even to the naked eye began to swirl around the sword in a frenzy, instantly piercing a giant hole with a radius of several thousand feet into the dark clouds in the sky.

A ray of bright sunlight passed through the hole, illuminating the entire area around Lu Ji and making him resemble a majestic sword immortal. The eyes of everyone down below were unconsciously drawn to him, and Han Li was also looking up at the massive hole in the clouds while standing next to the giant stone puppet on the island that he and Qilin 9 were stationed on.

The sword had risen up, but it hadn't descended.

The phenomenon created by the rising sword wasn't actually all that astonishing, but given Han Li's expertise in swordsmanship, he was able to see some things that others couldn't.

The concentration and sharpness of the sword qi around the flying sword were unlike anything he had ever seen before, and he had a feeling that once the sword did fall, it would do so with devastating effect.

Sure enough, mere moments later, dazzling silver light erupted within the dark clouds, and a string of loud sounds that were different from thunderclaps rang out as a menacing aura began to emanate through the air.

Blue light flashed within Han Li's eyes as he cast his gaze toward the sky, and he discovered a streak of pristine white swordlight that was over 10,000 feet in length standing among the clouds like a massive mountain.

Streaks of sword qi were surging around it in a frenzy, and bursts of rumbling resembling what one would hear in an avalanche were ringing out incessantly.

In the next instant, the streak of white swordlight descended like a snow-covered mountain crashing down toward the sea of dark clouds.

The layers of clouds melted away like snow and ice in the face of the swordlight, and a massive opening that was over 100,000 feet wide quickly emerged.

The streak of swordlight looked as if it were going to slice the entire heavens apart, and it descended with unstoppable force toward the light barrier down below, which was already severely warped from the barrage of fireballs.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as an enormous indentation appeared in the defensive light barrier, quickly stretching to several thousand feet in length before elongating even further.

The light barrier was already close to being a spent force, and it was unable to revert back to its original form, exploding violently and disintegrating into countless specks of light.

However, the massive streak of swordlight that had destroyed the light barrier was barely slowed down as it continued to descend.

All of a sudden, a burst of dazzling white light erupted into the heavens from the main island, and an enormous white snow lotus flower projection appeared, clashing against the swordlight tens of thousands of feet in the sky to result in a violent explosion.

Bursts of powerful shockwaves instantly erupted in all directions, sweeping up enormous waves in the surrounding sea within a radius of thousands of kilometers.

All of the cultivators assembled by the Ubiquitous Pavilion on the dozens of spirit boats in the dark clouds erupted into excited cheers at the sight of the defensive array being broken, and their eyes were glowing as if they could already see the countless spirit stones waiting for them to plunder.

"Now that the defensive array has been destroyed, how much you can plunder from the Holy Puppet Sect will be up to you, fellow daoists," Xue Han cackled.

As soon as his voice trailed off, countless figures instantly sprang down from the black spirit boats in the dark clouds, and they swooped directly toward the main island down below like a flock of starving crows.

However, right as they were approaching the island, the spirit patterns on the bodies of the eight giant puppets situated around the main island suddenly lit up.

Pillars of light of different colors that were hundreds of feet thick erupted out of the pagodas on top of the giant puppets' heads before converging toward the main island, where they came together to form a colorful light barrier that encompassed the entire island.

The hundred or so Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators who were charging at the forefront hurriedly tried to stop themselves in their descent, but were unable to arrest their own momentum and crashed straight into the light barrier.

Aside from several True Immortals who were able to summon protective treasures in time and were only sent flying upon crashing into the light barrier, all of the other cultivators were instantly reduced to ashes, leaving only acrid plumes of black smoke in the air.

This second defensive barrier had stopped all of the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators cold in their tracks, and they quickly spread themselves out in all directions with wary looks on their faces.

Right at this moment, Bai Fengyi commanded, "Engage the enemy!"

Streaks of light rose up from all over the surrounding islands as countless figures sprang up into the sky around the colorful light barrier, charging directly toward the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators.

They were immediately followed by several hundred mechanical flying boats that hurtled directly toward the black spirit boats up above. In the meantime, some of the important locations on the islands were still being guarded by some cultivators and puppets in case of sneak attacks.

"I'm going ahead," Yun Ni said to Bai Fengyi, then rose up from the main island.

Bai Fengyi turned around to take a glance at Bai Suyuan and the others with a complex look in her eyes, then instructed, "Make sure to stay here and don't go anywhere."

After that, she also rose up into the air behind Yun Ni.

High up in the sky, Lu Ji was looking down to find a massive snow lotus flower projection rapidly ascending toward him from down below.

His expression remained unchanged as he raised a hand up high before making a beckoning motion, and a silver longsword swooped down from the giant hole in the dark clouds before landing in his grasp.

Chapter 286: Imminent Battle

"You've saved me the trouble of coming after you," Lu Ji remarked in an indifferent voice, then raised his silver longsword before taking a step forward, upon which he instantly vanished from the spot.

Immediately thereafter, countless streaks of swordlight crashed into the petals of the oncoming snow lotus flower projection, with thousands of clashes taking place in an instant. An ear-splitting screeching sound rang out from the clashing swordlight and flower petals, while the nearby space trembled violently.

"I'll see you on the island, Fellow Daoist Xue Han," Zhong Luan said, then flipped a hand over to summon a long black saber before jumping straight down from the black spirit boat, plummeting directly toward the nearest island puppet.

"I'm sure that won't take too long," Xue Han murmured to himself as he swept a sleeve through the air, and a palm-sized golden ring flew out amid a flash of golden light.

The golden ring then rapidly swelled in size to a diameter in excess of 1,000 feet before hovering in mid-air.

Xue Han then chanted an incantation, and dense layers of runes instantly appeared on the surface of the giant golden ring, releasing rays of yellow light and bursts of formidable law fluctuations.

A string of dull thuds rang out within the space encompassed beneath the golden ring, and it was as if a burst of invisible pressure had isolated the area and was forcefully compressing the air down below.

A deep indentation that corresponded with the golden ring also appeared on the surface of the colorful light barrier down below, and it began to tremble unsteadily amid a burst of incessant buzzing.

Xue Han let loose a loud roar as he thrust a palm forcefully downward, and a long rift was instantly torn open on the light barrier, making it appear as if it could collapse at any moment.

Right at this moment, a streak of blue light hurtled rapidly through the air from down below, then struck the giant golden ring in the sky with a loud clang.

The golden ring shuddered violently upon being struck by the streak of blue light, and yellow light that it was releasing also began to sway in an unstable manner. As a result, the pressure on the light barrier down below was significantly alleviated, allowing it to return to its original form.

Xue Han's expression darkened slightly upon seeing this, and he looked down to find a beautiful woman in a palace dress rising up toward him while wielding a shimmering blue sword, and she was accompanied by a young daoist priest in a gray daoist robe.

There was a silver gourd strapped to the daoist priest's waist and a golden horsetail whisk held in his hand. His appearance was no different from that of a normal human, but in reality, it was an extremely life-like high-grade puppet.

"A faux immortal puppet, I see," Xue Han chuckled as he licked his own lips.

He then made a beckoning motion with one hand, and the golden ring flew back to him before fitting itself around his wrist, following which he turned and flew directly toward the woman and the young daoist priest.

Meanwhile, the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators had already spread themselves out, and they were flying toward the surrounding array islands rather than continuing to charge at the colorful light barrier.

At this point, they had already noticed that the light barrier seemed to have been connected to the giant puppets around the main island, so if they were to vanquish these puppets, then the light barrier would automatically be unraveled.

However, the cultivators of the Holy Puppet Sect naturally weren't just going to allow them to do as they pleased, and they had already risen up into the air to oppose the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators.

A fierce battle instantly ensued.

The majority of the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators were itinerant cultivators, so their powers and abilities were all quite varied.

In the northwest, one of the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators opened up a spirit beast pouch to release several dozen strange-looking ferocious beasts, each of which was close to 1,000 feet in size, and they immediately pounced onto the army of puppets being controlled by the Holy Puppet Sect cultivators down below.

In the southeast, someone summoned a giant black flag that was over 2,000 feet in size, and the flag released gusts of inky-black yin wind that instantly stripped the flesh from the bones of many low-grade Holy Puppet Sect disciples.

In the southwest, someone opened a white bone box to release a swarm of countless golden hornets that began attacking the Holy Puppet Sect cultivators with their highly toxic stingers.

In contrast, the powers and abilities of the Holy Puppet Sect disciples were far less varied, but they were determined to defend their sect with their lives, and with the army of puppets on their side, they far outnumbered the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators, so they were able to gain the upper hand for now.

High up in the sky, all of the black spirit boats dispersed as the golden patterns on their surfaces began to glow radiantly, and a series of golden spears that were several dozen feet thick shot out of the giant holes on the undersides of the boats before raining down amid a sharp screeching sound.

The hundreds of mechanical flying boats that had already risen up into the sky also began to glow brightly as the circular array at the center of each of the boats flashed with red light, releasing a relentless barrage of crimson fireballs the size of millstones. These fireballs converged in mid-air to form a fiery storm to oppose the oncoming golden spears, and a string of deafening booms rang out as the fireballs clashed against the golden spears.

Golden light and crimson flames erupted in all directions, plunging the entire sky into a state of complete chaos.

While the battle was raging in the sky, a fierce skirmish was taking place down below as well.

Some of the Ubiquitous Pavilion were locked in battle against Holy Puppet Sect disciples and puppets, while others were charging toward the eight giant puppets, led by True Immortal cultivators, aiming to destroy the puppets so that the light barrier that was protecting the main island would be unraveled.

The hundred or so Holy Puppet Sect cultivators who were standing on the giant puppet on the southwestern island were all holding a series of golden and silver talismans tightly in their hands while looking up at the sky with tense expressions.

This was the island where Han Li and Qilin 9 stationed, and the latter was peering into the distance as he said, "There are over 200 cultivators coming to our island, three of whom are True Immortal cultivators, while the majority of the rest of them are below the Grand Ascension Stage."

"You and I can take care of those three True Immortals, while the Holy Puppet Sect's cultivators deal with the rest," Han Li proposed.

"My thoughts exactly," Qilin 9 replied with a nod.

With that, the two of them didn't waste any more time with words before launching themselves up toward the approaching Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators.

A chorus of incantations rang out as numerous talismans flew up into the sky from the top of the giant puppet's head, and puppets of all types of shapes and forms flew out of the talismans amid flashes of bright light.

The army of puppets was followed closely by the Holy Puppet Sect cultivators.

Among the three True Immortals from the Ubiquitous Pavilion, one of them was a burly and imposing young man, while to his left was a thin old man that was quite a bit shorter in stature, and to his right was a voluptuous woman, the type that Elder Hu Yan would've referred to as possessing big tits and a big arse.

As soon as the old man spotted Han Li and Qilin 9, his brows immediately furrowed slightly as he cursed to himself under his breath.

"What's wrong?" the burly young man asked.

"Those two are fellow Transient Guild members, and they're both azure mask members. What terrible luck," the thin old man replied.

"I recall hearing you speak about the hierarchy of your Transient Guild, and you told me that all of the guild's azure mask members are quite formidable. It looks like we're in for a rough battle," the burly man remarked.

"I'm starting to get a little scared after hearing that," the voluptuous woman chuckled. "In any case, I definitely don't want to take on either of them on my own."

"The one with the cow mask seems a little weaker. I'll take care of him by myself and leave the other one to you two," the burly man decided.

"Alright, we'll do as you say," the thin old man immediately agreed, and the voluptuous woman had no objections, either.

As the two opposing forces reached within 10,000 feet of one another, all of the cultivators below the True Immortal Stage made a conscious effort to distance themselves from the True Immortal cultivators before commencing their battle.

Meanwhile, the burly man flew directly toward Han Li, while the thin old man and the voluptuous woman charged toward Qilin 9, one from the left and one from the right.

Qilin 9 gave a cold harrumph as he rose up further into the air, opening up some distance between himself and Han Li as he met his assailants head-on.

While he was still several thousand feet away, the burly man abruptly flicked his wrist through the air, sending a streak of black light flying out of the palm of his hand directly toward Han Li.

The streak of black light then swelled drastically in size, transforming into a massive black ax the size of a small mountain in the blink of an eye before crashing down toward Han Li.

Even before the ax had reached Han Li, a ferocious gust of wind was already sweeping toward him, forcing all of the surrounding air to either side while threatening to slice the very space apart.

Han Li was caught slightly off guard, not expecting his opponent to unleash such a ferocious attack from the get-go, but that didn't hamper his reaction speed at all as a layer of golden scales appeared over his arm, and he clenched his hand into a tight fist before swinging it forcefully into the blade of the ax.

A resounding boom rang out as a gust of fierce wind swept through the air in all directions.

Han Li was forced down by over 1,000 feet before stomping his feet forcefully into the air below to stabilize himself.

Meanwhile, the giant ax was sent flying back, and it reverted back to its original size before being caught by the burly man, who also stumbled back a few steps involuntarily from the tremendous momentum that the ax carried.

"I didn't expect you to also be a Profound Immortal," the burly man exclaimed.

Han Li paid no heed to him as he made a hand seal while chanting an incantation, and his Heavy Water True Axis instantly appeared before him, giving off powerful water law fluctuations.

"Go!" he commanded, and the Heavy Water True Axis began to rapidly revolve in mid-air, transforming into a black blur as it hurtled directly toward the burly man.

The Heavy Water True Axis was traveling extremely quickly, reaching the burly man in the blink of an eye.

The burly man's expression changed slightly seeing this, and he grabbed onto the shaft of the ax with both hands before holding it in front of him like a shield.

This ax had been refined using many types of precious ore and earth-attribute materials, and there were also many bolstering runes engraved onto its surface, making it an extremely formidable treasure that was no less sturdy than a top-tier defensive treasures, so he was confident that he would be able to block this attack.

Chapter 287: Two VS Three

The Heavy Water True Axis reached the giant ax in the blink of an eye, and a Water Dao Rune on the axis released a burst of water law powers amid a flash of blue light as it crashed into the ax with unfathomable power.

The spirit patterns engraved onto the ax instantly lit up, only to quickly break apart, immediately following which the entire ax itself also shattered into countless pieces.

A stunned look flashed through the burly man's eyes upon seeing this, and a burst of light instantly appeared on his chest, forming a yellow array projection that managed to keep the Heavy Water True Axis at bay.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

Through his spiritual connection with his Heavy Water True Axis, he could sense that it was as if the axis had fallen into a swamp, and all of its power was stripped away.

He immediately increased his immortal spiritual power output, and a resounding boom instantly rang out as the burly man felt a burst of mountainous pressure crashing into chest.

Even though the immortal talisman on his chest had nullified most of the power of the Heavy Water True Axis, it was still too much for him to bear, and he was sent flying back through the air with blood gushing out of his mouth.

Meanwhile, Qilin 9 was locked in a fierce battle against the other two True Immortal cultivators.

The voluptuous woman was wielding a purple whip with purple bars all over its surface. The whip was giving off a metallic gleam, and as she flicked her wrist through the air, the whip transformed into countless whip projections that lashed out at Qilin 9 from all directions.

Qilin 9 was wielding an antiquated golden sword that he was swinging through the air with tremendous power, unleashing countless streaks of golden swordlight that sliced the oncoming whip projections into shreds.

There were nine stars that were glowing brightly on the blade of the sword, forming a secure barrier of dazzling light around him.

Right at this moment, a burst of black light suddenly flashed past behind him, and a thin figure sprang out of thin air in a completely silent manner. The thin figure was wearing a set of sharp silver claws on each hand, and he plunged those claws straight into the light barrier around Qilin 9's body.

The runes on the silver claws lit up as the thin old man brought his hands apart in a forceful motion, tearing a gash into the light barrier.

A vicious look flashed through his eyes as he suddenly opened his mouth, and a burst of black light appeared inside his oral cavity before a dark green needle treasure shot out from within, piercing directly toward Qilin 9's heart from behind.

Qilin 9 had been trying to keep tabs on the thin old man this entire time while facing the voluptuous woman, but he was still unable to detect his assailant until it was too late.

"It's time for you to die!" the old man cackled with a cold gleam in his eyes.

However, right as his voice trailed off, a burst of golden light suddenly appeared behind Qilin 9, and a square-shaped antiquated golden mirror appeared.

A faint clang rang out as the flying needle struck the surface of the mirror and was instantly repelled.

Immediately thereafter, a thunderous roar rang out from within the mirror, and a sense of foreboding welled up in the thin old man's heart upon seeing this.

He immediately opened his mouth to recover his flying needle, then shot back in retreat.

All of a sudden, a burst of light flashed over the golden mirror, and a giant golden tiger with fiery red stripes all over its body pounced out of the mirror with its cavernous mouth wide open, biting down upon the thin old man.

In response, the old man flicked a wrist through the air, and the thin green string flew off from around his wrist before transforming into a massive azure python that pounced at the giant tiger before winding itself around the tiger's body.

Meanwhile, the old man retreated back to the voluptuous woman's side several thousand feet away as he complained, "This guy's a real pain to deal with. I should've chosen the guy with the cow mask."

As soon as his voice trailed off, he heard an agonized howl, and he hurriedly turned around to find the burly man having his chest stomped on by Han Li, sending him plummeting down toward the sea below like a rucksack.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li also swooped down toward the surface of the sea as a streak of azure light.

"Looks like neither of them are easy opponents. If we don't go all-out, not only will we not be able to plunder anything from the Holy Puppet Sect, we could easily lose our lives here," the thin old man said in a grim voice.

"We do indeed have to get serious. Please hold him off for me while I... get changed into something more comfortable," the voluptuous woman said with a seductive smile.

The thin old man couldn't help but shudder at the sight of her smile, and he swept a sleeve through the to summon a large yellow flag, which he grabbed onto with both hands before charging toward Qilin 9.

At the same time, a vicious look appeared in the voluptuous woman's eyes as she slid down the collar of her robes to reveal a shoulder, followed by a section of her arm, where a slender woman in a red dress was tattooed. The woman was holding a lute with a peculiar smile on her half-concealed face.

This tattoo wasn't just a cosmetic accessory. Instead, it was a powerful treasure that was crafted from human skin. She had been nurturing it with her own flesh and blood this entire time, and she was only willing to use it now as she had identified just how perilous this situation was.

She began to chant a peculiar incantation, and the tattoo of the woman on her arm suddenly became rather blurry, as if all of its colors were spreading and fading.

At the same time, the skin on her arm began to take on a red coloration, and what appeared to have been a rash quickly appeared before spreading over her entire body.

The woman let loose a pained groan as the black cloak that she was wearing gradually faded, and she transformed into the woman in red that was tattooed on her arm. In the wake of her transformation, her cultivation base had been elevated from the mid-True Immortal Stage to the late-True Immortal Stage.

With a flick of her wrist, a crimson oil paper umbrella flew out of the palm of her hand amid a flash of red light, then opened itself up in mid-air before flying toward Qilin 9.

The woman also drifted through the air behind the umbrella as she said in a cold voice, "We have to put an end to him as quickly as possible."

Right at this moment, a resounding boom rang out from the sea down below, and a massive wave erupted upward, following which a figure flew out of the water, rising several thousand feet up into the air before drawing to a halt.

It was none other than Han Li, and his Heavy Water True Axis was revolving in mid-air behind him.

Immediately thereafter, a golden figure also erupted out of the water, and it was none other than the burly man that Han Li had just sent plummeting into the sea. At this moment, it was as if a layer of golden paint had been applied to his entire body.

At this moment, golden blood was pouring out of all of his orifices, and he was sorely regretting his decision to challenge Han Li on his own.

He had been forced to devour the Golden Rot Pill that he had cherished for many years, and only then was he able to withstand Han Li's barrage of ferocious attacks.

He had no idea what that black wheel treasure of Han Li's was. It was clearly a water-attribute treasure, but it was incredibly heavy, as if it contained an entire ocean.

With a flick of his wrist, a white bone shard appeared on the palm of his hand. There were some peculiar crimson patterns engraved onto the surface of the bone shard, and they were giving off faint energy fluctuations.

A hesitant look appeared on the burly man's face as he looked down at the bone shard in his hand.

Meanwhile, Han Li was hovering in mid-air with his Heavy Water True Axis continuing to revolve incessantly behind him.

He took a glance at Qilin 9 to find that he was gradually being forced onto the back foot by the woman in red and the thin old man, and a slightly grim look appeared in his eye as he turned his gaze back to the burly man.

The burly man's heart immediately jolted slightly upon seeing this, and the hesitation in his eyes faded entirely as he brought his palms together, holding the bone shard in between them as he began to chant an incantation.

Wisps of smoke began to billow out from between the palms of his hands as the bone shard was set alight, transforming into an azure fire lotus flower that shot forth through the air.

This flame was known as the Phosphorus Bone Flame, and it was an extremely rare flame that could only arise under a set of extremely rigorous special conditions. Furthermore, it could only be stored in specially made bone shards of high-grade demon beasts. It was an extremely formidable flame, but it was also a disposable item that could only be used once, and that was why he had been so hesitant to unleash it.

The burly man thrust both palms forcefully through the air, and the fiery lotus flower drifted toward Han Li at a deceptively fast speed, reaching no more than 1,000 feet away from him in the blink of an eye.

All of a sudden, balls of azure flames erupted from the fiery lotus flower before hurtling toward Han Li in a frenzy.

Han Li naturally wasn't going to allow those flames to come into contact with his body, and the Heavy Water True Axis had already positioned itself in front of him at his behest.

He began to chant and incantation, and a burst of black light erupted out of the axis as it hovered in front of the fiery lotus flower like a huge black shield.

However, even after coming into contact with the Heavy Water True Axis, the Phosphorus Bone Flame wasn't snuffed out. Instead, it quickly enveloped the entire axis while releasing a scorching aura.

Han Li could feel a burst of extremely strange power surging through his Heavy Water True Axis, and it seemed to have been causing the heavy water to evaporate, reducing the weight of the axis as a result.

The weight reduction was virtually negligible, but Han Li's heart still jolted slightly upon detecting this. If he didn't clear away these azure flames as quickly as possible, he didn't know what other impact it was going to have on his Heavy Water True Axis.

With that in mind, he extended a hand forward, and a tiny fiery silver figure took shape on the palm of his hand. It turned around to give him a wide smile, then skipped down from his hand and transformed into a wave of silver fire that swooped onto the Heavy Water True Axis to intertwine itself with the Phosphorus Bone Flames.

The silver and azure flames intertwined on the surface of the axis, and to the Phosphorus Bone Flame's credit, it was able to temporarily hold its own against the Essence Fire Raven, with neither one able to devour the other.

Chapter 288: Saved in the Nick of Time

While the Flame of Essence and the Phosphorus Bone Flame were locked in battle against one another, Han Li made a hand seal with one hand, then produced an azure longsword with a flick of his wrist, and he emerged from behind the Heavy Water True Axis before charging directly toward the burly man.

The burly man immediately switched to a different hand seal upon seeing this, and balls of azure flames erupted out of the fiery azure lotus flower before hurtling toward Han Li.

In response, Han Li slashed his longsword through the air, unleashing a string of sword projections that bloomed like a lotus flower in front of him to repel the azure fireballs.

This flame was supposed to have been extremely sticky, as evidenced by the fact that it was able to instantly cling to the Heavy Water True Axis, but it was unable to adhere to the azure longsword at all, much to the burly man's surprise.

He gritted his teeth before expelling a mouthful of blood essence, then pointed a finger at it, and the ball of blood essence instantly transformed into a cloud of blood mist that vanished into the fiery azure lotus flower in a flash.

The fiery lotus flower instantly began to rapidly revolve, and all of its petals trembled before shooting through the air, transforming into a series of fiery azure blades that swept toward Han Li in an all-encompassing wave.

Han Li made a hand seal with one hand in an unhurried manner while slashing his sword through the air with his other hand, instantly releasing countless massive sword projections that shot forth toward the burly man.

The wave of sword projections appeared to have been quite chaotic, like a disorganized army with no general, hurtling through the air in a seemingly haphazard fashion, but somehow, they were able to keep all of the fiery azure blades at bay.

For the second time, a hint of foreboding welled up in the burly man's heart, and he decided that it was too much of a risk to continue this battle. With that in mind, he switched to a different hand seal before clapping his hand together.

A resounding boom rang out as the fiery azure lotus flower swelled to several times its original size, following which all of its petals exploded violently, creating a sea of azure flames that swallowed up the entire wave of sword projections.

All of a sudden, the entire sky was filled with sword projections and azure flames, sending waves of scorching heat and an aura of unmatched sharpness erupting in all directions.

After doing all of this, the burly man brought his index and middle fingers together without any hesitation, and a golden talisman was set alight between his fingertips, following which he vanished from the spot amid a flash of golden light.

However, a massive azure longsword then suddenly appeared out of thin air several dozen kilometers away, and the burly man within the streak of golden light struck the blade of the longsword with unerring accuracy, having his body instantly sliced into two.

Immediately thereafter, a purple nascent soul that was identical in appearance to the burly man emerged from his body before flying away with a terrified look on its face, only to be caught in a large silver net before it was able to get very far.

A burst of crackling rang out as the nascent soul was zapped into a plume of smoke that was blown away by the wind.

Even in the instant right before he died, the burly man had no idea how Han Li had been able to cover a distance of dozens of kilometers in the blink of an eye to intercept him.

As it turned out, it was very simple. In the instant that the burly man detonated his Phosphorus Bone Flame, Han Li had already activated his Reversal True Axis ability to enhance his own speed, allowing him to cover a vast distance in the blink of an eye.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to stow the azure longsword away, then made a beckoning motion toward the burly man's corpse, and the man's storage bracelet and storage ring quickly flew into his grasp.

After taking a moment to inspect the contents of the storage treasures, he was very pleased to find that he had made a very good haul, and he stowed them storage treasures away before flying back toward his Heavy Water True Axis.

Without the support of the burly man's immortal spiritual power, the Phosphorus Bone Flame was no match for the Essence Fire Raven and had already been devoured. At this moment, the Essence Fire Raven was in its miniature humanoid form, and it was seated on the Heavy Water True Axis while swinging its little legs back and forth with a blissful look on its face.

Upon spotting Han Li's return, it immediately reverted back into the form of a silver fire raven before flying toward him.

Han Li smiled as he raised an arm so that the fire raven could fly back into his sleeve.

He then turned his gaze toward the giant puppet to find that both the Holy Puppet Sect and Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators there had already suffered severe casualties.

There were several Ubiquitous Pavilion Grand Ascension and Body Integration cultivators that had snuck away from the battle before flying toward the giant puppet, hoping to destroy it so that the light barrier encompassing the main island would be unraveled.

However, before they could even get close, the giant puppet suddenly swiveled its body to face them, and the runes on its giant silver blade lit up before releasing gusts of fierce wind that swept directly toward the oncoming intruders.

The gusts of wind were carrying countless blades of wind, and it swept up the nearest few Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators in the blink of an eye.

Those cultivators hurriedly summoned their protective treasures, but they were only able to keep the blades of wind at bay for a few moments before their bodies were torn to shreds, while their nascent souls were only just barely able to escape.

Seeing as the giant puppet was able to protect itself just fine, Han Li began flying over to Qilin 9 with his Heavy Water True Axis trailing along behind him.

At this point in the battle, the situation had become quite dire for Qilin 9.

After transforming into that woman in the red dress, not only had the voluptuous woman had her cultivation base elevated, even her abilities had undergone a drastic change.

Furthermore, that red oil paper umbrella of hers was extremely troublesome to deal with, able to release thin red threads down upon anyone situated under it, and if one were to be ensnared by those red threads, their immortal spiritual power circulation would become very sluggish.

Thankfully, the dazzling light radiating from his nine star golden sword had formed a protective barrier around him to keep the red threads at bay, so he was able to remain largely unaffected.

At this point, the golden tiger that had been released from the antiquated golden mirror was already riddled with wounds, but it was still constantly prowling by his side, protecting him from any potential sneak attacks from his two assailants.

The giant azure python released by the thin old man earlier had already been torn to shreds by the golden tiger, and it was clear that he intended to claim the golden mirror to make up for that loss after Qilin 9 was killed.

"We have to end this now!"

The woman in red had already noticed that Han Li was approaching, and a hint of killing intent flashed through her eyes as she encircled her arms in an embracing motion to summon a crimson lute that was as translucent as jade.

She began to gently strum the strings of the lute, producing a sound that immediately made Qilin 9's skin crawl.

It wasn't because the sound was extremely unpleasant. Instead, it was a very crisp and clean sound that was very pleasing to the ears, but as soon as the woman began playing the lute, the oil paper umbrella above Qilin 9 suddenly swelled to twice its original size.

The crimson threads trailing down from the umbrella were also becoming denser, and they were pouncing at him like a nest of spirit snakes, moving at several times their original speed.

At the same time, the thin old man had also sprung into action. He raised a hand to release a three-colored ring, which flew through the air before transforming into countless three-colored ring projections to ensnare the golden dragon.

Meanwhile, the thin old man himself appeared above Qilin 9 in a wraith-like manner, then swept a sleeve through the air, sending a streak of dazzling swordlight that was over 100 feet in length sweeping down toward him.

Qilin 9 had no choice but to divert the golden mirror away to ward off the oncoming streak of sword light, but as a result, his back was left unguarded, and several red threads pierced into his shoulder and back in quick succession.

As soon as the red threads pierced into his body, they immediately began to sprout branches that burrowed into his flesh like the roots of a plant.

Qilin 9 immediately felt a numb sensation spread through his shoulder and arm, and even more alarmingly, his immortal spiritual power had become extremely sluggish.

Right at this moment, he spotted a black shadow hurtling toward him out of the corner of his eye, and right as he was about to use a life-saving talisman to save himself from this dire situation, a glowing black wheel flashed through the air in front of him inches away from his chest to shield him from the oncoming dark green dagger.

Immediately thereafter, a figure arrived by his side in the blink of an eye, and with a sweep of their sword, all of the red threads that had burrowed into his body were instantly severed.

Those severed threads quickly turned a lifeless gray color like vines that had been stripped of their nutrients, and Qilin 9's immortal spiritual power circulation returned to normal.

"I owe you one, Fellow Daoist!" Qilin 9 said in a solemn voice as he took a glance at Han Li.

"Let's focus on taking care of these two before we talk about anything else," Han Li said.

Qilin 9 nodded in response, and he flexed his shoulder to find that the numb sensation from before had already completely faded.

Meanwhile, the thin old man and the woman in red had also convened together, and as they exchanged a glance, each of them could see their own astonishment mirrored in one another's eyes.

They had deemed Han Li to have been the weaker one of their two opponents, yet not only had he just slain their companion in a very short time, he had also managed to ward off both of their attacks on his own, seemingly with ease.

"I'm not staying around to fight a losing battle," the thin old man sighed, then immediately sped away as a streak of light without any hesitation.

"Sly old bastard..." the woman in red cursed under her breath.

Having used that human skin tattoo treasure, she had already severely depleted her immortal spiritual power, and she had thought that at the very least, she and the thin old man would've been able to kill Qilin 9 to reap some spoils, but their plan had been foiled by Han Li.

With the thin old man fleeing for his life, she naturally wasn't going to stay and take on Han Li's duo on her own.

Thus, the red oil paper umbrella suddenly flew back to her at her behest, then carried her away at an incredible speed.

Chapter 289: Negotiations Falling Through

Qilin 9 was furious, and he was naturally unwilling to let his two assailants get away. "You think you can just attack me as you please, then leave when you see fit?"

As soon as his voice trailed off, he flipped a hand over to produce a golden talisman before waving it through the air, and the talisman immediately burst into golden flames, which transformed into an expanse of light that enveloped his entire body.

Immediately thereafter, he vanished from the spot without any warning, and through his spiritual sense, Han Li was able to detect that he had teleported to several thousand kilometers away to intercept the woman in red.

He then cast his gaze toward the direction that the thin old man was fleeing in with a hint of mockery in his eyes.

In the next instant, he withdrew his Heavy Water True Axis back into his body, following which arcs of silver lightning emerged around him, then erupted all around him to form a lightning array that was around 10 feet in radius in the blink of an eye.

Tens of thousands of kilometers away, the thin old man was flying through the air above the Thunderstorm Sea with his entire body enveloped in a murky layer of light.

"That was some terrible luck! Why did I have to run into those two freaks? If I hadn't escaped when I did, I would've died back there!"

All of a sudden, the old man's brows suddenly furrowed tightly, following which he drew to an abrupt halt before shooting back over 10,000 feet in retreat.

A burst of loud rumbling rang out in the sky ahead of him, and a vast expanse of lightning emerged out of thin air before transforming into a circular lightning array.

Countless arcs of lightning flashed incessantly amid a rumbling thunderclap, following which the lightning faded to reveal none other than Han Li.

"I've already made up my mind to take no further part in all of this. Seeing as we're both members of the Transient Guild, would you be able to let me go this time, Fellow Daoist?" the old man implored.

Han Li was in no hurry to strike, and he smiled as he replied, "There's no personal vendetta between us, so I'm not interested in a fight to the death, either, but you almost killed my companion just now, and I can't just let things slide. Shouldn't you be leaving something behind as compensation?"

"In that case, how do you want to settle this?" the thin old man asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"If I'm not mistaken, that's a 30,000-year-old Thistle Spirit Flower that I'm sensing on you, right?" Han Li asked with a smile.

Back when the trio of Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators first arrived on the island, Han Li had already sensed that the thin old man was carrying 30,000-year-old Thistle Spirit Flower thanks to his enormous spiritual sense, and right there and then, he had decided that this was something he was definitely going to secure as the stamen of the Thistle Spirit Flower was one of the ingredients listed on his dao pill recipe.

The thin old man's expression instantly darkened slightly upon hearing this.

He was indeed carrying a Thistle Spirit Flower on his body, and due to the fact that it was a live specimen, he couldn't put it in his storage bracelet. On top of that, he had obtained the flower not long before coming on this mission, so he had temporarily stored it in a special jade box.

However, he had already cast several seals onto the jade box, so no one should've been able to detect it.

Could it be that this man possesses spiritual sense superior even to that of a Golden Immortal?

The old man's heart jolted slightly as this thought occurred to him, but he then dismissed the notion.

Han Li's aura suggested that he was only at the mid-True Immortal Stage, so in the old man's eyes, there was no way that his spiritual sense could've been so formidable. Instead, he was most likely carrying some type of special treasure that allowed him to detect spirit medicines.

With that in mind, the old man swept his spiritual sense through the surrounding area to ensure that there was no one else nearby, then unleashed his enormous aura in full force as a cold smile appeared on his face. "You're biting off more than you can chew, Fellow Daoist! Do you really think you can just walk all over me as you please?"

Han Li had already identified that the one among the trio with the highest cultivation base wasn't that burly man at all, nor was it that voluptuous woman. Instead, it was this sly old man who had been concealing his true power this entire time.

Instead of attacking Han Li right away, the old man had initially tried to avoid a battle by putting on a façade of weakness, so it was clear that he was someone who held no regard for his own dignity and prioritized survival and profit above all else.

If he had been willing to give up his Thistle Spirit Flower, Han Li would've naturally been happy to avoid unnecessary bloodshed, but seeing as the negotiations had fallen through, a battle was unavoidable.

There was no one else present, and Han Li was confident that he would be able to take down his opponent in a one-on-one battle.

With that in mind, he made a hand seal with both hands, and his Heavy Water True Axis instantly appeared behind him amid a flash of black light, then rose up while revolving rapidly before hurtling toward the old man at his behest.

A series of black ripples that were visible to the naked eye spread through the air in the wake of the axis, and it was as if they were threatening to tear the very space apart.

The thin old man spread his hands open to summon a three-colored ring upon seeing this, and the ring transformed into a vast expanse of ring projections that sped toward the Heavy Water True Axis.

However, the Heavy Water True Axis was far heavier than he imagined, and it was able to tear through the countless layers of ring projections with unstoppable force before crashing into the ring itself with a loud clang.

The three-colored ring was only able to hold itself intact for an instant before exploding into pieces, and the thin old man shuddered from the backlash as an unnatural flush appeared on his face.

At the same time, he made a grabbing motion with one hand, and a large yellow flag that was over 20 feet in length appeared in his grasp.

The image of a vast desert with three suns hanging above it was emblazoned onto the flag, and it was giving off a parched and scorching aura.

The old man took a step forward with his hands clenched tightly around the flag's shaft, then swept the flag forcefully through the air.

The surface of the flag rippled as a vast expanse of yellow sand surged forth in a frenzy, sweeping toward Han Li in an all-encompassing wave that inundated everything within a radius of close to 100,000 feet.

Han Li's eyes narrowed slightly as blue light flashed within them, but he was still unable to see his surroundings clearly. He felt as if he had been swallowed up in a sandstorm that was severely limiting both his visibility and his spiritual sense, rendering him unable to detect his opponent's location.

Right at this moment, the old man's voice suddenly rang out from behind him. "Have a taste of my Three Sun Pass!"

As soon as Han Li turned around, he immediately spotted three balls of dazzling white light hurtling rapidly toward him from three different directions, releasing waves of scorching heat as they raced through the air.

His brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he was just about to take some evasive measures when he suddenly noticed that he was unable to move.

He looked down to find that a layer of white crystals had crept over his calves without his detection, and it had frozen him to the spot like a layer of ice crystals.

Immediately thereafter, the same material began to appear over his shoulders, arms, and chest, and it was rapidly spreading over the rest of his body.

Upon closer inspection, he discovered that these were countless tiny grains of translucent sand that had been scorched into a semi-transparent crystalline material by the three suns. The material quickly spread to his neck, immobilizing his entire body.

Han Li was alarmed by this turn of events, but he didn't panic. Azure light surged over his body ,and he was just about to break free from the crystalline material when he spotted the thin old man abruptly appearing beside him, plunging a green dagger toward his glabella.

He gave a cold harrumph as a hint of golden light flashed through his eyes, and he released a burst of tremendous spiritual sense to encompass the entire surrounding area in a radius of several dozen kilometers.

The thin old man had already reached Han Li, but he noticed that a circle of extremely tiny runes had appeared around each of Han Li's pupils, and he reflexively slowed down as a safety precaution.

Right at this moment, Han Li's voice rang out with the volume of an enormous gong being struck. "Let heaven and earth be cleansed!"

His words were like an almighty decree, and all of the yellow sand immediately subsided. Even the dark clouds hanging in the sky had vanished, and it was as if the entire area really had been cleansed.

"Impossible!" the thin old man exclaimed with an astonished expression as he hurriedly darted back to open up some distance between himself and Han Li.

"Let heavenly fire descend!" Han Li declared, and a streak of white light descended upon him from the heavens, transforming into a burst of silver flames that enveloped his entire body.

"This is impossible! Not even a Golden Immortal can speak things into reality as they please! Who are you? Take the flower!" the thin old man yelled in a horrified voice while continuing to dart back in retreat?

A cold smile appeared on Han Li's face as he scoffed, "Don't you think it's too late to be saying this now? Let there be lightning!"

In the next instant, a vortex of dark clouds appeared in the sky out of thin air, and lightning was flashing incessantly within the vortex amid a string of rumbling thunderclaps.

All of a sudden, a bolt of blue lightning that was as thick as a water vat came crashing down upon the thin old man from above.

The old man hurriedly dodged to the side, yet he had only just barely evaded the first bolt of lightning when countless more came crashing down from the heavens like a relentless storm, cutting off all avenues for escape or retreat.

At this point, the old man was so shaken up that he had completely lost all will to fight, and as he continued to evade the bolts of lightning that were falling from the heavens, he had also summoned a golden talisman, which he was planning to use to facilitate his escape.

However, right at this moment, Han Li abruptly vanished from the spot, only to appear behind the old man without any warning in the next instant, and a layer of golden scales appeared over his arm as he plunged his hand straight through the old man's heart.

The golden light in his eyes then gradually faded as he withdrew his spiritual sense, and all of the blue lightning in the sky vanished to reveal the yellow sandstorm that had been raging this entire time.

"It was all an illusion..." the thin old man murmured to himself with a wry smile as the light in his eyes gradually began to fade.

However, a burst of golden light then erupted out of his glabella alongside a burst of powerful energy fluctuations.

At this point, the old man knew that he wouldn't be able to escape, and he had decided there and then to detonate his own nascent soul.

A cold gleam flashed through Han Li's eyes as a burst of silver light erupted out of his arm amid a loud thunderclap, and the eruption of silver lightning instantly destroyed the old man's nascent soul, following which his body fell completely limp and lifeless.

Chapter 290: Observation

Han Li's expression eased slightly upon seeing this, but at the same time, he was gasping for air.

It seemed that he had just made short work of his opponent, but in reality, the situation had been far more perilous than it had appeared. The layer of crystalline material that had trapped him was extremely resolute, and even with his tremendously powerful physical body and immense immortal spiritual power, it would've taken him at least five seconds to break free, which would've been more than enough to spell his demise.

If the old man had gone through with his attack, then Han Li would've been a sitting duck. While it was true that his physical body was immensely powerful, there was no way that his glabella would've been able to withstand a direct blow, and if his physical body had survived that attack, he would've most definitely suffered extremely severe injuries.

Hence, as a last gasp Hail Mary, he had unleashed his Mantra Domain ability to sow doubt into the heart of his opponent. After that, he had brought down that illusory streak of heavenly fire to act as a smokescreen for the Essence Fire Raven, which emerged to free him from the layer of crystalline substance while also convincing the old man that he truly did have the power to control everything in this space.

At that point, the old man had already completely lost his bearings, and Han Li pounced on the opportunity, using his Reversal True Axis ability to deal the killing blow.

It seemed that all of these True Immortal cultivators had some trump cards up their sleeves, so he would have to be more careful when facing them in battle from now on.

With that in mind, Han Li raised a hand, and a burst of azure light swept out of his sleeve before enveloping the old man's body so that it wouldn't fall into the sea. After that, he consumed a restorative pill, then sat down to meditate.

At this point, only fewer than 40 of the Time Dao Runes on his Mantra Treasured Axis had been recovered, and using the Reversal True Axis in succession had severely taxed both his body and his immortal spiritual power.

A short while later, he reopened his eyes and cast his gaze toward the body of the thin old man, and after some brief searching, he found a long green jade box and an azure tiger mask tucked under the collar of the old man's robes.

There were several golden and purple talismans adhered to the jade box for the purpose of concealing the aura of the spirit plant inside, and Han Li tore the talismans away before opening the box to reveal a purple spirit flower with its roots still completely intact.

The entire flower was brimming with spiritual qi, and just its aroma alone was enough to instill within him a soothing sense of relaxation.

It's not quite old enough to be used, but it certainly is a Thistle Spirit Flower that's over 30,000 years old.

The Thistle Spirit Flower was an extremely rare spirit plant that contained a hint of law powers, and even its seed wasn't something that could be found in the Transient Guild, so it was certainly a pleasant surprise for Han Li to have secured one on this mission.

If it weren't for the sake of this flower, he wouldn't have bothered to come after the thin old man at all. His mission was solely to protect the Holy Puppet Sect, and he certainly didn't care if any of the invaders were to escape.

After closing the jade box, he placed the removed talismans back onto it as well, then added a couple of golden talismans of his own before carefully tucking it away under the collar of his robe.

After that, he took a closer look at the azure tiger mask to find that it bore the number "11", which was the same as the number on Bai Suyuan's mask, indicating that he wasn't a cultivator from anywhere near the Ancient Cloud Continent.

Han Li was just about to destroy the mask when a thought suddenly occurred to him, and he decided to preserve the mask and stow it away instead.

After that, he also took the old man's storage bracelet, as well as that yellow flag and his other treasures, then flew back toward the island.

It hadn't been very long since he left the island, and the battle nearby was still raging.

However, Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators had somehow added around a dozen more Grand Ascension cultivators to their ranks, and due to the absence of Han Li and Qilin 9, they were able to completely dominate the Holy Puppet Sect cultivators, who were on the verge of being wiped out.

Han Li was able to assess the situation from afar with his spiritual sense, so as soon as he arrived on the scene, he immediately charged into the fray, killing all of the Ubiquitous Pavilion Grand Ascension cultivators in a matter of moments, and all of the other Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators immediately fled the scene in a blind panic.

All of the Holy Puppet Sect cultivators had thought that this was where their lives were going to come to an end, and they were ecstatic to see Han Li reversing their fortunes with ease. Their morale was instantly elevated to unprecedented heights, and they lashed out at the remaining Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators to completely drive them off the island.

Meanwhile, Han Li flew over to the giant puppet, then looked around to find Qilin 9 flying back to the island from afar. Along the way, he slew several dozen Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators, then quickly arrived beside Han Li.

He was carrying multiple injuries, and his clothes had become quite tattered, clearly indicating that he had just endured a rough battle as well.

"That woman had quite a few tricks up her sleeve. In the end, I was able to destroy her physical body, but her nascent soul managed to get away," Qilin 9 said in a slightly disappointed voice.

"If she had so many tricks up her sleeve, then surely she would've been quite wealthy as well, so you must've reaped some substantial spoils, right, Fellow Daoist Qilin 9?" Han Li asked with a smile.

"She did have some treasures and materials, but nothing all that valuable," Qilin 9 replied in an ambiguous manner to gloss over the subject.

Right at this moment, a resounding boom suddenly rang out from the sea toward the east, causing the nearby space to tremble violently.

Immediately thereafter, the colorful light barrier above the main island flashed a few times before disintegrating into countless specks of light that then faded into nothingness.

The glowing pagoda beside Han Li and Qilin 9 also flashed a few times before it completely dimmed.

"It looks like the Ubiquitous Pavilion has come extremely well prepared. We've managed to guard our island, but some other islands have fallen," Qilin 9 sighed.

"The situation is looking a little grim," Han Li replied with a nod.

"Do you think we should do something, Fellow Daoist?" Qilin 9 asked.

"I don't recall receiving any instructions other than to protect this island," Han Li replied.

"That's exactly right! We've been tasked with protecting this island, so it would be wise for us not to leave our post and just observe the battle for now," Qilin 9 chuckled.

Han Li gave an ambiguous nod in response, then cast his gaze toward the main island with blue light flashing in his eyes.

All of the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators were ecstatic to see that the light barrier encompassing the main island had disappeared, and they took a moment to reorganize their ranks before converging toward the main island.

That was the foundation of the Holy Puppet Sect, so if they wanted to reap the best spoils, then that was the place that they had to go.

After a brief respite, the battle continued at an even higher degree of ferocity than before.

A string of deafening booms instantly rang out across the sky above the main island, and even the main island itself was trembling incessantly in the wake of the powerful clashes taking place above it, looking as if it could collapse at any moment.

Due to the uneven distribution of forces on the battlefield, some of the parts of the defensive line where the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators had a numbers advantage were quickly overwhelmed, and the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators there immediately swooped down toward the main island.

Some of the bolder individuals among them had gone straight past the outermost level of the island and descended onto the second and even the third levels of the island.

However, all of the restrictions and traps laid out on the island were quickly triggered, and all of the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators that had stormed recklessly onto the main island were instantly met with a ferocious barrage of attacks.

Meanwhile, the black spirit boats in the dark clouds up above were also beginning to rapidly descend toward the island.

As for the mechanical boats that had been attacking them earlier, their defenses were too frail, and their attacks were lacking in variety, so they were only able to destroy two of the black spirit boats before all of them were wiped out.

Two of the black spirit boats were descending toward a wide river on the main island, yet before the pair of spirit boats had even landed on the surface of the water, the river down below had begun churning violently as if the water had been brought to a boil.

Right at this moment, around a dozen incredibly thick black chains shot out of the river, clanging loudly as they hurtled toward the pair of black spirit boats. The massive metal anchors attached to the ends of the chains easily passed through the protective barriers around the boats before plunging straight into the boats themselves.

Immediately thereafter, the sound of grinding gears rang out from the riverbed down below, while the two spirit boats shuddered violently as all of the runes on their surfaces lit up at once as they attempted to rise up with all their might to struggle free from the chains.

All of a sudden, a layer of blue light appeared over the chains, and countless tiny runes emerged from the blue light, releasing a burst of tremendous power that fused the chains and the entire river into one. It was as if the entire river were dragging down the pair of spirit boats rather than just the dozen or so chains.

The sound of mechanical grinding continued to ring out as the pair of spirit boats were slowly brought down further and further before falling into the water, where they exploded into pieces with an almighty boom.

Not far away, around a dozen turtle puppets had assembled themselves into a line, and the spirit patterns on their shells were glowing brightly as they raised their heads up high, releasing pillars of blue light out of their mouths toward the descending spirit boats and Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators up above.

The entire island had been plunged into a state of complete chaos, and all of the Holy Puppet Sect cultivators that were fighting in the air immediately descended to reinforce the main island.

Several dozen Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators had appeared on the plaza on the main island, and they were led by a pair of True Immortal cultivators as they engaged the Holy Puppet Sect cultivators on the island in a fierce battle.

Bai Suyuan's cultivation base wasn't very advanced, and at the moment, she was hanging back in the crowd, holding a silver longsword in one hand and a life-saving talisman given to her Yun Ni in the other as she inspected her surroundings with a wary expression.

As soon as the battle ensued on the main island, even more puppets began to enter the fray, and as a result, the Holy Puppet Sect forces were suddenly vastly outnumbering the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators, making it appear as if the tide were about to turn.

Chapter 291: Enemy Reinforcements

High up in the sky, the battle between the most powerful forces for both sides had also reached white-hot intensity.

The swordsman by the name of Lu Ji was standing in mid-air, and his robes were flapping audibly in the wind. Sword qi was surging throughout the entire area over 10,000 feet in front of him, and countless streaks of swordlight of different colors had converged in one place, forming what appeared to have been a pond of sword qi in the air.

Directly across from Lu Ji was a vast expanse of pristine white light, within countless translucent snow lotus flower projections were in full bloom, releasing a floral aroma that reached far and wide.

In the area where the two places were connected, sword qi and floral projections were clashing incessantly, sending powerful energy fluctuations erupting in all directions.

It was as if there were countless pairs of flower scissors ravaging the sea of flowers, but it also looked as if there were countless crystalline flowers constantly blunting the edges of the flower scissors.

It was quite a splendid sight to behold, but it was just as perilous as it was beautiful, and any cultivators below the Golden Immortal Stage would've been torn to shreds if they were to get between the pair of combatants.

As for the two combatants themselves, it appeared as if they weren't doing much, but in reality, both of them were rapidly burning through their immortal spiritual power, and if either side were to run out of immortal spiritual power, they would immediately be overwhelmed by the sword array or the floral sea unleashed by the other.

"You're clearly not a member of the Holy Puppet Sect, so why are you willing to go so far for them? We can give you just as much compensation as the Holy Puppet Sect has. As long as you're willing to stay your hand, you'll be compensated accordingly," Lu Ji said as he continued to control his sword array.

Yun Ni had used her Transient Guild mask to adopt an extremely seductive female appearance, and she giggled, "There's no need for such a strong and handsome sword immortal like yourself to talk about compensating me. If you’re willing to come into my snow lotus flower and have a good time with me, I'd even be willing to turn around and fight the Holy Puppet Sect by your side!"

Despite her carefree facade, she was actually quite concerned about the current situation. Her opponent's power level was on par with hers, and if things were to continue like this, it was very difficult to say what the outcome of this battle was going to be.

"If you're unwilling to accept my goodwill, then you can die!" Lu Ji harrumphed coldly.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he made a strange hand seal with one hand, then pointed it at the hilt of his sword, and the sword instantly released a draconic roar.

The pond of sword qi before instantly began to churn violently, and all of the sword qi came together to form a rainbow-colored wyrm that pounced directly at Yun Ni.

Yun Ni had also switched to a different hand seal, and countless white flower petals rose up from within the vast snow lotus flower field before her, forming a floral wave that surged toward the oncoming sword qi wyrm.

Meanwhile, the scar-faced man by the name of Xue Han was situated several thousand kilometers away, and yellow light was pouring incessantly out of his sleeves, forming a series of yellow halos that flew directly forward.

The yellow halos descended upon the gray-robed daoist priest puppet, which swept its horsetail whisk through the air to release countless translucent white threads that spread through the surrounding area like translucent steel needles to keep all of the yellow halos at bay.

At the same time, the puppet removed the silver gourd strapped to its waist with its other hand before tossing it up into the air.

The silver gourd immediately rose up into the sky, rapidly swelling to almost the size of a house during its ascent. The spirit patterns on its surface also began to glow brightly as bursts of dull thunderclaps rang out from within.

Immediately thereafter, the stopper of the gourd was abruptly removed, and it released a flurry of silver lightning directly at Xue Han, illuminating the entire sky with silver radiance.

At the same time, blue light flashed behind the daoist priest puppet, and Bai Fengyi rushed out of the blue light before sweeping her sleeves through the air to conjure up a pair of giant blue light barriers that hurtled toward Xue Han from two different directions, one from the left and one from the right.

Xue Han was completely unfazed as he raised a hand in an unhurried manner, and a yellow bead rose up into the air before exploding to release countless specks of yellow light that encompassed the entire area within a radius of over 1,000 feet around him.

The blue light barriers and the silver lightning arrived in unison, yet they were completely kept at bay by the yellow light as if it were an impregnable fortress.

Bai Fengyi's face was looking rather pale. Xue Han was far more powerful than her and the daoist priest puppet, and even the two of them combined were only just barely able to keep him occupied.

However, thankfully, the Holy Puppet Sect had gained a clear upper hand in the battle taking place on the main island, so as long as she and Yun Ni could keep the two enemy Golden Immortals occupied until the outcome of the battle on the main island was decided, then they would've been successful in their defense.

Inside the yellow light, Xue Han wasn't struggling in the slightest as he said with a mocking sneer, "If you're trying to stall us in order to buy time for the other cultivators of your sect, then I'm afraid I'll have to disappoint you."

He flipped a hand over as he spoke to summon a palm-sized dark azure linen pouch, upon which was embroidered the character for "fortune" in an ancient script, and it didn't appear to have been remarkable in any way.

He laid a hand onto the pouch while chanting an incantation, and the empty pouch immediately swelled like a balloon, with countless little bulges appearing on its surface as if it had been crammed full with beans.

A hint of foreboding instantly welled up in Bai Fengyi's heart upon seeing this, and she hurriedly injected more power into the pair of blue light barriers to exert more pressure on Xue Han.

However, the mocking sneer on Xue Han's face only grew more pronounced, and in the next instant, the opening of the linen pouch abruptly sprang open at his behest as countless pea-like azure beans came flooding out of the pouch before raining down upon the main island of the Holy Puppet Sect.

Upon landing on the ground, all of the azure beans rapidly swelled in size before taking on the form of warriors clad in suits of azure armor.

Their height and appearance were no different from the average person, but all of them were identical in appearance. Furthermore, all of them wore the same wooden expression, and their bodies were riddled with patterns that were glowing with azure light. The only thing that set them apart was the weapons that they wielded, of which there was a great deal of variety.

Before long, thousands of these azure-armored warriors had appeared all over the main island to engage the Holy Puppet Sect cultivators and puppets in battle.

These warriors moved extremely quickly and were far more agile than the average puppet, and they were able to quickly adapt to their environment, regardless of whether they were fighting in the mountains or in the rivers.

The Holy Puppet Sect cultivators were greatly alarmed to see so many new opponents appearing on the battlefield at once, and the tide of the battle was quickly turning against their favor.

All of a sudden, it was the Holy Puppet Sect cultivators who were forced onto the back foot.

In contrast with the chaos unfolding on the main island, the surrounding array islands had been completely abandoned by the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators.

After all, all of the spirit stones and treasures were on the main island, and now that the main island had been exposed, no one was going to waste any more time and effort attacking the array islands.

"I didn't think the enemy would deploy Dao Warriors into the battle," Han Li mused as he observed the main island from afar with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes.

"It looks like the Holy Puppet Sect is truly in severe trouble," Qilin 9 sighed.

While the two of them were speaking with one another, Qi Heng emerged from the entrance of the round pagoda with a grim look on his face, then cupped his fist toward Han Li's duo in a salute as he said, "There's no need to defend this array island any longer, seniors. Please go to the main island to join the battle there, and I'll be with you shortly."

As he was speaking, he took a subtle glance at Han Li, and a peculiar look flashed through his eyes.

Han Li paid no heed to this as he exchanged a glance with Qilin 9 before nodding in response.

They were being hired by the Holy Puppet Sect, and according to the rules of the Transient Guild, they had to carry out the requests of those who had hired them.

Thus, the two of them heeded Qi Heng's call and flew toward the main island.

They had only just flown several hundred kilometers when they heard a burst of loud rumbling ring out from behind them, and they hurriedly turned to discover that the giant puppet on the array island had suddenly begun to move.

It had stepped into the sea and was wading through the water toward the main island, churning up massive waves as it did so.

All of the giant puppets on the other array island that hadn't been destroyed were currently also converging toward the main island.

At this moment, on the plaza on the main island, several hundred azure-armored Dao Warriors and several dozen Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators were locked in battle against several dozen Holy Puppet Sect cultivators and close to 100 silver-armored puppets. Many of the surrounding buildings had already been razed to the ground, and the area was littered with dismembered body parts, presenting a grisly sight to behold.

Meanwhile, Bai Suyuan had also been forced to one corner of the plaza alongside a Holy Puppet Sect elder and around a dozen disciples by over 100 Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators.

At this moment, she was holding a silver longsword in one hand, and there was a white jade bracelet around her other wrist. The life-saving talisman given to her by Yun Ni was already pressed against her wrist, and she could activate it any moment with an injection of magic power.

At this moment, she was looking up at the sky with a concerned expression, and the white jade bracelet around her wrist was releasing a white halo that encompassed her entire body. Furthermore, she had also put on a white veil garment that was releasing specks of silver light outside of her original clothes.

On her belt beneath the veil garment was a square azure peachwood talisman that was riddled with glowing spirit patterns.

The peachwood talisman was a gift from Bai Fengyi, and it was a defensive treasure of a very high caliber, one that could withstand an all-out attack from an early-True Immortal cultivator.

However, it would only be able to withstand that single attack, after which its usefulness would be severely diminished, or it could be disabled altogether, so she wasn't going to use it unless she absolutely had to.

A tall Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivator was staring intently at Bai Suyuan as he yelled, "That masked woman is carrying a bunch of really strong treasures! Let's take her down and split everything among us!"

Greedy looks appeared in the eyes of all of the surrounding Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators upon hearing this, and all of them began to converge toward that corner of the plaza.

As a result, the chaotic plaza was plunged into even more chaos and disarray.

Chapter 292: Saved

In the face of all of the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators charging toward her, Bai Suyuan made a hand seal with one hand while slashing her sword upward, and countless silver threads instantly shot out of the tip of her sword before flying in all directions.

The space in the wake of the silver threads twisted and blurred, and three Body Integration cultivators instantly had their bodies completely dismembered, having been caught off guard by the attack.

A string of sharp clangs rang out as all of the surrounding Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators hurriedly adopted defensive measures to keep the silver threads at bay, not daring to get any closer.

Right at this moment, a streak of black light flew through the air overhead, following which a figure wielding an inky-black spear was revealed.

The figure was giving off the aura of a Grand Ascension cultivator, and he was swooping down toward Bai Suyuan like lightning.

Bai Suyuan's reactions were quite sharp, and she immediately pierced her sword directly upward to strike the tip of the oncoming spear.

However, to her surprise, the black spear abruptly melted into a liquid form, then flowed down the silver longsword toward her arm.

At the same time, her silver longsword was fizzling incessantly as if it were being severely corroded, and plumes of white smoke were rising up amid erratic flashes of spiritual light.

Bai Suyuan was quite startled by this, and she hurriedly tried to shake the black liquid off her sword, but the liquid was unexpectedly sticky and continued to flow toward the hilt of the sword, despite her best efforts to keep it at bay.

In this dire situation, she decisively tossed the longsword aside, then retreated back to over 1,000 feet away.

However, right at this moment, a burst of yellow light erupted out of the ground, then transformed into a thick vine that was enveloped in azure light before attempting to wind itself around her legs and her waist.

The white veil garment that she was wearing instantly began to glow with dazzling white light, conjuring up a light barrier to keep the vine at bay.

Meanwhile, Bai Suyuan summoned a white handkerchief with a flick of her wrist before waving it at the azure vine.

There was a crescent-shaped moon embroidered onto the white handkerchief, around which were a series of cloud-like spirit patterns that were rippling with moonlight.

As she swept the handkerchief through the air, the spirit patterns on the handkerchief began to glow brightly, releasing faint moonlight that surged along the azure vine to ensnare it tightly.

Immediately thereafter, the light on the handkerchief flashed at Bai Suyuan's behest, and the entire azure vine was instantly turned to stone before being reduced to dust by a gentle sweep of her hand.

The Grand Ascension cultivator that was charging toward her stopped in his tracks upon seeing this, seemingly a little wary of Bai Suyuan's treasures.

The greed in the eyes of the other Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators became even more pronounced at the sight of her formidable treasures, but many of them had moved back to open up some distance between her and themselves.

They could see that she still had many trump cards up her sleeve, so it definitely wasn't a good idea to rush in head-on. Hence, everyone was waiting for her to be worn down before they swooped in for the kill.

Bai Suyuan swept her gaze across her surroundings, and her heart immediately sank.

The situation was far from encouraging. Most of the Holy Puppet Sect's elders and disciples were either dead or severely wounded, and at this rate, they weren't going to be able to hold off the enemy for much longer.

A gim look appeared in her eyes upon seeing this, and she injected a wisp of magic power into the talisman that was adhered to her wrist.

The talisman immediately began to release golden light that enveloped her entire body, and she abruptly vanished from the spot.

However, almost at the exact same moment, the space nearby shuddered, and a golden light barrier appeared. A humanoid figure crashed into the light barrier before falling to the ground, revealing itself to be none other than Bai Suyuan.

After falling to the ground, she immediately scrambled to her feet, then swept a hand through the air to send the white handkerchief revolving around her.

There was an alarmed look in her eyes, and she hurriedly looked around to find that all of the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators were also looking very surprised, as if no one had any idea when this light barrier had been set up.

Right at this moment, a one-eyed elderly man with gray scales all over his face emerged from the back of the crowd. He was wearing a black cloak, and he cackled in a raspy voice, "This girl is mine, so I suggest all of you get back if you know what's good for you!"

Everyone immediately turned to discover that the old man was a True Immortal cultivator, so all of them had no choice but to do as they were told.

The most powerful Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators present aside from the old man were only at the Grand Ascension Stage, so no one dared to oppose him.

"You certainly don't see someone with the Moonlight Immortal Physique every day! I have a dual cultivation method that suits your constitution very well," the old man chuckled as he stroked his own chin while sizing up Bai Suyuan with a lustful look in his eyes.

Bai Suyuan couldn't help but shudder as a hint of disgust welled up in her heart, and she unconsciously tightened her grasp on the white handkerchief in her hand.

The old man licked his lips at the sight of this subtle gesture of hers, and he chuckled, "Resist all you want! It won't be any fun if you give up right away."

As soon as his voice trailed off, a gray talisman flew out of his sleeve with a flick of his wrist before adhering itself to Bai Suyuan's forehead in the blink of an eye.

The talisman was moving far too quickly for her to react, and her entire body was completely immobilized, while her magic power circulation also stagnated.

The one-eyed old man reached out toward Bai Suyuan with a sinister smile.

Even if he didn't reap any other spoils from this trip, Bai Suyuan alone would've already been an extremely prized acquisition.

Right as his hand was about to come into contact with Bai Suyuan's clothes, a loud thunderclap suddenly rang out in the sky, following which a burst of golden light plummeted out of the heavens before transforming into a shimmering golden flying sword.

A loud thump rang out as the flying sword pierced through the golden light barrier with ease, and the light barrier wasn't even able to slow it down in the slightest.

The old man was very alarmed by this, and he hurriedly darted back several thousand feet before coming to a stop, sending around a dozen Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators and azure-armored Dao Warriors toppling to the side as he did so.

A sharp clang rang out as the golden longsword pierced into the ground, unleashing powerful shockwaves that sent Bai Suyuan and all of the cultivators and puppets around her flying back through the air.

Immediately thereafter, two streaks of light descended in front of her out of the sky, revealing themselves to have been none other than Han Li's duo.

The one-eyed old man could see that Han Li and Qilin 9 were both True Immortals who weren't any less powerful than him, and he immediately fled the scene, not daring to linger any longer.

"What a coward!" Qilin 9 harrumphed coldly as he picked up his nine star golden sword and cast his gaze toward the fleeing old man, but displayed no intention of going after him.

Yun Ni was still locked in battle against Lu Ji in the sky, and despite the intensity of her battle, she had made sure to keep an eye on the main island this entire time. As soon as she noticed that Bai Suyuan was being targeted, she immediately used a secret technique to transmit a message to Qilin 9, imploring him to protect Qilin 11.

Qilin 9 and Han Li had only just arrived on the main island at the time, and upon receiving this message from Yun Ni, he immediately realized who Qilin 11 was, and thus, he had hurried onto the plaza with Han Li to save her.

Han Li took a glance at the immobilized Bai Suyuan, and even though he had already guessed that Qilin 3 was most likely none other than Yun Ni, he was still left feeling a little perplexed about why Bai Suyuan had come on this mission when she was only at the Grand Ascension Stage.

He raised a hand and gently wiped it over Bai Suyuan's forehead, releasing a burst of azure light that removed the gray talisman with ease.

Bai Suyuan shuddered and stumbled slightly before steadying herself, having been freed from the talisman's restraints.

She immediately approached Han Li's duo, then cupped her fist toward them in a salute as she said, "Thank you, fellow daoists."

Han Li and Qilin 9 merely nodded in response without saying anything.

The surrounding Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators naturally didn't dare to attack them, but the azure-armored Dao Warriors had no such inhibitions, and after eradicating the nearby Holy Puppet Sect cultivators, they immediately converged toward Han Li's duo.

In the blink of an eye, Han Li was surrounded by over 100 azure-armored Dao Warriors, all of which lashed out at him with their weapons.

A layer of golden scales appeared over Han Li's fists as he spun rapidly on the spot like a spinning top while simultaneously throwing punches in all directions to unleash a vast array of golden fist projections.

None of the azure-armored Dao Warriors were able to withstand more than a single blow, exploding into pieces as soon as they came into contact with any of the golden fist projections.

The pieces of the destroyed azure-armored Dao Warriors erupted through the air like shrapnel, punching large holes into the bodies of the Dao Warriors that were still yet to be eradicated.

At a rough visual estimate, Han Li determined that the physical constitution of these azure-armored Dao Warriors was roughly on par with that of the Golden Dao Warriors that he had fought against in the past, but these ones were faster and more agile.

At the same time, these Dao Warriors also seemed to have possessed stronger vitality, able to continue attacking without slowing down in the slightest even if their bodies had already been severely ravaged.

While Han Li continued to destroy more of the oncoming Dao Warriors, he was looking around with a hint of disappointment in his eyes. These Dao Warriors were just ordinary specimens, and there weren't any primary beans among them. Otherwise, he would've had another primary bean to plant.

Around two hours later, not only had the number of people on the plaza not decreased, it was only increasing further and further, with streaks of light rapidly converging from all directions.

The Holy Puppet Sect was in a dire situation, and all of its remaining forces were converging toward the plaza on the main island.

Chapter 293: Mystery Solved

A burst of dull rumbling rang out as a giant puppet that was close to 10,000 feet tall stepped over a mountain situated in front of the plaza, then staggered through the masses of azure-armored Dao Warriors en route to the plaza.

It was clear that the journey had been quite rough, as evidenced by the fact that many parts of its enormous body had already been severely ravaged, and a huge hole had appeared on its chest, while a large chunk of the giant silver blade that it was wielding was also missing.

Before it had even set foot onto the plaza, it was swarmed by over 100 azure-armored Dao Warriors that attacked it from all directions.

These attacks wouldn't have been able to inflict much damage, but having already endured so much on the way to the main island, the giant puppet was already a spent force, and it didn't take long before one of its massive legs was snapped down the middle with an almighty crack.

As a result, the giant puppet fell heavily onto the ground, and its massive head rolled toward the plaza like a huge boulder.

All of the cultivators in its path hurriedly took evasive measures, but some weren't quick enough to get away in time, and they were dealt severe injuries as they were sent flying back through the air.

The puppet's head continued to roll forward without displaying any signs of stopping, and Han Li finally decided to step in, rising up into the sky before sweeping a sleeve through the air to release a burst of white light, which flew in a circle around the puppet's head.

A resounding boom rang out as the seemingly unstoppable head was drawn to an abrupt halt, having sunk deep into the ground.

The round pagoda on the head was also already in ruins, revealing a series of long-dead bodies that belonged to the Holy Puppet Sect cultivators that had been controlling the giant puppet.

Han Li swept his gaze over the wreckage, then suddenly raised an eyebrow as he swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light, which removed a chunk of the pagoda's wall before dragging Qi Heng out from under the rubble.

Qi Heng's face was deathly pale, and blood was flowing out of all of his orifices, but he was still alive.

It appeared that he had been reduced to such a sorry state as he had severely overexerted his magic power while controlling the giant puppet.

Han Li descended out of the sky, then fed Qi Heng a yellow pill before pressing a glowing azure hand against Qi Heng's chest to help him digest and absorb the pill.

After that, he laid Qi Heng flat against the ground, and several elders and disciples immediately converged around him with concerned expressions.

Han Li turned to exchange a glance with Qilin 9, following which both of them took a glance up at the sky in unison, and they certainly weren't encouraged by what they saw.

There really wasn't much suspense left when it came to the battle taking place on the main island. With the assistance of the Dao Warriors, the cultivators of the Ubiquitous Pavilion had already seized the absolute upper hand, and the eight giant puppets of the Holy Puppet Sect had all been taken out.

Furthermore, over half of their True Immortal cultivators were either dead or wounded, while several of the Transient Guild cultivators were also missing, so they either fled the battle or met their demise as well.

In other words, if the Holy Puppet Sect didn't have any more tricks up its sleeve, the battle would draw to a conclusion before the outcome of the battle between the Golden Immortals in the sky was decided.

Right at this moment, a burst of yellow light exploded violently in the sky, sending bursts of terrifying shockwaves and gusts of ferocious wind sweeping several hundred kilometers in all directions.

A white figure then plummeted out of the sky before falling toward the plaza.

Close behind the white figure was a blue figure that hurriedly descended out of the heavens, then caught the white figure with a pained look on her face right before it smashed into the ground.

The white figure was none other than the daoist priest puppet that had been fighting alongside Bai Fengyi earlier, and it had been knocked out of the sky after shielding her from a particularly vicious attack from Xue Han.

Han Li took a glance at the puppet to find that the light in its eyes had completely faded, and its body wasn't giving off any spiritual fluctuations. Furthermore, a large hole had been blown straight through the center of its chest, clearly indicating that its core had been completely destroyed.

A grim look flashed through Bai Fengyi's eyes as she stowed the puppet away, then quickly made her way toward Bai Suyuan.

Bai Suyuan hesitated momentarily before approaching Bai Fengyi, and Han Li was rather befuddled upon seeing this.

Is there some type of connection between them as well?

"Are you alright?" Bai Fengyi asked.

Bai Suyuan nodded in response as she gestured to Han Li and Qilin 9 as she replied, "I'm fine. These two fellow daoists from our Transient Guild saved me in the nick of time."

Bai Fengyi cast her gaze toward Han Li and Qilin 9 upon hearing this, then gave the two of them a slight nod.

Han Li became even more convinced that Bai Suyuan had to have been related to this deputy sect master of the Holy Puppet Sect in some way upon seeing this.

"Li Feiyu..."

Right at this moment, a voice suddenly rang out in Han Li's mind, and he was rather alarmed, but remained composed as he subtly inspected the area around him. As it turned out, Qi Heng had woken up and was staring directly at him.

"Don't be alarmed, Fellow Daoist Li. I'm the one who's speaking to you right now."

With that, it was confirmed that Qi Heng was the voice communicating with Han Li through voice transmission.

"How did you recognize me?" Han Li asked.

"I don't recognize you, but I recognize that black wheel treasure of yours. I had the misfortune of facing that treasure in the Profound Ice Mountain Range, and in the end, you destroyed my physical body, with only my nascent soul managing to escape," Qi Heng explained.

Han Li was enlightened upon hearing this, then replied, "Ah, so you were the one back in the Profound Ice Mountain Range. No wonder I felt a sense of familiarity when I first saw you. Are you seeking vengeance for what happened back then?"

"That was originally my intention, but not only have you come to assist our Holy Puppet Sect in its hour of need, you also saved my life just now, so I can't bring myself to resent you any longer. Besides, with your powers, even if I were at my peak, I would still be no match for you," Qi Heng replied as a wry smile appeared on his face.

"I'm only assisting your Holy Puppet Sect for the sake of the mission reward, and all I did just now was dig you out from under some rubble, so if you want to seek vengeance, then you're free to do so. However, prior to that, I really want to know why you tried to abduct that disciple of our Blaze Dragon Dao," Han Li said.

"To be honest, that was all just a misunderstanding. That female disciple is a descendant of Deputy Sect Master Bai, and I was acting under orders to bring her to the Holy Puppet Sect," Qi Heng explained with a resigned expression.

"In that case, why did you ambush her in the Profound Ice Mountain Range instead of visiting our sect and openly declaring your intentions?" Han Li asked.

"Deputy Sect Master Bai instructed me to carry out this task in secret, but I was never told why," Qi Heng explained.

Han Li was left feeling rather speechless upon hearing this. Such a minor misunderstanding had almost led to the demise of a True Immortal, and it felt a little absurd.

A thought then suddenly occurred to him, and he hurriedly asked, "What is your deputy sect master's name?"

"Bai Fengyi," Qi Heng replied.

Han Li turned to take a surprised glance at the woman in the blue palace dress upon hearing this.

Right at his moment, another resounding boom rang out in the sky, and a streak of light came plummeting down toward the plaza from the heavens.

As the streak of light landed on the ground, Yun Ni was revealed with a section of one of her sleeves torn away to reveal a part of her arm, but she didn't appear to have sustained any injuries.

Bai Fengyi and Bai Suyuan hurriedly rushed over to her, and the latter asked with a concerned expression, "Are you alright, Mistress?"

"I'm fine. The other Golden Immortal came after me with a sneak attack, but I was able to escape just in time," Yun Ni replied.

"It's all my fault for not being able to keep him at bay," Bai Fengyi said with a dejected expression.

"Now's not the time to be pointing fingers and assigning blame. At this point, the outcome of the battle is already largely decided, and there's not much point in continuing this battle," Yun Ni sighed.

"The main island of the Holy Puppet Sect is a mechanical array in itself, and if worse comes to worst, I'll activate the array and detonate the entire main island to send it sinking to the seabed. I won't let these bastards get anything!" Bai Fengyi declared in a cold voice.

"If that coward had agreed to come with me, there's no way we would be in this situation right now. What a foolish bastard he is! He's lived for so long, yet he's still dumber than a dog! Even after so long, he's still hung up over a bunch of insignificant things," Yun Ni grumbled as a hint of displeasure flashed through her eyes.

A faint smile appeared on Bai Fenyi's face upon hearing this.

"It's quite a rare occurrence to hear you cuss, Mistress. I thought that after my departure, that would pave the way for you two to come together, but alas... "

Her smile gradually faded as she spoke, and in the end, she couldn't help but heave a forlorn sigh.

"You are the only one who did nothing wrong in all of this, yet you had to bear all the consequences, and that's extremely unfair on you. Regardless of what happens here today, I'll make sure that the two of you can escape safely," Yun Ni said in a decisive voice.

Bai Fengyi shook her head in response. "I owe a great debt to the Holy Puppet Sect and its sect master, so I definitely can't leave at a time like this. Just take Suyuan with you when you go. Now that I've met her, I leave this world with no regrets."

An urgent look appeared on Bai Suyuan's face upon hearing this, and she was just about to raise objections when Lu Ji and Xue Han descended from above, hovering high up in the sky as they looked down at everyone with cold expressions.

With the most powerful combatants from both sides appearing on the scene, the battle that was taking place on the main island gradually drew to a halt.

All of the remaining Holy Puppet Sect cultivators formed a circle around Bai Fengyi, while the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators didn't dare to get too close to Bai Fengyi and Qilin 3, so they surrounded the entire plaza alongside the azure-armored Dao Warriors.

Chapter 294: The Restricted Area and the Golden Immortal Puppet

"Fellow daoists of the Transient Guild, you've already done more than enough for the Holy Puppet Sect. Are you really going to lay down your lives for a sect that has nothing to do with you? If you leave now, we won't stop you," Xue Han declared in a booming voice that was audible across the entire main island.

Bai Fengyi's heart immediately sank slightly upon hearing this, and the remaining Transient Guild members also began exchanging uncertain glances with one another.

They had already fulfilled their mission by protecting the array islands to the best of their abilities, but they had failed due to factors outside of their control, and several of them had most likely already met their demise, while the rest of them were at a very real risk of meeting the same fate.

The reward offered by the Holy Puppet Sect was indeed quite substantial, but it certainly wasn't worth dying for.

Right as everyone was hesitating about how to proceed, Yun Ni's voice suddenly rang out in their minds.

"The compensation issued by the Holy Puppet Sect is already in my storage bracelet, and they've given twice the promised reward. All you have to do to receive the reward is defend the Holy Puppet Sect to the best of your abilities."

Everyone's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this, but it didn't take long before they calmed down, and someone transmitted their voice to Yun Ni in response.

"The compensation is indeed very alluring, but it won't matter for anything if we're dead. If we keep this up, there's a very good chance that we'll all be wiped out here."

"Rest assured, I naturally won't let all of you die here. I'll issue the order to retreat at the right opportunity, but prior to that, anyone who dares to flee will be deemed to have disobeyed orders. I'm sure you all know what the consequences of such a transgression are," Yun Ni threatened in a cold voice.

Some of the Transient Guild members were still reluctant to stay, but no one dared to leave in the face of the combination of the increased reward and Qilin 3's threats.

Right at this moment, an earth-shattering boom suddenly rang out from behind the plaza of the Holy Puppet Sect, and a pillar of white light erupted into the sky before disintegrating.

"Looks like Fellow Daoist Zhong Luan has already succeeded on his end," Xue Han chuckled.

A hint of elation also flashed through Lu Ji's eyes as he nodded in response, while all of the Holy Puppet Sect cultivators were extremely alarmed and infuriated by this turn of events.

"Something's happened at the restricted area! How could this be? I left five elders there!" Bai Fengyi exclaimed.

"Haven't all of the most precious treasures of the sect already been transferred elsewhere? Is there something important in the restricted area?" Yun Ni asked.

"There's a Golden Immortal Stage immortal puppet in the restricted area, and it's the most precious treasure of our entire Holy Puppet Sect," Bai Fengyi replied with a wry smile.

"If you had such a thing, then why didn't you use it before?" Yun Ni asked with a perplexed expression.

"The immortal puppet has been passed down in our Holy Puppet Sect for a very long time, but it's not a complete immortal puppet as it's missing a suitable core. Hence, it can only be used when fused with our sect master, in which case it can display mid-Golden Immortal Stage power. Outside of that, it's constantly being nurtured in a spirit pond in the restricted area," Bai Fengyi explained.

As soon as her voice trailed off, seven or eight more pillars of white light erupted into the heavens in unison from behind the plaza.

"The restrictions in the restricted area are about to be broken!"

An alarmed look appeared on Bai Fengyi's face, and she was just about to fly away in that direction when she was stopped by Yun Ni.

"Don't panic. You still need to oversee proceedings here, and if you leave, all of the Holy Puppet Sect cultivators will be without a leader. If that happens, I don't think they'll even be able to withstand a single wave of attacks," Yun Ni cautioned.

Bai Fengyi forced herself to calm down upon hearing this, then turned to several of the nearby Holy Puppet Sect elders as she instructed, "Elder Yu, Elder Fu... Go and reinforce the restricted area right now!"

Meanwhile, Yun Ni's gaze roamed back and forth between Han Li and Xiong Shan for a moment before she finally decided, "Wyrm 15, go and give them a hand."

Han Li nodded in response before flying away with the three Holy Puppet Sect elders.

"Qilin 9, assist Deputy Sect Master Bai to keep that scar-faced man occupied to the best of your abilities. I'm going to use a secret technique to try and wound the other Golden Immortal," Yun Ni said as she turned to Xiong Shan.

Xiong Shan also nodded in response before making his way over to Bai Fengyi's side.

"Looks like it's time for the final battle, Fellow Daoist Lu Ji," Xue Han chuckled as he watched the four True Immortals depart from the battlefield.

He then turned to the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators and the azure-armored Dao Warriors down below as he yelled, "Everyone, victory is imminent! Charge!"

His declaration was met with a resounding collective wary cry as all of the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators surged toward the center of the battlefield, and with that, the final stage of the battle commenced.

……

Meanwhile, a string of resounding booms were ringing out incessantly within a well-concealed valley behind the plaza on the main island.

As Han Li and the others arrived outside the valley, they saw eight pillars of white light erupting straight into the heavens, forming a vortex of white light up above.

"The array has already been breached! Perhaps the enemy has already entered the restricted area!" a Holy Puppet Sect elder with white hair and a white beard said in a concerned voice.

"We have to enter the valley right away," another azure-robed elderly man yelled in an urgent voice.

The four of them immediately flew into the valley, and along the way, they were greeted by the sight of toppled mountains, severed rivers, felled trees, and countless bodies that belonged to Holy Puppet Sect disciples and elders.

"Elder Lu!"

The azure-robed elder who was flying at the forefront suddenly shuddered as a pained look appeared on his face.

Everyone looked down to find that portly old man with a benevolent-looking face had been pinned to a cliff face up ahead by a longsword.

That man was none other than the azure-robed elderly man's closest friend in the sect.

However, there was no time to stop and grieve, and everyone continued to fly toward the place in the valley where the pillars of light had risen up.

Before long, they reached the end of the valley, where a waterfall that was over 1,000 feet tall awaited them.

The waterfall was cascading down from above, sending water splashing in all directions to form a series of arched-bridge-like rainbows in the air.

Beneath the waterfall was a large green pond, within which was an octagonal white stone altar, and that was what the eight pillars of white light were rising up from.

Outside the pond, a battle was still taking place. A tall elderly man with his entire body drenched in blood was fighting alongside an eight-armed puppet against three Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators, and it was clear that the elderly man wasn't going to be able to last much longer.

Scattered around them were the remains of around a dozen Holy Puppet Sect cultivators and puppets, all of which were in horrific condition.

Out of the three Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators, only one of them was at the True Immortal Stage, while the other two were both at the Grand Ascension Stage, so they were extremely alarmed by the arrival of four enemy True Immortals and hurriedly took a glance at the vortex up above.

The azure-robed elder was furious, and he immediately charged toward one of the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators, who slashed a crimson halberd through the air to release a streak of crimson light, which swept directly toward the azure-robed elder's throat.

At the same time, he made a strange hand seal with his other hand, and a layer of crimson light appeared over his body.

"You're not getting away!" the azure-robed elderly roared in a furious voice, then knocked the halberd aside with his longsword, and the a burst of azure light erupted out of the sword's blade, instantly elongating by several feet to decapitate the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivator.

At the same time, the azure-robed elder swept his other sleeve through the air to release a burst of flames that enveloped his opponent's head before incinerating it into ashes along with his nascent soul.

The other two Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators didn't dare to hesitate any longer upon seeing this, and they hurriedly fled in opposite directions.

One of them was only able to fly about 1,000 feet before he was pinned down firmly against the ground by a giant lion puppet.

As for the only True Immortal among the trio, his entire body was enveloped in a layer of hazy starlight, and with just a single punch, he was able to knock back the Holy Puppet Sect elder that was standing in his way, following which he leaped over 10,000 feet up into the air to escape from the valley.

Everyone was just about to give chase when the tall elderly man suddenly stumbled and began to fall forward.

Han Li immediately appeared beside the elder to support him, but he was looking in the direction that the Ubiquitous Pavilion True Immortal had fled in with a peculiar look on his face.

The tall elderly man's body was riddled with over 100 wounds that were deep enough to expose bone, and not a single spot on his body wasn't drenched in blood.

However, he paid no heed to the severity of his own injuries as he pointed at the vortex in the sky with a trembling finger and said in an urgent voice, "Hurry... Go... Someone has already entered the restricted area!"

The three Holy Puppet Sect elders' expressions changed drastically upon hearing this.

The azure-robed elder pierced through the head of the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivator pinned under the giant lion puppet with his sword, making sure to destroy his nascent soul as well, then returned to the tall elderly man's side before feeding him a pill.

After taking the pill, the elderly man was finally unable to cling onto consciousness any longer, and he slumped to the ground in an unconscious state.

Meanwhile, the severely ravaged eight-armed puppet stumbled over to the elderly man's side before falling apart into a pile of scrap materials.

The azure-robed elder hesitated momentarily, then approached Han Li as he said, "Fellow daoist of the Transient Guild, may I trouble you to go after the person that just escaped? It doesn't matter if you manage to successfully kill him or not, just make sure that he won't come back here."

Han Li took a glance at the vortex in the sky, and he knew that the three elders were about to enter the restricted area to pursue the intruder. As an outsider, he naturally couldn't be allowed into the restricted area, and that was why he was being diverted away.

With that in mind, he nodded in response. "Sure."

After that, he vanished from the spot, flying away as a streak of light.

Following his departure, the azure-robed elder turned to his two companions as he said, "Leave the snow lion puppet behind to look after Elder Fang. We have to go in right away."

The other two elders nodded in response, and the three of them flew into the vortex in the sky in unison.

Meanwhile, Han Li had only just flown out of the valley before stopping in his tracks.

He stood in mid-air as he swept his gaze across his surroundings, and a faint smile appeared on his face as he flew toward a forest outside the valley.

Chapter 295: Great Universe Origin Arts

Before long, Han Li descended onto a plot of empty land in the forest, then looked around momentarily, following which a faint smile appeared on his face.

"You're quite a cunning fellow, aren't you? You're waiting for the battle in the secret area to be decided, ideally with both sides taking each other out so you can sneak back in and reap the spoils," Han Li mused as he cast his gaze toward a huge tree several thousand feet away.

As soon as his voice trailed off, an imposing figure slowly emerged from behind that tree, and it was none other than the True Immortal cultivator that had fled earlier.

"Isn't it rather unwise for you to have pursued me here on your own, Fellow Daoist?" the burly figure chuckled, following which his hands balled up into tight fists.

At the same time, a string of loud cracks and pops rang out from within his body, and he had suddenly grown noticeably taller.

"If I hadn't come on my own, you most likely wouldn't have revealed yourself so easily," Han Li chuckled.

He took a step back as he spoke, then adopted a casual fighting stance as he cast his gaze toward the burly figure.

"You sound very confident!"

The burly figure lunged forward like lightning, reaching no more than 1,000 feet away from Han Li in the blink of an eye before throwing a vicious punch.

Seven blue specks of starlight emerged on his chest and his abdomen, and his arm suddenly thickened significantly. His fist had also turned as translucent as jade, and it was hurtling through the air with tremendous force, leaving a trail of ripples that were visible even to the naked eye in the space in its wake.

Han Li raised an eyebrow as a layer of golden scales appeared over his arm, and the sound of metallic grating rang out from the joints of his fists as he met the burly figure's fist with a punch of his own.

A resounding boom rang out as a burst of tremendously violent power erupted in all directions, sweeping up ferocious gusts of wind that tore through many of the surrounding trees, sending them tumbling down onto the ground while countless wood scraps and branches flew through the air.

The burly figure was sent flying back, and after landing on the ground, he stumbled back around a dozen steps before steadying himself. Meanwhile, Han Li hadn't moved back even a single step, and a surprised look appeared in the burly figure's face as he exclaimed, "You're also a Profound Immortal?"

"Why do you sound so surprised?" Han Li asked with a smile.

"No wonder you dared to trade punches with me in such a casual manner. Looks like I was too careless," the burly figure mused.

A Profound Immortal would normally be able to gain a significant advantage if they could get close to a cultivator of the same cultivation base, but of course, that didn't apply if the other person was also a Profound Immortal.

"It seems like you didn't go all-out with that punch just now. How about you show me your full power?" Han Li asked.

Upon realizing that Han Li was also a Profound Immortal, the burly figure's overbearing attitude completely faded, and he replied in a softer tone, "If you wish to see my full power, then I'm happy to oblige."

As soon as his voice trailed off, the seven specks of blue starlight on his chest and abdomen appeared again, but right after that, more specks of blue light emerged on his shoulders, arms, and waist as well.

To his surprise, Han Li was able to count 18 specks of starlight on the burly man's body, and that wasn't even counting the ones that could've been present on his back.

His brows furrowed slightly, and this time, he didn't wait passively for the burly man's attack. Instead, he took a step forward, and a layer of golden scales appeared over his arm as seven specks of blue starlight appeared on his body as well.

"That's the Big Dipper Origin Arts!" the burly man exclaimed upon seeing this.

However, neither of them displayed any intention of stopping as they traded another punch with an earth-shattering boom.

An enormous cloud of dust swept through the air in all directions, and all of the trees in a radius of close to 10,000 feet were completely destroyed, opening up a huge, barren area around the two combatants.

Both Han Li and the burly man were sent flying back through the air with their feet plowing massive trenches into the ground, and only a distance of several thousand feet had been opened up between the two of them did they each draw to a halt.

Han Li sprang out of the trench beneath his feet, hovering in mid-air as he looked down at the burly man and asked, "Would you like to continue, Fellow Daoist?"

The burly man remained standing on the spot without making any moves, and a massive black wheel had appeared right above him, revolving rapidly while releasing formidable law fluctuations.

He took a glance up at Han Li, then heaved a faint sigh as he lowered his fists, and the specks of blue light all over his body also faded away.

"Who are you? How did you manage to obtain the Big Dipper Origin Arts?" the burly man asked with a perplexed expression.

"Before I answer that, why don't you tell me how you were able to open up so many profound acupoints with your Big Dipper Origin Arts?" Han Li asked with a smile.

Instead of answering Han Li's question, the burly man asked, "What do you plan to do to me?"

"What do you want me to do with you, Fellow Daoist Cold Flame?" Han Li countered through voice transmission.

The burly man shuddered upon hearing this and an incredulous look appeared on his face. Only after staring at Han Li for a long while did he ask through voice transmission, "Are you... Fellow Daoist Han Li?"

"You're a smart man, Fellow Daoist Cold Flame."

Han Li made no attempt to deny his identity.

"Truth be told, the Big Dipper Origin Arts is a cultivation art that I obtained by chance in a set of ancient ruins, and I don't believe it's being passed down anywhere else. Hence, my chances of encountering someone else who's also using this cultivation art are slim to none.

“On top of that, I felt a sense of familiarity from you, and that led me to the conclusion that you were Fellow Daoist Han Li. However, I didn't think that you would reach the mid-True Immortal Stage so soon after your ascension. Your rate of progress is truly astounding," Patriarch Cold Flame sighed.

Instead of making small talk or catching up with Patriarch Cold Flame, Han Li said, "Indeed, it seems that we were fated to meet here, but before we talk about anything else, I'll have to ask you to answer my question about how you managed to open up so many immortal acupoints."

A slightly hesitant look appeared on Patriarch Cold Flame's face upon hearing this.

"I'm sure you're not considering trying to deceive me, are you? You've already seen how formidable my spiritual sense is, and we are acquaintances of sorts, so don't force me to use a soul search technique on you," Han Li warned in a meaningful voice.

Patriarch Cold Flame took a glance at the Heavy Water True Axis that was hanging above his head, then composed himself as he replied, "I wouldn't dare to try and deceive you, Fellow Daoist Han. Truth be told, the Big Dipper Origin Arts that you're cultivating is related to body refinement cultivation art that I obtained by chance from a set of ruins. After I mastered the cultivation art, I compiled it into a simplified version for the descendants of my sect to cultivate."

"Oh? In that case, what is the name of the complete cultivation art that you discovered?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"It's called the Great Universe Origin Arts. You can have a copy of it if you'd like."

Patriarch Cold Flame flipped a hand over to produce a gray stone slab as he spoke, then handed it to Han Li without any hesitation.

Han Li made a grabbing motion to release a burst of azure light, which enveloped the stone slab, and only after verifying that the slab hadn't been tampered with did he draw it to himself before carefully inspecting it.

The stone slab was only around the size of a human hand, and it was riddled with tiny antiquated text on both sides.

Han Li inspected the stone slab for a moment, following which his brows suddenly furrowed slightly as he asked, "If I'm not mistaken, the cultivation art recorded on this stone slab is incomplete, right?"

"I'm afraid that can't be helped, Fellow Daoist. I only managed to obtain half of the Great Universe Origin Arts at the risk of my own life in those ruins, and I don't have the other half," Patriarch Cold Flame hurriedly explained.

Han Li could tell that he didn't appear to have been lying, so he flipped a hand over to produce a jade slip, then pressed it against the stone slab before making a hand seal, and a few seconds later, a copy of the cultivation art had been made.

After that, he withdrew his Heavy Water True Axis with a wave of his hand, but instead of returning the stone slab to Patriarch Cold Flame, he tossed him the jade slip.

Patriarch Cold Flame's expression remained unchanged as he watched Han Li stow the stone slab into his storage bracelet while he caught the jade slip that was tossed at him.

"You've killed a bunch of people on the island, so I'm sure you must've already reaped some substantial spoils, right? I advise you to leave the island right away. The Holy Puppet Sect's defeat is already sealed, but there's no telling how ferocious its retaliation could be in its final moments, so it would be unwise for you to stay," Han Li advised.

"Thank you for your advice, Fellow Daoist, I was just about to leave," Patriarch Cold Flame said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

Indeed, he was planning to leave after this foray into the restricted area anyway.

Furthermore, once the Holy Puppet Sect was destroyed, the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators would've completed their mission, and they would've no longer been bound by the Ubiquitous Pavilion.

Even if a battle didn't immediately break out, there was inevitably going to infighting over treasures and resources, so leaving before that would spare Patriarch Cold Flame a great deal of trouble.

Han Li took a meaningful glance at Patriarch Cold Flame. Even back in the Spirit Domain Realm, he had felt Patriarch Cold Flame to have been quite a shrewd and cunning man who was more adaptable than the native immortals of the Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

That thought only flashed through his mind for a moment before he turned and flew back toward the restricted area.

Patriarch Cold Flame looked on at Han Li's departing figure, and he was holding onto the jade slip in his hand so tightly that the tips of his fingers were slightly pale.

Only after Han Li had completely disappeared out of sight did he heave a long sigh of relief before murmuring to himself, "That was way too close! Why did I have to run into him of all people? Thank heavens I managed to get out of that one unscathed! I really have to be more careful when taking on missions like this from now on."

After that, he stowed the jade slip away, then summoned a silver flying boat with a sweep of his sleeve before leaping onto it and flying away.

Chapter 296: Intense Clash

Before long, Han Li was already back in the valley.

He looked up to find that the eight pillars of light were still standing, as was the giant vortex in the sky.

The elder with the Fang surname was also still laying beside the pond in an unconscious state, while the snow lion puppet was on guard duty by his side, and it displayed no reaction to Han Li's arrival.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li descended out of the sky, yet before he landed on the ground, he felt a burst of formidable spatial fluctuation erupting out of the white vortex above the pond.

He hurriedly stopped in his tracks, then looked up to discover that the vortex had begun to revolve rapidly while radiating dazzling white light.

Immediately thereafter, a figure plummeted out of the vortex with their body riddled with wounds that were deep enough to expose bone, while their azure robes were completely drenched in blood.

He appeared to have been in just as horrific a condition as the unconscious Elder Fang, and as soon as he spotted Han Li, he immediately yelled in a frantic voice, "Save me, Fellow Daoist!"

Han Li only took a brief glance at him before turning his gaze to the vortex with tightly furrowed brows.

Another burst of white light surged within the vortex, following which a black figure emerged from within.

The black figure was holding a long black blade, and he chortled, "Why did you abandon your companion? Weren't you talking about avenging Elder Lu not long ago?"

Han Li's gaze immediately fell upon the long black saber in the black figure's hand, and he discovered that it was none other than the saber that had been previously used by Fang Pan before being sold by him in the Transient Guild.

"Oh? Looks like there's someone else here. I wasn't really satisfied yet anyway, so I'll take care of you as well," the black figure chuckled as he spotted Han Li.

Beneath the figure's black hood was a slightly yellow face with some type of metallic headgear on his forehead, and it was none other than one of the three leaders of the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators, Zhong Luan.

With a flick of his wrist, he slashed his black saber toward Han Li.

It was a very casual-looking swipe, but in the instant that the saber was sent sweeping through the air, all of the spirit patterns on its surface instantly lit up, following which hundreds of extremely formidable black saber projections erupted through the air, with the majority of them hurtling toward Han Li, while only a minority were aimed at the azure-robed elderly man.

The azure-robed elderly man was horrified to see this, and he injected what little remained of his immortal spiritual power into a pair of silver balls before hurling them forward, and the silver balls instantly transformed into a pair of silver puppets that situated themselves in front of him.

At the same time, a suit of already severely ravaged azure wooden armor appeared over his body amid a flash of azure light.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he flipped a hand over to summon an azure longsword, then slashed it at the oncoming blade projections.

Hundreds of azure sword projections instantly erupted out of the longsword before scattering far and wide to clash against the black blade projections.

A string of metallic clangs rang out as the black blade projections clashed against the azure sword projections, all of which exploded violently into a vast expanse of black and azure light.

All of a sudden, the azure-robed elderly man yelled, "Look out, Fellow Daoist! That black blade..."

Before he had a chance to finish, a peculiar turn of events began to unfold.

The black blade projections had already disintegrated into specks of black light, but they quickly reformed into more black blade projections that continued to hurtle toward Han Li and the azure-robed elderly man, and their power hadn't been diminished in the slightest.

The two silver puppets in front of the azure-robed elderly man were wielding jointed steel whips that they lashed out at the black blade projections with, but they were no match for the oncoming blade projections, which shredded their whips before punching countless holes straight through their bodies to destroy them on the spot.

Immediately thereafter, the suit of azure armor that the elderly man was wearing also began to tremble violently in the face of the black blade projections, looking as if it could be torn apart at any moment.

This suit of azure armor was his final line of defense, and if it were to also be vanquished, then his demise would immediately follow.

In this dire situation, the nearby snow lion puppet suddenly pounced forward, landing in front of the azure-robed elderly man before swiping its front paws through the air to unleash countless claw projections.

As soon as the claw projections came into contact with the blade projections, they were immediately destroyed, but most of the blade projections were also nullified, while the snow lion puppet withstood the rest with its body.

A relieved look appeared on the azure-robed elderly man's face upon seeing this, but he then threw up a mouthful of blood before slumping to the ground.

In contrast, Han Li was far more calm and collected.

With a flick of his wrist, he swung his longsword through the air, unleashing a string of sword projections that formed an azure sword barrier around him.

The black blade projections struck the sword barrier in a relentless barrage before exploding and reforming over and over again.

Only after many cycles of this did the blade projections finally run out of spiritual power and disintegrate for good.

Up to this point, only a few seconds had passed since Zhong Luan unleashed his initial attack.

"Looks like you're not quite as useless as those idiots! Very good. Let's see how long you can last!" Zhong Luan cackled as he licked his own lips.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he closed both of his hands around the hilt of his saber, and bursts of black light began to appear over his body.

Immediately thereafter, a layer of black light appeared on the surface of the black saber alongside a series of thin golden lines, forming numerous antiquated runes that were giving off terrifying energy fluctuations.

Gusts of ferocious wind were swept up in the surrounding air as the nearby world's origin qi surged toward the black saber in a relentless wave.

With the injection of the world's origin qi, the golden lines on the black saber glowed brighter and brighter, as did the runes on its surface, which looked as if they were about to emerge from the blade itself.

Waves of black and golden light surged through the surrounding area, carrying tremendous law power fluctuation that caused the entire space to tremble and quiver.

Han Li's brows furrowed tightly with befuddlement upon seeing this.

It was the same black saber, but this man was able to unleash far more formidable power with it than he and Fang Pan had been capable of, and Han Li couldn't help but wonder if he was the saber's original owner.

Right at this moment, Zhong Luan suddenly let loose a loud roar, then spun around in mid-air, using the momentum of his pirouette to slash his saber at Han Li.

A sharp clang rang out as a black and golden saber projection that was over 10,000 feet in length came crashing down from above, devouring all of the world's origin qi in the area while giving off a burst of terrifying spiritual pressure.

A solemn look appeared in Han Li's eyes as he made a hand seal with one hand while slashing his sword diagonally upward with the other.

The spirit patterns on the longsword were glowing brightly as it released wave upon wave of surging azure light, which transformed into dozens of azure sword projections in the blink of an eye.

Immediately thereafter, all of the sword projections combined as one to form a huge azure sword projection that was over 1,000 feet in length before hurtling toward the giant saber projection.

The sword projection was threatening to tear the very space apart, and an earth-shattering boom rang out in the sky as the pair of enormous blade projections clashed against one another.

Devastating tremors were sent sweeping across the entire main island of the Holy Puppet Sect, to the point that all of the people battling on the plaza were stopped cold in their tracks for a moment before the battle resumed.

Even Yun Ni and the Ubiquitous Pavilion Golden Immortals detected the disturbance taking place on the main island, but the battle that they were engaged in was too perilous for them to get distracted, so none of them released their spiritual sense to check what was happening.

"Looks like the Holy Puppet Sect still has some more tricks up its sleeve, but I wonder if they'll be able to contain a madman like Zhong Luan," Xue Han chuckled with a relaxed expression.

Beside the pond in the valley, the azure-robed elderly man was struck by a burst of tremendous shockwaves resulting from the clash, and he threw up a large mouthful of blood before finally falling unconscious.

In the instant before he lost consciousness, his heart was filled with immense regret.

After witnessing Han Li's power, it occurred to him that if he had chosen to bring Han Li into the restricted area with him instead of diverting him away, perhaps the other two elders wouldn't have died, and the immortal puppet wouldn't have been taken.

However, there was no point in crying over spilled milk, and at this point, he could only pray that Han Li would be able to overcome his opponent.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as Han Li was sent plummeting out of the sky before crashing into the pond in the valley.

Dozens of enormous waves instantly erupted out of the pond, while a massive crater was smashed into its bottom, causing the water level in the pond to drop rapidly, revealing large patches of the pond bed as a result.

As for Zhong Luan, he was also sent flying back by the clash and involuntarily rose up much higher into the sky.

A grim look appeared on his face, and after steadying himself, he immediately shot back toward the pond in the valley at an astonishing speed while slashing his saber downward once again.

Right at this moment, a burst of loud buzzing suddenly rang out from within the pond, immediately following a black wheel treasure emerged from the water while revolving rapidly.

The Time Dao Rune on the surface of the wheel was glowing brightly as it rose up with half of the water in the pond, ascending toward Zhong Luan with incredible power.

Chapter 297: Destined to Cross Paths

Zhong Luan let loose a low roar as the muscles on his arms bulged, mustering up even more power as he swung his long black saber down onto the Heavy Water True Axis with ferocious might.

A resounding boom rang out, and a jolt of numbness shot through Zhong Luan's arms. A burst of indescribable power surged along his saber, and he was stopped cold in his tracks as if he had hit a wall.

Immediately thereafter, bursts of tremendous water law powers surged toward him, forcing him back and threatening to send him flying.

Zhong Luan's expression immediately changed slightly as he felt the unique aura of the Heavy Water True Axis, and even though he was clearly on the back foot, he suddenly burst into laughter.

"I've been looking for you everywhere, but never did I think I would be able to find you here, Han Li! You've saved me a trip to the Ancient Cloud Continent!"

As soon as his voice trailed off, his eyes suddenly turned an inky-black color, and he opened his mouth to release a glowing black thread that vanished into his saber in a flash.

The black saber began to tremble violently as a layer of translucent black light appeared over its surface, and its weight was instantly multiplied by severalfold.

Zhong Luan let loose a thunderous roar as wisps of black mist began to slowly seep out of his body, and he pressed his saber down with both hands, managing to force back the Heavy Water True Axis.

At this point, Han Li had already emerged from the pond, and he made a beckoning motion to draw the Heavy Water True Axis back to him as he hovered in mid-air while holding his azure longsword in one hand.

He cast his gaze toward Zhong Luan as he asked in a cold voice, "How are you related to Fang Pan?"

Even though he had no idea who this person was, the fact that he was able to unleash the true power of the black saber coupled with the fact that he knew Han Li's true name indicated that he had to have been related to Fang Pan somehow.

After all, Han Li had been using false aliases this entire time in the Immortal Realm, so no one should've been aware of his true name.

The three people that had attacked him all those years ago had been killed one after another, but that person that was able to control those mysterious chains from afar, the original owner of Fang Pan's black saber, and the person who had instructed Fang Pan to come after him were still all people that he had to be wary of.

There was a very good chance that this person was the original owner of the black saber, but Han Li still didn't know how he was tied to Fang Pan.

"That junior martial brother of mine may be an incapable fool, but I had thought that it would've at least taken a late-True Immortal cultivator to kill him, but the information that I gathered from the Ubiquitous Pavilion told me that you're only an early-True Immortal Stage Profound Immortal. I will admit, you do have some powerful tricks up your sleeve," Zhong Luan remarked as he looked at Han Li from afar.

Han Li's heart stirred slightly upon hearing this, and he said, "So you're Fang Pan's senior martial brother. Have you come to avenge him?"

"I have better things to do with my time than to avenge that idiot, but in order to take you down, he paid a heavy price to borrow this Black Emperor Immortal Slaying Blade of mine, only for you to turn around and sell it. Do you not owe me an explanation for this?" Zhong Luan asked in an unhurried voice.

"That saber of yours is indeed a rare treasure, and my intention was to return it to its original owner, and that's why I put it up for sale in the Transient Guild to see if anyone recognized it. It looks like my efforts paid off and you were reunited with your saber, but there's no need to thank me," Han Li replied.

"It sounds like I owe you a favor if you put it that way! However, the fact that my junior martial brother was so determined to kill you indicates that you must be harboring some important secrets. On top of that, I have to recover the Origin Separation Law Chains on your body for my master, so you'll have to die. Rest assured, I'll grant you a swift and painless death to repay you for returning my saber!" Zhong Luan chuckled.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the black mist that was revolving around him instantly swelled to inundate his entire body.

Immediately thereafter, a gentle breeze blew past, and the black mist was scattered to reveal nothing inside.

Han Li had already released his spiritual sense to encompass the entire surrounding area, but in the instant before the mist was scattered, he was still of the opinion that Zhong Luan had been concealed within it.

In the next instant, a cloud of black mist suddenly began to take shape in the air behind him, and before it had even fully formed, a black saber shot out from within it, piercing directly toward the back of Han Li's chest.

Han Li's Heavy Water True Axis instantly appeared behind him at his behest, and a loud clang rang out as the tip of the black saber struck the Heavy Water True Axis, grating against it with an ear-piercing screeching sound.

Zhong Luan slowly emerged within the black mist with a cold smile on his face, and the wisps of black mist around his black saber formed a series of extremely thin black needles that shot forth along the tip of the saber, piercing straight through the gaps in the Heavy Water True Axis to attack Han Li.

A layer of golden scales instantly appeared all over Han Li's body amid a flash of golden light, and a string of crisp clangs rang out as the black needles struck Han Li's golden scales before being repelled and shattering into black mist again.

Han Li immediately swung around as he slashed his longsword through the air, and with a single sweep of his sword, he was able to slice Zhong Luan's body cleanly in half.

However, Zhong Luan merely grinned at him before the two halves of his body disintegrated into a cloud of mist.

A sense of foreboding welled up in Han Li's heart upon seeing this, and he instantly flew back tens of thousands of feet to get away from the cloud of black mist.

However, before he had even drawn to a halt, he suddenly felt a cold sensation running down his back, as if there were a slippery snake slithering down his spine.

He hurriedly made a hand seal, and the protective spiritual light around his body instantly expelled the thing that was adhered to his back, revealing it to have been a small cloud of black mist that resembled a living creature.

There were countless soft feelers that were as thin as strands of human hair on its surface, and those feelers were writhing incessantly, trying to get close to him and burrow their way into his body.

Han Li reached out to conjure a glowing azure palm projection to seize control of the cloud of black mist, and he carefully inspected it to discover that it contained an extremely faint hint of law powers.

It was so faint that he was unable to determine exactly what attribute the law power was, but thankfully, he hadn't withdrawn the layer of protective golden scales over his body, and that had kept the black mist at bay.

All of a sudden, the space around the cloud of black mist began to tremble, and wisps of black mist emerged out of thin air, following which Zhong Luan's body re-emerged without any warning.

The piece of black cloth that was obscuring his face had been removed, revealing a large yellow-skinned face, and he opened his mouth to release a thread of translucent black light that shot directly toward Han Li's face at an alarming speed.

Han Li immediately slashed his longsword diagonally upward, instantly shattering the black thread into a burst of black light upon contact.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he immediately shot back in retreat.

As soon as he did so, another black thread appeared at the spot where he had originally been standing, and it began to fly toward him again.

As expected, those black threads can also reform after being destroyed, just like those blade projections from earlier.

All of a sudden, the newly formed black thread was somehow able to connect itself to the azure longsword in his hand from afar, and it darted up along the blade of the sword before shooting into the palm of his hand.

Han Li felt a slight numb sensation in his hand, and he immediately began to inspect his own internal condition, but he didn't notice anything else amiss aside from that fleeting sensation of numbness in his hand.

However, that only made him feel even more uneasy.

Right at this moment, he detected several auras approaching from afar through his spiritual sense, but he was unable to determine whether these were allies from the Holy Puppet Sect or more enemies from the Ubiquitous Pavilion.

Han Li's brows were tightly furrowed, and after a brief moment of contemplation, he made a beckoning motion with both hands to stow his azure longsword and Heavy Water True Axis away.

Regardless of whether the people approaching the scene were from the Ubiquitous Pavilion or the Holy Puppet Sect, he was planning to leave this place.

His opponent's abilities were extremely troublesome to deal with, and he seemed to have been able to wield some type of law power related to mist. Furthermore, Han Li was unable to go all-out here, and that placed him at a severe disadvantage.

With that in mind, he made a hand seal with both hands, and arcs of silver lightning sprang out of his body, forming a huge lightning array around him in the blink of an eye.

A loud thunderclap rang out as several thick bolts of silver lightning erupted out of the center of the array, and in the next instant, Han Li vanished from the spot, leaving behind only a faint charred odor in the air.

"Interesting! I guess I can play with you for a while longer," Zhong Luan mused with a cold smile, following which his body disintegrated into a cloud of black mist once again.

……

Meanwhile, the battle on the plaza on the main island was still raging, but the commotion had already died down significantly.

Almost all of the Holy Puppet Sect's puppets had already been destroyed, while the majority of the surviving disciples were carrying injuries and had been trapped in a far smaller encirclement than before.

What was quite moving was that despite the dire nature of the situation, not a single one of the Holy Puppet Sect cultivators surrendered or fled the battlefield. Instead, all of them continued to fight on with determination in their eyes.

One reason for this was that all of the people that had chosen to remain behind in the sect had already resolved themselves to defend the sect with their lives, while the other contributing factor was that all of them had relatives that had already been evacuated from the sect.

As long as those people remained safe, they were able to fight without any qualms.

In contrast, the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators hadn't been able to gain much of an upper hand at all. Not only had the majority of them already perished or sustained injuries during the battle, many of them had departed in advance just like Patriarch Cold Flame, so there weren't all that many of them left on the plaza.

At this point in the battle, everything had slowed down significantly.

All of the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators who had managed to survive to this point were quite cunning, and they knew that a cornered beast was more dangerous than anything else, so they couldn't afford to be overly aggressive in this situation.

Instead, it was much better to maintain the status quo and slowly grind down the Holy Puppet Sect cultivators so that they could secure an easy victory later.

As a result, the Dao Warriors released by Xue Han had become the main force that was battling the remaining Holy Puppet Sect cultivators, and they were at the forefront of the encirclement.

Chapter 298: Imminent Defeat

Somewhere among the Holy Puppet Sect cultivators, Bai Suyuan's clothes had already been completely stained black by blood, and the drenched fabric was clinging to her body, further accentuating her alluring curves. Even the pair of white earrings that she was wearing were covered in a layer of dried blood.

However, most of the blood on her body belonged to Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators, and there was also a lot of blood that had splashed onto her from nearby Holy Puppet Sect cultivators. The only injury that she was carrying was a gash on her right arm from a sneak attack from a Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivator.

The attack had been aimed at her heart, but the peachwood talisman gifted to her by Bai Fengyi had saved her in the nick of time, diverting the attack away so that it had only managed to graze her arm.

She had retreated to the center of the crowd and taken her final regenerative pill to replenish her magic power, but she wasn't actually as fearful and uneasy as she had been at the beginning of the battle.

In the past, she had only ever been involved in small-scale battles that couldn't even have held a candle to a battle of this magnitude and this degree of brutality.

Not only did Bai Suyuan possess exceptional aptitude, she had been forced to fend for herself from a young age, so she was certainly no vulnerable little girl, and the battle unfolding around her had brought the cold and decisive side of her personality to the fore.

Not only that, but her cultivation bottleneck was also beginning to display signs of budging, and she was confident that if she could survive this crisis, then she would definitely have been able to make a breakthrough after no more than 20 years of seclusion.

However, was this a crisis that she would be able to survive?

A grim look appeared in her eyes as this thought crossed her mind, and she looked up at the sky to find that a massive hole with a that was over 1,000 feet wide had been torn into the dark clouds up above, and it extended for several thousand kilometers.

Inside the hole, countless streaks of sword qi were surging incessantly, plunging the world's origin qi into complete disarray while relentlessly tearing at the very space itself amid bursts of deafening rumbling.

An enormous snow lotus flower projection could be seen slowly revolving within the hole, and glowing white petals that were giving off powerful energy fluctuations were flying off the lotus flower one after another.

A massive sword projection was bearing down upon the snow lotus flower projection with tremendous might, but it was unable to break through, and an impasse had ensued between the two.

Yun Ni was standing at the center of the lotus flower projection, making a string of hand seals while chanting an incantation that struck the listener with a sense of intoxication. Furthermore, there was a pink glow in her eyes, and her entire body was enveloped in a hazy floral projection, giving her an extremely seductive and unforgettable appearance.

As her chanting continued, countless barefoot women stepped out from the stamen of the snow lotus flower projection before springing up into the air from the flower's petals.

A massive artwork was unfurled within the clouds, and there were hundreds of barefoot women depicted within it. There were colorful silken belts around their waists that spread open like the canopies of peacocks as the women danced through the sky, presenting an incredibly beautiful sight to behold.

If a mortal had even witnessed this scene, even for just a split second, their soul would've come straight out of their body and entered the artwork to become sustenance for the dancing celestial maidens.

Even cultivators who were lacking in cultivation base or mental fortitude wouldn't have fared much better than mortals if they were to get too close to the artwork. At the very most, they would've only been able to last a few moments before their souls were also sucked out of their bodies.

Directly in front of the artwork stood Lu Ji with his sword held in his hand.

His clothes were smooth and pristine, not creasing in the slightest despite the ferocious wind blowing through the sky.

At this point, he appeared more like a peerlessly sharp sword than a human, and it was as if no amount of wind, no matter how fierce, would be able to crease his clothes even in the slightest.

Instead of looking at the artwork in the sky, his gaze was focused intently on Yun Ni inside the snow lotus flower projection. A layer of faint pink coloration had already appeared in his left eye, but his right eye was completely clear and unchanged.

Meanwhile, in the sky above the sea several thousand kilometers away, a nine star golden sword that was over 10,000 feet in length was glowing radiantly as it came crashing down upon Xue Han.

The sword left layers of golden sword projections in its wake alongside countless specks of dazzling white light, resembling a spectacular golden starry sky.

Xue Han's robes were tattered in many places, but there was a mocking look on his face as he sneered, "It's very impressive that a pair of mere True Immortals like yourselves were able to keep me occupied for this long, but unfortunately, you won't get to live to tell the tale."

As soon as his voice trailed off, he swept a hand through the air to summon a large black flag that was around 10 feet tall.

The flag was torn in many places, and at the center of it was embroidered a series of golden vortex designs, around which were numerous antiquated runes that were giving off an incredibly formidable aura.

Xue Han closed both of his hands around the shaft of the flag, then chanted an incantation before swinging the flag through the air.

The surface of the flag immediately began to ripple like the surface of a turbulent sea, and the runes that were embroidered onto its surface flew out one after another, releasing dazzling golden light that obscured the entire sky.

At the same time, the golden vortexes on the flag also began to rapidly revolve as if they had sprung to life, then flew out of the flag as well to send bursts of tremendous force surging through the air.

As soon as the golden starry sky came into contact with these vortexes, it was immediately sucked in by the immense suction force that the vortexes were releasing.

As the starry sky rapidly diminished in size, the aura of the nine star golden sword was also becoming weaker and weaker, and by the time it actually fell upon the flag, the sword had been reduced to no more than 1,000 feet in length. In its weakened state, it was barely even able to move the flag before it was repelled.

Qilin 9 raised a hand to catch the golden sword, and he couldn't help but stumble backward. He had expended so much immortal spiritual power that his immortal spiritual power circulation was becoming a little stagnant.

"How are you doing?" he asked as he turned to the figure beside him.

"I'm just about ready to go. You can take some time to recover now," Bai Fengyi said as she rose to her feet with a slightly pale complexion.

Just now, she and Qilin 9 had attacked Xue Han together, and Xue Han had intentionally displayed a façade of weakness to lure her in, only to unleash a golden ring treasure that struck her on her left shoulder. She was able to avoid major injury thanks to her protective treasures, but her immortal spiritual power was scattered, rendering her temporarily unable to draw upon it.

Thankfully, Qilin 9 had stepped in to protect her, allowing her the respite that she needed to take some pills and recover somewhat from her injuries.

At this moment, her left sleeve had already been completely torn away, and a large gash had also been torn into her collar, revealing a large patch of fair and delicate skin.

As a result, one could see that she was wearing layers of strapping around her chest beneath her robes, restraining the voluptuous peaks there to make them appear smaller and more compact.

She switched positions with Qilin 9 so that she was facing Xue Han, while Qilin 9 tossed a couple of pills into his own mouth before focusing on digesting them.

Xue Han gave a cold harrumph, and he was just about to close in on Bai Fengyi when his expression suddenly changed slightly, and he cast his gaze toward the main island of the Holy Puppet Sect.

After a brief hesitation, he raised a hand to stow the black flag away, then sped away as a streak of light, quickly vanishing into the distance.

An alarmed look appeared on Bai Fengyi's face upon seeing this, and she hurriedly set off in pursuit.

If she couldn't keep Xue Han occupied, then he would be able to join forces with Lu Ji, and that would place Yun Ni in grave peril.

However, as a True Immortal, there was no way that she could catch up to Xue Han, and he arrived beside Lu Ji in what seemed like no more than the blink of an eye.

A hint of wariness appeared in Xue Han's eyes at the sight of the alluring artwork in the sky, and he took a glance at the peculiar pink coloration in Lu Ji's left eye before calling out to him in a low voice.

Despite the low pitch of his voice, it was extremely penetrative, and the pink coloration in Lu Ji's left eye instantly faded away as both eyes returned to their original clarity.

Immediately thereafter, he took a stride forward as he raised his longsword, and he swept his joint index and middle fingers of his other hand over the blade of the sword to release streaks of pristine white sword qi that transformed into a series of white dragons that revolved around the sword.

It seemed that all of this had come out of nowhere, but in reality, he had been preparing this attack for a long time.

Prior to this, he was on the verge of unleashing the attack, but at that critical juncture, he had fallen prey to Yun Ni's secret technique, and that was why the attack had been delayed up to this point, but it was also exactly because of this prolonged stage of suppression that the attack had accumulated even more formidable power.

All of a sudden, a clear draconic roar rang out, and a streak of white sword qi that was over 10,000 feet in length swept through the heavens. All of the white dragons revolving around the sword also instantly swelled to over 100 times their original size before pouncing at Yun Ni.

All of a sudden, thousands of dragons were surging through the sky, churning up the dark clouds and stirring up gusts of ferocious wind.

Yun Ni's expression remained unchanged as she witnessed all of this from inside her snow lotus flower projections, but she couldn't help but heave an internal sigh.

An ordinary Golden Immortal cultivator would've already lost control over themselves after being exposed to her Illusory Celestial Maiden Artwork for so long. Even if they didn't fall under her control, at the very least, they wouldn't have been able to oppose her any longer.

However, Lu Ji's mental fortitude far exceeded her expectation, and even though it appeared that he had fallen prey to her secret technique, he was able to immediately shut off his six senses to protect his own mind.

If Xue Han hadn't intervened, it would've taken Yun Ni at least several more minutes to completely immobilize Lu Ji, at which point she would've been able to turn her attention to Xue Han, and perhaps this crisis could've been averted, but as things were now...

Chapter 299: I Dare You!

In the face of the formidable army of sword dragons, Yun Ni began to chant an incantation, and the pink coloration in her eyes gradually turned a golden hue, while her aura also underwent a drastic change.

Inside the giant artwork in the sky, the clothes worn by all of the barefoot women gradually blurred before transforming into suits of golden armor, and all of the musical instruments that they were holding also transformed into artifacts such as demon restraining vials and devil vanquishing pestles.

At the same time, the intoxicating music ringing out from the artwork also turned into Buddhist chanting, and in the blink of an eye, the entire complexion of the artwork had changed.

Bright golden light was glowing in Yun Ni's eyes, and all of the golden-armored women on the giant artwork flew out at her behest, forming a huge shimmering golden array in the sky.

A massive female projection that was over 10,000 feet tall appeared at the center of the array, and it bore a very close resemblance to Yun Ni, but it was lacking her seductive allure.

The projection was clad in a suit of golden armor and was wielding a golden sword that it slashed toward the oncoming sword dragons.

A vast expanse of golden light erupted from the golden sword to clash against the streaks of white swordlight, and the golden light exploded violently to illuminate all of the dark clouds in a golden hue, while gusts of fierce wind were sent sweeping in all directions.

Everyone on the plaza below was astonished by what was unfolding up above, and they all stopped what they were doing to look up at the sky.

After a brief impasse, the army of white sword dragons was able to break through the golden light before surging into the golden projection.

A burst of rumbling rang out as the golden projection was instantly split apart down the center, exploding into countless specks of light alongside all of the white dragons.

The sound of tearing fabric rang out, and the giant scroll in the sky was also torn apart down the center, then rapidly shrank down amid erratic flashes of golden light before drifting down from above.

Yun Ni was struck by a sense of tightness in her chest, and she forcibly suppressed the blood that was threatening to gush out of her throat as she stowed away the two halves of the torn scroll.

At this point, Bai Fengyi had already arrived by her side, and she hurriedly approached Yun Ni asked in a concerned voice, "Are you alright, Mistress?"

"I'm fine," Yun Ni replied with a wry smile.

A dejected look appeared in Bai Fengyi's eyes at the sight of Yun Ni's expression, and she heaved an internal sigh.

She knew that Yun Ni had done everything in her power, but the Holy Puppet Sect was simply beyond saving.

However, the inevitability of the outcome made her feel as if a heavy load had been removed from her shoulders, and a bright smile appeared on her face as she said, "Take Suyuan and leave, Mistress. I am honored to have been your disciple this lifetime."

A forlorn look appeared on Yun Ni's face upon hearing this, and she opened her mouth to say something, but couldn't find the words. In the end, she could descend toward the plaza down below with Bai Fengyi.

Lu Ji's expression eased slightly upon seeing this, and he turned to Xue Han before extending a grateful salute.

"You have my thanks."

"Don't worry about it, Fellow Daoist Lu Ji," Xue Han replied with a dismissive wave, then said, "I don't know what Zhong Luan is up to, but he suddenly left the main island and is already outside of my spiritual sensory range."

Lu Ji's expression changed slightly upon hearing this, and he replied, "You were the one who recruited him for this mission. Surely he hasn't been overcome by greed and decided to take that incomplete immortal puppet, has he?"

"I don't think so. His branch of disciples have never been interested in puppetry, so he's probably gone to do something else. In any case, I'll be sure to contact him after everything is said and done to recover that immortal puppet for you," Xue Han assured.

"That would be best. For now, let's eradicate the Holy Puppet Sect," Lu Ji replied in a cold voice.

As soon as Yun Ni and Bai Fengyi descended onto the plaza, they were immediately surrounded by remaining Transient Guild members.

"Fellow Daoist Qilin 3, while it's true that you're the leader of the mission, if you continue to try and force us to stay here and sacrifice ourselves, then don't blame us for resisting your orders!" one of them immediately said.

He wasn't communicating to her through voice transmission. Instead, he had spoken out loud, instantly drawing everyone's attention as he did so.

"Indeed, we've already done everything that can be reasonably expected of us!"

"Even if we raise this matter to the guild's supervisory division, we have a watertight case!"

All of the other Transient Guild members also immediately chimed in with their complaints.

Yun Ni took a glance at Bai Fengyi and Bai Suyuan, then turned her gaze toward the other Transient Guild members as she declared, "This mission is over, you're free to leave as you please now."

She summoned a batch of storage rings as she spoke and handed one out to each Transient Guild member.

After receiving their reward, all of the Transient Guild members briefly inspected the contents of the storage rings with their spiritual sense, and ecstatic looks appeared on their faces before all of them departed one after another, with the exceptions of Bai Suyuan and Qilin 9.

For some reason, they were allowed to leave by the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators and the azure-armored Dao Warriors.

Before long, all that remained on the plaza were Yun Ni's group and what little remained of the Holy Puppet Sect's forces.

Qilin 9's gaze roamed back and forth between Yun Ni and Bai Suyuan, and he appeared to have been rather hesitant.

"You can go as well," Yun Ni sighed.

Qilin 9 was silent for a moment, then cupped his fist in a salute toward Yun Ni before flying away as a streak of light.

……

Meanwhile, in an area of the Thunderstorm Sea tens of thousands of kilometers away from the Holy Puppet Sect's main island.

A loud thunderclap suddenly rang out as a pillar of lightning as thick as a water vat crashed down from the heavens, striking the surface of the sea to churn up massive waves and raise a vast expanse of water vapor.

Immediately thereafter, a figure emerged from the lightning, standing on the surface of the water.

It was none other than Han Li, and as soon as he appeared, he immediately released his spiritual sense to encompass the entire surrounding area in a radius of thousands of kilometers.

A few moments later, a hint of befuddlement appeared on his face.

Could it be that he's not coming after me? Wait, no...

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he cast his gaze toward a certain direction, and the space several dozen kilometers away began to ripple, following which a cloud of black mist emerged out of thin air before transforming into Zhong Luan.

The befuddlement in Han Li's eyes faded upon seeing this, and he made a hand seal to conjure up another lightning array to teleport himself away.

A mocking sneer appeared on Zhong Luan's face upon seeing this, and he also vanished from the spot as a cloud of black mist.

……

Back on the plaza, the Holy Puppet Sect had fewer than 1,000 members left, and almost all of them were carrying injuries. At this point, they had lost all hope and had already prepared themselves to sink to the bottom of the sea with the main island.

"You should go as well, Mistress," Bai Fengyi said as she took a long glance at Bai Suyuan.

"Ancestor..."

Tears began to well up in Bai Suyuan's eyes.

"Work hard in your cultivation under Mistress, and don't consider vengeance until you've reached a sufficient cultivation base," Bai Fengyi said as she slipped off her storage bracelet before putting it on for Bai Suyuan.

Bai Suyuan was silent for a moment before nodding firmly in response.

"Are you really not going to come with us? Even if I bring the two of you with me, there's no way those two will be able to stop us as long as I sacrifice some of my cultivation base," Yun Ni said to Bai Fengyi through voice transmission.

Bai Fengyi merely shook her head with a faint smile and offered no response.

Yun Ni could tell that she had already made up her mind, so she latched onto Bai Suyuan's hand and was just about to fly away when a loud voice rang out in the distance.

"You're not getting away!"

Yun Ni was rather taken aback to hear this, and she turned to discover Lu Ji and Xue Han emerging from behind the other Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators, all of whom parted to open up a wide path for the two of them.

"Oh? You think you can stop me?" Yun Ni scoffed with a mocking sneer on her face.

Lu Ji's expression remained unchanged as he said in a calm manner, "I can tell that you have close ties with the Holy Puppet Sect, so if I let you leave now, that'll be sure to spell trouble for us down the line."

Xue Han was originally against the idea of facing a Golden Immortal in a battle of life and death, but after hearing what Lu Ji had to say, he also realized that they had no choice but to strike down Yun Ni here.

He knew that it wasn't going to be easy to slay a Golden Immortal even with their combined powers, but that was still a preferable option over having to constantly worry about vengeance from a formidable Golden Immortal like Yun Ni.

"You must really have fallen deeply in love with me if you want to kill me just to keep me. It's a pity that I already have someone I love, so I must go today," Yun Ni said with a seductive smile as she gently tucked some strands of stray hair behind her ear, and all of the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators interspersed throughout the azure-armored Dao Warriors were instantly completely enraptured by her charm.

"Don't fall for her seduction!" Xue Han yelled, and his voice wasn't very loud, but it was clearly audible to all of the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators, who shuddered in unison as they snapped back to their senses before turning to Yun Ni with lingering fear in their eyes.

If Xue Han hadn't snapped them back to their senses, they would've fallen under her control and been reduced to mindless puppets.

"Don't be such a spoilsport. We're significantly outnumbered here, so I was just trying to borrow some people from you," Yun Ni chuckled.

On the surface, she appeared to have been quite relaxed, but internally, she was already considering using that secret technique that would burn through her cultivation base.

"We'll hold them at bay while you get away, Mistress," Bai Fengyi said with a determined expression.

Xue Han immediately burst into laughter upon hearing this, as if he had just been told the most hilarious joke. "You think you can stop us with this ragtag bunch of scrubs? What a joke!"

Before Bai Fengyi had a chance to respond, a thunderous voice suddenly rang out in the heavens.

"I dare you to lay a hand on them!"

Chapter 300: Bad Signs

The voice seemed to have come from somewhere very far away, and it was reverberating incessantly in the sky.

Xue Han and Lu Ji both faltered slightly upon hearing this, and right as everyone was scrambling to see where the voice had come from, a streak of silver light came flying in from afar, dragging a fiery silver tail behind it, much like a comet.

A myriad of emotions welled up in Yun Ni's heart upon seeing this, and Bai Fengyi was slightly dazed for a moment before a hint of surprise appeared in her eyes.

Within the streak of silver light was a silver gourd that was around 70 to 80 feet in size, and it was covered with glowing spirit patterns, giving it quite a remarkable appearance.

A long red rope was tied into a love knot around the tapered section of the gourd, and the two ends of the rope were hanging down and swaying in the wind.

An daoist priest who appeared to have been in his forties was standing on the gourd in a pristine white daoist robe that was flapping in the wind, giving off an air of grace and elegance that was similar to Lu Ji's disposition.

If Han Li had been on the plaza at this moment, he would've been stunned by the sight of the newcomer as the person who was standing on the silver gourd was none other than the seemingly perpetually drunk Elder Hu Yan.

On this day, he had made a drastic change to his usual sloppy appearance. His graying hair had been combed impeccably and arranged into a tall bun under a brand new purplish-golden lotus flower crown, beneath which was a slightly jaded face.

His facial hair had also been carefully groomed, and what was particularly noteworthy was that his normally sleepy and murky eyes were incredibly clear and bright at this moment, giving off a sharp gleam that was completely uncharacteristic of the usual Elder Hu Yan.

Tied around the waist of his pristine daoist robe was a green jade belt, hanging from which was a red wine gourd that had also been restored to brand new condition.

A cold look appeared on Lu Ji's face as he cast his gaze toward Daoist Hu Yan, and his longsword, which had already been returned to its scabbard, was drawn out by several inches once again, with its blade reflecting a bright white gleam.

Xue Han's expression changed slightly at the sight of Daoist Hu Yan, and he laid a hand onto Lu Ji's arm to stay his sword. "I know this man. He's one of the 13 Golden Immortal Stage dao lords of the Blaze Dragon Dao, and he's referred to as Daoist Hu Yan."

Daoist Hu Yan was renowned for being an avid wine enthusiast, as well as a master in the arts of pill refinement and puppetry. In his younger days, he would often leave the sect to go on long journeys, but it had been a very long time since he had last left the Ancient Cloud Continent, so Lu Ji didn't recognize him.

However, as an elder of the Ubiquitous Pavilion, Xue Han knew all of the important figures in the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region like the back of his hand, so he was naturally able to identify Daoist Hu Yan right away.

However, he wasn't wary of Daoist Hu Yan for his identity.

The Ubiquitous Pavilion had records on all 13 Golden Immortal Stage dao lords of the Blaze Dragon Dao, and those records included their history, cultivation arts, cultivation, and even their personalities and likes and dislikes. He clearly recalled all of the information that the Ubiquitous Pavilion had on Daoist Hu Yan, and when it came to the assessment of his combat prowess, the Ubiquitous Pavilion's records only contained one word: "Unknown".

Given how incredibly proficient the Ubiquitous Pavilion was at gathering information, there were definitely no more than 10 people in the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region that had such a status in their records, and Daoist Hu Yan was one of them.

This was a clear indication that he was definitely not someone to be easily messed with.

"If you're going to retreat just from a Golden Immortal's verbal threat, then your Ubiquitous Pavilion is hardly worthy of its status in the Northern Glacial Immortal Realm," Lu Ji said in a cold voice.

"Hold on a second, Fellow Daoist Lu Ji. The fact that he's come here on his own indicates that he's most likely made some preparations, so let's watch the situation unfold for now. If he's unwilling to settle this matter peacefully, then we can examine his power together," Xue Han communicated to Lu Ji through voice transmission while also informing him of the Ubiquitous Pavilion's appraisal of Daoist Hu Yan.

Lu Ji's expression remained unchanged upon hearing this, but he didn't immediately lash out, either.

As for the other Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators, they didn't know who Daoist Hu Yan was, but they could tell that he was on the Holy Puppet Sect's side, and he wasn't making any effort to conceal his immense Golden Immortal Stage aura, so everyone knew that he was no to be messed with.

At the moment, it appeared that the Ubiquitous Pavilion held the upper hand in the battle, but the ones that were truly going to decide the battle were still the Golden Immortal cultivators, and now that both sides had two Golden Immortal cultivators each, the situation had naturally taken a drastic turn.

In fact, many of the Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators were already contemplating retreat.

At the center of the plaza, Yun Ni withdrew the disguise of her Transient Guild mask, and there was a slightly dazed look in her eyes as she looked up at Daoist Hu Yan.

After staring at him for a while, a warm smile appeared on her face.

"You came, after all..." she murmured to herself with a mixture of elation and displeasure in her voice.

In her eyes, Daoist Hu Yan's figure was gradually blurring and overlapping with a younger version of him.

At the time, Hu Yan had been a handsome young man with a perpetually impeccable lotus flower crown on his head, and his white daoist robe was also always pristine, giving him a clean and refined appearance.

Back then, he hadn't been such a heavy drinker, and in the place of that red wine gourd, he had a crimson longsword strapped to his waist, giving him the appearance of a sword immortal more than a daoist priest.

However, later on, that red wine gourd had appeared on his waist, while the crimson longsword was casually strapped to his back, and the sword immortal had turned into a drunken sword immortal that had a more casual and unrestrained flair about him.

He had never been good in matters related to love, and in the love triangle between the three, both he and Bai Fengyi had chosen to run away, while Yun Ni was the only one left actively pursuing an outcome, and she had already lost count of how many years she had been waiting for him.

However, her waiting had finally paid off, and now that he had arrived, he wasn't going to be running away any longer.

Meanwhile, Bai Fengyi was also looking up at Daoist Hu Yan, then turned her gaze to Yun Ni, and a faint smile appeared on her face. In that instant, all of the pent-up guilt and internal conflict in her heart had washed away.

Xue Han took a step forward as he declared, "Dao Lord Hu Yan, need I remind you that your actions are pitting the Blaze Dragon Dao against our Ubiquitous Pavilion?"

"You sure talk big for such a cowardly bastard! There's no need for the sect to intervene, I can take care of this matter on my own," Daoist Hu Yan said in an indifferent voice as he took a disdainful glance at Xue Han.

After that, he removed the wine gourd from his waist and took a swig of wine before sweeping his gaze across the plaza down below.

His brows furrowed slightly as he caught sight of Bai Fengyi, and he murmured to himself in a confused voice, "They don't seem to be as big as I recall..."

Yun Ni couldn't hear what he was saying, but she had a rough idea of what he was referring to judging from the look in his eyes, and her expression immediately darkened slightly.

As for Bai Fengyi, she was feeling a little uneasy under Daoist Hu Yan's scrutiny and unconsciously averted her gaze.

Bai Suyuan had noticed the subtle silent exchanges taking place between the trio, and given what she already knew, she was able to quickly come to some conclusions.

The bastard and coward that Yun Ni had been referring to was most likely none other than Elder Hu Yan.

He's a little old, but he's definitely way more handsome than Elder Li...

As soon as this thought occurred to her, a faint blush immediately appeared on her face, and she couldn't understand why her mind had automatically drawn a comparison between Daoist Hu Yan and Han Li.

Daoist Hu Yan strapped his wine gourd back to his waist, following which he cast a cold gaze toward Lu Ji and Xue Han as he asked, "Are you the ones trying to lay your hands on those fine ladies over there?"

At the same time, the giant silver gourd rapidly shrank down to its original size before returning to his grasp.

"If you want to fight, then let's not waste any time with unnecessary words!" Lu Ji countered as he sprang up into the sky, facing off against Daoist Hu Yan from over 10,000 feet away.

"There's no hurry. It looks like you're enjoying quite a nice numbers advantage here, so how about I give you a taste of your own medicine? I just so happen to have to air out my beans as well. Otherwise, they're about to grow mold," Daoist Hu Yan said with a smile, then made a hand seal with one hand while tipping the silver gourd in his other hand upside-down.

The spirit patterns on the silver gourd began to glow brightly as a burst of white light emerged from the opening of the gourd, following which countless pea-like black beans were poured out onto the ground below.

All of a sudden, close to 1,000 black beans had appeared in the sky, producing a sound that resembled falling rain.

As soon as each bean landed on the ground, it immediately began to glow with black light while swelling rapidly in size, transforming into a giant black Dao Warrior that stood at around 10 feet in height.

These Dao Warriors were far taller than the average person, and they weren't clad in suits of armor. However, each of them was wielding a huge black ax, giving them a very formidable appearance.

These black Dao Warriors were far outnumbered by Xue Han's azure-armored Dao Warriors, but their auras were significantly more powerful, and as opposed to the dazed and wooden expressions on the faces of the azure-armored Dao Warriors, the faces of these black Dao Warriors were far more expressive.

A grim look appeared on Xue Han's face upon seeing this, and thoughts of retreat instantly crept into his mind.

It was clear to him that these Dao Warriors were of a far superior caliber to his own, and at this point in the battle, most of the azure-armored Dao Warriors had already perished, so there was no way that they could contend against their superior adversaries.

Furthermore, with the arrival of Daoist Hu Yan, they had also lost their advantage in Golden Immortal numbers, so there was no point in continuing this battle.

Chapter 301: Baleful Qi

"I don't believe it would be wise to continue this battle any further, Fellow Daoist Lu Ji. Let's make a retreat," Xue Han said to Lu Ji through voice transmission.

"My sword has already been drawn several inches out of its scabbard, I can't just sheath it again for no good reason," Lu Ji replied in a cold voice.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he drew his longsword completely out of its scabbard, sending an enormous streak of white sword qi hurtling directly upward.

"Impressive!" Daoist Hu Yan chuckled as he swept a hand through the air, and a crimson longsword appeared behind him out of thin air.

The golden spirit patterns on the sword's blade were glowing radiantly, and there was a massive sword projection that was over 10,000 feet in length around it. Crimson flames were surging out of either side of the sword projection, resembling a pair of giant fiery wings that had spread open in the sky.

All of a sudden, the air temperature within a radius of hundreds of kilometers elevated sharply, and scorching heat permeated throughout the entire area.

At the same time, the spirit patterns on the giant black axes wielded by all of the black Dao Warriors also lit up with scorching flames, and they lashed out at the azure-armored Dao Warriors and Ubiquitous Pavilion cultivators.

The Holy Puppet Sect cultivators had already resigned themselves to death, and all of them were so elated by this turn of events that many of them had burst into tears. All of the sudden, the tide of the battle was turned once again.

Xue Han heaved a faint sigh upon seeing this, and he was just about to fly toward Lu Ji when Yun Ni and Bai Fengyi rose up into the air to get in his way.

With that, the melee on the plaza resumed.

……

On the Thunderstorm Sea, somewhere hundreds of thousand of kilometers away from the Holy Puppet Sect.

Han Li was standing in mid-air, facing Zhong Luan from afar.

He had used his lightning teleportation array several times up to this point, but he had been unable to shake off Zhong Luan.

"You won't be able to escape from me even if you flee to the corners of this realm, Han Li!" Zhong Luan declared as a mocking sneer appeared on his face.

"That's quite a bit of insolence from someone who's only gained some slight mastery over baleful qi laws. It looks like you're not much better than that idiot junior martial brother of yours!" Han Li jeered.

A cold look appeared in Zhong Luan's eyes upon hearing this. "I didn't think you would be able to identify my baleful qi laws. It appears I may have underestimated you."

"I'm assuming you've been using baleful qi to track me this entire time and to unleash those sneak attacks against me, right?" Han Li chuckled.

"Indeed. The reality is that you've been bringing me with you this entire time, and I haven't had to do anything," Zhong Luan openly admitted with a mocking sneer on his face.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged upon hearing this, but internally, he was rather intrigued.

He didn't actually know much about baleful qi laws as it was a very uncommon type of laws, so he wasn't familiar with what was special about it.

That black thread that Zhong Luan had shot into his body earlier was one that had been manifested from baleful qi laws, and through it, he seemed to be able to track his location and teleport himself to his side.

Aside from that, Han Li could also clearly sense a violent and baleful energy accumulating in his heart. Even with his enormous spiritual sense, he was unable to forcibly suppress it, and the more he tried to do so, the quicker this baleful energy grew.

Han Li had a feeling that once this baleful energy developed to a certain point, that would be when his opponent would unleash his killing blow. Hence, the best course of action would be to finish this battle as soon as possible.

With that in mind, Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to summon his Heavy Water True Axis amid a flash of black light, then sent it hurtling directly toward Zhong Luan.

A faint smile appeared on Zhong Luan's face, and instead of taking any evasive measures, he flew directly toward the axis.

In the instant that the Heavy Water True Axis was about to crash into his body, he transformed into a cloud of black mist once again, allowing him to pass through completely unscathed.

Han Li immediately made a hand seal upon seeing this, and the Water Dao Rune on the Heavy Water True Axis began to glow brightly, while the axis itself swelled to around twice its original size and began to revolve rapidly.

All of the water-attribute spiritual qi in the area was churned up into a frenzy by the axis, which was releasing bursts of incredibly powerful tearing force, and it didn't take long before an enormous vortex took shape on the surface of the sea.

All of a sudden, the cloud of black mist that Zhong Luan had transformed into was sucked into the vortex, quickly vanishing into it before he had a chance to react.

However, Han Li knew that this was far from the end of the battle, and he made a beckoning motion to draw the Heavy Water True Axis back to himself, where it hovered in the air in front of him.

As a result, the vortex of water that had risen up into the heavens cascaded back down into the sea, raising a series of massive waves as it did so.

However, even after the waves had completely subsided, Zhong Luan was still nowhere to be seen.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this. Just now, a burst of aggression had risen up inexplicably in his heart without any warning, and wisps of black mist were also beginning to seep out of his glabella.

Right at this moment, a black shadow suddenly appeared in the seawater down below, much like the ink of a squid, and it quickly spread to stain all of the seawater in a radius of over 10,000 feet black.

Black waves began to churn incessantly on the surface of the sea with wisps of black mist surging out from within.

All of a sudden, a series of enormous waves rose up from all directions like a giant black flower, and its petals closed in around Han Li, attempting to devour him whole.

Han Li immediately tried to take evasive measures, but right this moment, a flash of black light suddenly appeared on his glabella, and he was struck by a burst of sharp pain in his consciousness.

As a result, he was momentarily immobilized, and before he could do anything else, he was completely enveloped within the black wave along with his Heavy Water True Axis.

Han Li inspected his surroundings to find that he was situated in a completely pitch-black space.

Through the use of his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, he was able to see wisps of black mist hovering in the air around him, but he was unable to see very far through it.

At the same time, he discovered that his spiritual sense had also been severely limited, and at this moment, all he could sense was a seemingly boundless expanse of baleful qi around him.

He took a deep breath before sweeping a sleeve through the air, and his Heavy Water True Axis immediately began to revolve rapidly before launching itself forward.

A dull thud rang out as the Heavy Water True Axis struck a wall of water, which shuddered violently a few times before releasing wisps of black mist to ensnare the Heavy Water True Axis, rendering it completely immobilized.

The more immortal spiritual power he tried to inject into the Heavy Water True Axis, the tighter the surrounding wisps of black mist bound themselves to the axis.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he made a hand seal with one hand, and an azure longsword shot out of his sleeve, then split up into 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords amid a flash of azure light before flying away in all directions.

Each sword was glowing with azure light that was releasing more azure sword projections, amounting to several thousand sword projections that instantly filled the entire surrounding space.

If there were anyone situated outside this inky-black space at this moment, then they would be able to see that it was a black ball with a diameter in excess of 1,000 feet, and it was hovering above the sea, constantly absorbing the inky-black seawater down below.

At the same time, countless bulges were appearing incessantly on the surface of the black ball, stretching it into an irregular shape and making it resemble a spiky black ball.

Situated in the sky not far away from the spiky ball was a black crane with a golden crown and a metallic black plumage that had a faint fiery sheen, indicating that this was no ordinary creature.

Atop the crane's back sat Zhong Luan with his legs crossed. His black saber was resting across his hands, and he was staring intently at the black ball up ahead.

All of the spirit patterns on the surface of the black saber were flashing incessantly, and black qi was also surging over its blade.

"He's causing quite a ruckus in there, Master," the black crane said in a high-pitched voice as it swiveled its head around to face Zhong Luan.

"No matter. The more violently he struggles, the faster the baleful aura would converge, and the more he'll be corroded by my baleful aura. When he's completely spent and exhausted, that's when we'll put an end to his life," Zhong Luan replied with a smile.

"We wouldn't have to go through so much trouble if we weren't trying to uncover the secrets that he's harboring. There's no way he would be able to withstand your Black Emperor Immortal Slaying Blade, Master," the black crane said in a fawning voice.

"I'm truly curious about secrets Fang Pan was so desperate to uncover. If I can uncover all of those secrets, that would certainly be worth all the extra time and effort I'm investing here," Zhong Luan said.

As the two of them were conversing with one another, the unrest in the black ball gradually began to fade until it had completely subsided, and at this point, all of the black seawater had already been fused into the black ball.

However, strangely enough, not only had the black ball not become any larger, it had shrunk down significantly instead, and at this moment, it was resembling a giant black crystal.

"Looks like it's about time," Zhong Luan declared as he rose to his feet atop the black crane's back, then sprang up into the air and flew over to the black ball before gently laying a hand upon it.

A burst of black light suddenly appeared at the center of his palm before transforming into a black vortex, and a plume of black smoke immediately surged out of the black ball before entering Zhong Luan's body through the vortex.

As more and more black smoke emerged, the black ball shrank down further and further, and Han Li's figure was gradually revealed.

At this moment, his entire body was completely stiff and still, and his eyes were tightly shut. The baleful qi law thread on his glabella had already disappeared, having been replaced by an inky-black baleful rune that appeared as if it had become a part of his body.

The 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords and the Heavy Water True Axis beside him were all enveloped in a thin layer of black crystal, and they were struggling to break free, but unable to do so.

Zhong Luan gave a pleased nod upon seeing this, then raised a finger toward the baleful rune on Han Li's glabella.

As soon as his fingertip came into contact with the baleful rune, all of the secrets hidden in Han Li's mind would immediately be fully revealed to him.

However, right at this moment, Han Li's eyes suddenly sprang open, and a flash of blue light appeared in his pupils. A translucent thread then shot out of his glabella to shatter the baleful rune before hurtling directly toward Zhong Luan's glabella.

Chapter 302: Fierce Clash

Zhong Luan was clearly caught off guard by this turn of events, and he reflexively sprang back, but didn't take any measures to try and ward off the translucent thread, merely allowing it to fly toward his own glabella.

All of a sudden, a burst of azure light erupted out of the copper headgear on his forehead, and a projection of a four-eyed tiger-like beast emerged before opening its mouth to devour the translucent thread.

Meanwhile, a layer of golden scales had already appeared over Han Li's arm, and his fist was glowing with radiant golden light as he threw an almighty punch toward Zhong Luan's chest.

Zhong Luan forcibly suppressed his own bewilderment as he hurriedly raised his saber before him, then pressed a hand against the flat of the blade to brace it against Han Li's punch.

A resounding boom rang out as a burst of golden light exploded in the sky, and Zhong Luan was sent flying back like an asteroid from the force of the clash, crashing heavily down onto the surface of the sea to raise a flurry of massive waves.

Han Li didn't stop there, making a hand seal with both hands before sweeping his sleeves through the air, and the 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords immediately shattered the black crystal around them, then flew through the air as streaks of azure light before plunging into the sea in pursuit of Zhong Luan.

At the same time, the Water Dao Rune on the Heavy Water True Axis abruptly lit up, and it also broke free from the black crystalline material before crashing down toward the surface of the sea.

All of this had taken place in the span of just a few seconds, and only after this sequence of events had unfolded did the massive black crane in the sky finally react before flapping its wings vigorously downward.

The fiery black light on its wings brightened considerably, and they released a pair of massive black fireballs that hurtled toward the Heavy Water True Axis.

Two resounding booms rang out in succession as black flames erupted over the surface of the Heavy Water True Axis, diverting it slightly to the side and causing it to plow through the sea for a moment before it righted itself and continued to fly back toward Han Li.

Han Li only took a brief glance at the giant black crane before directing his gaze back to the surface of the sea.

Deep in the water, a black shadow rapidly rose upward before flying out into the open with a black saber held tightly in his hand, and he lashed out behind him without any hesitation.

The spirit patterns on the surface of the saber lit up, and one saber projection after another swept toward the sea like waves crashing against the shore.

Immediately thereafter, a series of glowing azure flying swords flew out of the water amid a string of splashes, and they crashed into the waves of saber projections with a piercing grinding sound.

The black saber projections were shattered one after another, while the azure longswords were also stopped in their tracks.

Meanwhile, Zhong Luan continued to fly back through the air before landing on the black crane's back, and he cast a furious gaze toward Han Li.

"I didn't think that you were able to free yourself from the corruption of my baleful qi. Even if your spiritual sense far exceeds that of your peers, there's no way you should've been able to do that. Could it be that you've cultivated the forbidden Spirit Refinement Technique?" Zhong Luan asked.

Han Li remained silent, displaying no intention of offering any response.

He swept his sleeves through the air, and the 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords immediately flew back to him, fusing into a single azure longsword before landing in his grasp.

"It looks like you really are harboring many secrets. No wonder Fang Pan was so determined to hunt you down. I'm really looking forward to capturing your nascent soul and seeing everything concealed in it!" Zhong Luan chuckled.

"Silence is a virtue," Han Li said with an indifferent expression, following which the Mantra Treasured Axis in his body abruptly began to revolve in reverse.

At the same time, over 40 of the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis lit up at once, and he instantly vanished from the spot, not even leaving any afterimages in his wake before appearing on the black crane's back as if through instantaneous teleportation.

Before Zhong Luan even had a chance to figure out what had happened, Han Li's azure longsword had already been plunged through his heart.

Zhong Luan's eyes widened with incredulity as he looked down at the sword protruding out of his chest and the black blood that was pouring out of the wound, which had already seeped through his robes.

"Master!" the black crane screeched in a shrill voice.

Meanwhile, Han Li pulled his longsword out of Zhong Luan's chest without any hesitation before darting back through the air.

He had only just flown off the black crane's back when Zhong Luan's body disintegrated into a cloud of black mist. As it turned out, that had only been a clone formed by baleful qi.

A cloud of black smoke then appeared elsewhere in the sky, and Zhong Luan re-emerged. At this point, all of the mockery in his eyes had been replaced by a cold and solemn look.

Han Li was feeling a little frustrated. His Mantra Treasured Axis still hadn't recovered all 108 of its Time Dao Runes yet, so he wasn't able to fully utilize his Reversal True Axis ability. As a result, he was unable to instantly slay an opponent of Zhong Luan's caliber with a single strike.

"I have indeed underestimated you. I didn't think that you would've also mastered the laws of speed just like Fang Pan, and your speed is even superior to his. No wonder you were able to kill him," Zhong Luan said with a serious expression.

Han Li naturally wasn't going to correct Zhong Luan's misevaluation of his law powers, and he asked, "The fact that you were able to survive that blow must have something to do with Fang Pan, right?"

"That's right. I did indeed prepare that clone as a safeguard against that junior martial brother of mine. He was developing a little too quickly, so I had no choice but to be wary of him, and I certainly didn't think that the clone would save me from someone else instead," Zhong Luan mused.

As he was speaking, he was discreetly making a string of hand seals with one hand concealed behind his back.

The circles of strange patterns on the palm of his hand began to glow with crimson light, and the skin beneath his black cloak was also beginning to take on a red coloration.

A hint of fear and alarm flashed through the black crane's eyes upon seeing this, and two balls of black light were flashing beneath its wings, clearly indicating that it was preparing itself to flee the scene at any moment.

Han Li had naturally noticed all of this, but his expression remained completely unchanged.His Heavy Water True Axis was hovering in front of him like a shield, and he held his azure longsword in one hand, while in his other hand were two balls of Heavy Water Veined Lightning, which he kept concealed up his sleeve.

A burst of chanting rang out as Zhong Luan's pupils turned a crimson color, and wisps of red mist began to rise up from his body. At the same time, his black saber was also gradually taking on a crimson hue.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he could sense a clear change in Zhong Luan's aura. He could still detect baleful qi rising up from his body, but it wasn't the same type of aggressive baleful qi as before.

"It's time to put an end to this battle," Zhong Luan declared as he vanished from the spot as a crimson shadow.

In the next instant, he appeared below Han Li to his right before slashing his saber diagonally upward, lashing out at Han Li from an extremely awkward angle.

Han Li seemed to have already anticipated this, and he swung his longsword downward to clash against the crimson saber, then took advantage of the impact of the clash to fly back through the air and open up some distance between himself and Zhong Luan.

At the same time, the two balls of Heavy Water Veined Lightning had slipped out of his sleeve and fallen down in front of Zhong Luan.

The purple lightning veins on the surface of the balls of veined lightning abruptly lit up, immediately following which came a thunderous explosion.

A devastating halo of purple lightning spread through the air in all directions, encompassing the entire surrounding area in a radius of several thousand feet.

Before the first explosion had a chance to subside, the other ball of Heavy Water Veined Lightning also lit up, but the lightning veins on this one were golden instead of purple.

Another violent explosion rang out, and two enormous black suns rose up above the surface of the sea one after the other, while golden and purple lightning flashed incessantly.

The eruption of light was so bright that it was impossible to see Zhong Luan within it, and the sea down below churned violently as countless tiny black specks of heavy water erupted in all directions, causing the surrounding space to shudder violently.

The explosions had released waves of spherical shockwaves that swept up enormous waves over the surface of the sea, and the black crane had already fled into the distance as a ball of black flames.

At this moment, it was hovering in the sky over 100,000 feet away, looking back at Han Li and Zhong Luan with a fearful look in its eyes.

"It looks like the Divine Devilbane Lightning is still the more powerful of the two," Han Li remarked to himself as he looked at the purple and golden lightning that was flashing above the surface of the sea.

Out of the two balls of Heavy Water Veined Lightning that he had just tossed out, one of them had been refined using the power of the purple crystal that he had obtained from the Thunderstorm Sea, while the other one had been refined using Divine Devilbane Lightning following latest refinement of his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords.

Of the former, he had already expended far too many of them while carrying sect and Transient Guild missions, so he didn't have many left, and as for the former, that was very difficult to refine, so he didn't have many of those, either.

Having just detonated one of each, it was clear that the Heavy Water Veined Lightning that was infused with Divine Devilbane Lightning was the more formidable of the two.

As the explosion subsided, torn scraps of a black cloak could be seen floating on the surface of the sea, and there was a cloud of blood mist hanging in the air, but instead being elated to see this, a grim look appeared in Han Li's eyes.

He could sense Zhong Luan's aura permeating throughout the entire surrounding area in a radius of tens of thousands of feet.

Right at this moment, the surface of the sea, which had already been stained crimson, began to bubble and froth, and it didn't take long before a layer of large bubbles had appeared over the entire surface of the sea in a radius of several hundred kilometers.

Chapter 303: Astonishment

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he cast his gaze toward that area to find the crimson sea churning incessantly.

Turbulent waves were surging on its surface while over 100 massive shadows were slowly rising up from the depths, bringing with them an overwhelmingly nauseating bloody odor.

Han Li activated his Spirit Refinement Technique to protect his consciousness, and he unconsciously tightened his grip on his sword as he inspected the surface of the sea with blue light flashing in his eyes.

Finally, all of the shadows rising up from below emerged out of the water one after another, revealing them to have been a series of different marine demon beasts of all types of different descriptions.

Han Li had seen all of these demon beasts in some of the books that he had read in the past, and he knew that their cultivation bases varied drastically, with the most powerful ones among them already at the True Immortal Stage, but at this moment, all of them were floating belly up on the surface of the sea, and they couldn't have been any more dead.

Each of them had a giant round hole in their abdomen, from within which blood was pouring out incessantly, spreading through the seawater like a massive crimson veil.

Han Li could see that the skin and flesh around those wounds were spread outward, indicating that their bodies had detonated from the inside, rather than the injuries being a result of external force.

All of a sudden, a near animalistic roar rang out, and massive waves swept over the surface of the sea down below.

A massive crimson hand that was over 1,000 feet in size suddenly parted the waves and reached out of the sea to make a grab for Han Li, who immediately darted back in an attempt to avoid it.

However, right as he did so, another identical giant crimson hand emerged from the water right in the path of his retreat before grabbing toward him as well.

Han Li hurriedly changed directions as a streak of azure light, but right at this moment, two more massive crimson hands emerged, one in front of him and one behind, and they were closing in on him from both directions.

The huge crimson hands were astonishingly fast, to the point that Han Li was caught between them before he had a chance to react.

Immediately thereafter, the seawater began to churn violently, and an enormous figure that was over 10,000 feet tall slowly rose up from the depth.

As it turned out, it was a giant crimson figure with clearly defined muscular lines all over its body, and it was completely naked with the exception of an azure loincloth around its waist.

It was like a giant that had just been skinned, and there was still blood all over its exposed muscles. Its face was extremely twisted and horrific, but some semblance of Zhong Luan could still be seen in it.

Aside from the pair of arms attached to its shoulder, the crimson giant had a pair of arms growing from beneath its ribs as well, and it was none other than the hands attached to that lower pair of arms that Han Li was trapped between.

At this moment, Han Li felt as if he were being crushed between a pair of massive mountains, and his bones were creaking and groaning incessantly.

He let loose a loud roar as a layer of golden scales appeared over both of his arms, and he pushed back at the pair of giant palms with all his might.

With his tremendous strength, he was able to push the giant palms slightly to the sides to open up a small gap.

The crimson giant immediately let loose a thunderous roar in response, and it exerted even more force through its hands, forcibly eliminating the gap that Han Li had just barely created between them.

Han Li's face was bright red as he let loose a low roar, and in the next instant, all of his muscles began to bulge as his body swelled up rapidly like a balloon, quickly transforming into a giant golden ape that was over 10,000 feet tall.

At the same time, white light appeared over his body, and seven specks of blue starlight appeared on his chest and abdomen, while his body swelled even further in size.

The giant ape let loose another low roar as it glowered at the crimson giant, then spread its arms open forcefully, and not only was it able to force the crimson giant's hands apart, it was able to grab onto them as well.

The golden ape then twisted its own arms, forcing the crimson giant's hands outward, and the sound of cracking bone instantly rang out, immediately followed by a roar of pain.

However, at the same time, the crimson giant reached out with its other two hands to lock the golden ape's arms in a vice-like grip.

Immediately thereafter, it began to chant an incantation in a rumbling voice, and as it did so, a series of strange corkscrew-shaped patterns on the palms of the hands that were locked around the giant ape's arms, and a pair of crimson snakes slithered out before winding themselves around the golden ape's arms.

Han Li immediately felt a burst of scorching pain shoot through his arms, and he hurriedly released the crimson giant's hands before stumbling back around a dozen steps.

After opening up some distance between himself and the crimson giant, Han Li looked down to find circles of corkscrew-shaped marks running all the way up his arms to his shoulders, and it was as if it had been branded into his skin.

"With my baleful blood mark on your body, you're as good as dead," the crimson giant declared in such a thunderous voice that the surrounding space was quivering incessantly.

As soon as his voice trailed off, it continued to chant its incantation, and a series of giant crimson runes began to appear over its body.

Han Li could feel the scorching pain in his arms becoming more intense by the second, and he leaned forward to plunge his arms into the seawater in an attempt to lessen the pain, but to no avail.

What was even more alarming was that all of his blood essence was currently surging violently through his body like a wild horse that had been let off its reins.

He could clearly sense that the temperature of his blood essence was rapidly rising, as if it were about to be set alight, and it wouldn't be long before it tore through his veins, causing his body to detonate.

If it weren't for the fact that he was a Profound Immortal with a physical body far more formidable than the average True Immortal, and he had cultivated the Organ Refinement Origin Arts, his organs would've most likely already exploded by now.

Han Li was astonished by this turn of events. The baleful qi law powers being wielded by his opponent was extremely difficult to deal with. First, it was the violent baleful qi that had swayed his spiritual sense, and now, this burst of blood baleful qi was attempting to control his blood essence.

He took a moment to compose himself, then attempted to quell the unrest in his blood essence using his immortal spiritual power, but to no avail, once again.

With so many types of power true spirit blood essence infused into his bloodline, his blood essence was far more powerful than that of the average True Immortal, and it was impossible for him to suppress it with his immortal spiritual power alone.

All of a sudden, a draconic roar rang out from within Han Li's body, following which a giant five-clawed golden dragon projection emerged behind him amid a flash of golden light before roaring to the heavens.

The giant ape's face became twisted with agony, and it also let loose a roar of pain.

"You possess a true spirit bloodline in your body? This is fantastic! The heavens are truly smiling down upon me!" the crimson giant exclaimed in an elated voice.

It then made a strange hand seal with all four of its massive hands, and a series of crescent-shaped runes appeared over its body, shimmering with a magma-like crimson and yellow glow.

Immediately thereafter, a clear phoenix cry rang out, and a rainbow phoenix projection emerged behind Han Li as well, hanging in mid-air right next to the golden dragon.

The black crane, which had already retreated to over 100,000 feet away, was very surprised to see this.

"He has more than one type of true spirit bloodline in his body! Normally, possessing multiple true spirit bloodlines would be a great asset, but given Master's abilities, those true spirit bloodlines will only work against him!" the black crane chuckled.

As soon as its voice trailed off, an Azure Luan Bird projection appeared behind the giant ape amid a flash of azure light, followed by a Lightning Bird projection amid a flash of silver lightning.

Immediately thereafter came the projections of a Five-colored Peacock and a giant black turtle.

"Impossible! How could he have this many?" the black crane exclaimed in an incredulous voice.

At this moment, it wanted nothing more than to grow a pair of hands to rub its own eyes. It was simply in complete disbelief that someone could possess so many powerful true spirit bloodlines, particularly a human, which had the weakest physical body among all races.

Another agonized roar erupted out of the giant ape's mouth, and the true spirit projections hovering behind it suddenly began to struggle violently, with someone trying to rise up into the heavens and others trying to descend into the sea.

The crimson marks on the giant ape's arms also began to glow brightly, and the unrest in its blood essence was becoming even more violent, causing it to crash through its veins like a wild bull.

This scorching sensation that came from within his body was even more painful than having his skin peeled and his bones plucked out.

Han Li could sense that the blood essence in his body was only continuing to grow more violent, and it would break out of his body as soon as it reached a certain threshold.

Once that happened, he would end up just like those dead marine demon beasts floating on the surface of the sea.

Chapter 304: Baleful Spirit Threads

The crimson giant could tell that Han Li was close to reaching his limits, and a ghastly smile appeared on its hideous face as it roared, "It's time for you to die!"

With this declaration, Han Li immediately felt the agony in his body increase by severalfold, and it was as if there were countless sharp needles piercing back and forth through his meridians and even his bones.

A layer of faint golden light appeared in his eyes, and he threw his head back and let loose a thunderous roar as he gave up on trying to suppress his blood essence with his immortal spiritual power, dedicating it fully to activating his Provenance True Devil Arts instead.

A layer of purplish-golden scales appeared over his body, and two fearsome-looking heads and four purplish-golden arms emerged on his shoulders and below his ribs, respectively.

The six eyes on the three giant ape heads sprang open in unison, and a short silver horn appeared on the forehead of the two heads on either side of the central one.

After unleashing his Holy Nirvana Physique, the true spirit projections that were threatening to break free flew back into his body one after another, and as a result, Han Li grew significantly taller once again, allowing him to tower over the crimson giant.

The purplish-golden scales all over his body connected together to form a suit of purplish-golden armor with countless antiquated runes inscribed onto its surface, and it encased Han Li's entire body while giving off an extremely formidable aura.

In the distance, Zhong Luan was looking on with an astonished expression.

He couldn't understand for the life of him how Han Li had managed to escape from the control of his baleful blood mark, and a sense of unease had welled up in his heart at the sight of this new transformation that Han Li had adopted.

In reality, Han Li wasn't confident that his Provenance True Devil Arts would be able to suppress the true spirit blood essence in his body, and he had only unleashed so that all of his true spirit bloodlines would be unified and guided to a collective cause, rather than continuing to rampage under the effects of the baleful blood mark.

Back in the Spirit Realm, he would often use all of his true spirit bloodlines to unleash his Holy Nirvana Physique, so this was not an alien process to him.

His three heads grinned in unison, following his six giant arms flashed through the air in a blur, unleashing countless projections that hurtled directly toward Zhong Luan.

All of a sudden, countless golden fist projections emerged to obscure the entire sky before abruptly vanishing into the thin air.

Almost at the exact same moment, the space around the crimson giant surged and churned violently, and countless golden fist projections emerged out of thin air before crashing toward it with devastating force.

The crimson giant immediately raised its four arms and swung them rapidly through the air to unleash a flurry of fist projections of its own, and a string of resounding booms rang out incessantly.

Before the clashes between the golden and crimson fist projections had a chance to subside, an enormous figure sprang up into the air, then came crashing down upon the crimson giant like a mountain. Raised above the enormous figures head was a huge crimson longsword, which was also being swung down with tremendous force.

In response, the crimson giant raised two of its hands and made a grabbing motion to conjure up a huge crimson saber, which it used to parry the massive azure longsword.

A thunderous boom rang out as the azure sword struck the crimson saber, sending a burst of astonishing force crashing down. The crimson giant was forced to one knee, and the back of its huge saber had also sunk deep into the flesh on its shoulder.

At the same time, massive waves swept over the surface of the sea, and even countless fish and marine demon beasts that were situated thousands of kilometers away were killed from the force of the almighty blow.

After forcing the crimson giant to one knee, Han Li strode forward before stomping a foot down onto the giant's chest.

Crimson light flashed within the giant's eyes, and a massive opening abruptly appeared on its chest, within which were countless jagged white fangs that closed in viciously around the giant ape's leg like an enormous bear trap.

However, all it saw was a blur flash before its eyes, following which it was struck by a burst of sharp pain in the chest.

As it turned out, the white fangs in its chest didn't even get a chance to open up before it was trodden on by the giant ape's foot, instantly snapping several dozen of them.

Furthermore, such was the force behind the enormous ape's stomp that a massive hole had sunken into the crimson giant's chest.

The crimson giant threw up a mouthful of blood as it thrust its long saber upward with all its might while punching at the giant ape with its other two hands.

The giant ape didn't back down, continuing to force its sword downward while retaliating with its four remaining fists.

The crimson giant's two arms were no match for the ferocious barrage from the giant ape's four arms, and it was being comprehensively dominated.

A string of loud thumps rang out, and all of the seawater down below was quivering incessantly with every single thump.

Before long, the crimson giant's chest and arms had been pummeled into a mangled mass of flesh and blood, presenting a sorry sight to behold.

Right at this moment, Han Li suddenly reached out with two of his hands to grab onto the pair of arms that Zhong Luan was using to hold his saber. As a result, he was able to liberate his sword-wielding arms, and he pulled the sword back before slashing it toward the crimson giant's head.

The crimson giant was greatly alarmed by this turn of events, and it immediately attempted to take evasive measures, but it was unable to go anywhere as it was being crushed under the giant ape's weight.

A thunderous howl rang out as half of its head was cut off by the crimson longsword, and having lost its head, the crimson giant's four arms instantly slumped down in a limp manner.

"Master!" the black crane called out in alarm from afar.

Never in all of its years by Zhong Luan's side had it ever seen him be reduced to such a sorry state, and its eyes were filled with wariness as it cast its gaze toward Han Li.

All of a sudden, the giant ape raised a hand, and a burst of golden light appeared on its palm as it prepared to lash out at what remained of the crimson giant's head.

However, all of a sudden, the crimson giant's body suddenly dissolved into a puddle of viscous bloody sludge that enveloped three of the giant apes hands and one of its feet.

The sludge then immediately began to exert enormous suction force that locked those hands and that foot firmly into place, making Han Li feel as if he had stepped into quicksand.

At the same time, a series of peculiar golden threads appeared within the sludge, resembling a school of fish that was swimming through it, and they were traveling toward the giant ape's arms and leg.

A sense of foreboding welled up in Han Li's heart as he detected the law fluctuations emanating from these golden threads, and he hurriedly drew upon his immortal spiritual power with all his might to try and extricate his arms and leg, but he was only able to pull them out around 10 feet before they refused to budge any further.

At this point, the golden threads had already arrived and were piercing toward him like golden needles.

Despite the layer of purplish-golden scales that covered his entire body, the golden threads were still able to pierce into his flesh without any impediment.

As soon as the golden threads entered his body, Han Li was immediately struck by a numb sensation, immediately following which all of his immortal spiritual power began to surge out of his body in a frenzy like floodwaters through a broken dam.

All of those thin threads were like a series of wide rivers that were channeling his immense immortal spiritual power out of his body and into that huge puddle of bloody sludge.

Han Li struggled vigorously to try and break free, but with the rapid loss of immortal spiritual power, the light radiating from his body gradually turned dim, and he also shrank down rapidly in size.

In just a few moments, he had reverted back to his normal human form, and half of his body was trapped in the sludge.

He was still completely unable to move, but thankfully, the golden threads that were funneling his immortal spiritual power out of his body had also disappeared.

Prior to unleashing his Holy Nirvana Physique, he had already stowed away his Transient Guilt mask, and at this moment, his exposed face was slightly pale, while his brows were tightly furrowed.

Over 1,000 feet away from him, a part of the puddle of sludge began to surge like a wave, quickly manifesting the top half of Zhong Luan's body, while the bottom half of his body was still fused with the sludge on the surface of the sea.

"I really did underestimate you. You've forced me to use the baleful spirit threads that I've been accumulating over the course of tens of thousands of years. If I don't manage to unearth all of your secrets, this will have been an extremely severe loss," Zhong Luan said in a cold voice.

His complexion wasn't much better than Han Li's, indicating that the immortal spiritual power that had been funneled away hadn't been directed into his body.

"Whose orders are you acting under? Why do you insist on hunting me down at every turn?" Han Li asked with a cold look in his eyes.

At the same time, he had already summoned an Immortal Origin Stone, which he was holding in his hand that was concealed within the blood sludge, and he was quickly absorbing the immortal spiritual power inside.

"I don't know whose instructions Fang Pan was acting under, but you should worry about yourself right now. How about you tell me why Fang Pan and the others were so eager to hunt you down? That would save me the effort of having to search your soul. The soul search technique that I use is rather unique, and I'm sure you wouldn't like it," Zhong Luan said.

"It just so happens to be the case that I've always been quite interested in soul search techniques, so I actually wouldn't mind seeing just what's so unique about yours," Han Li replied as a faint smile appeared on his face.

"Fine. If you insist on being punished, then I'll grant your wish," Zhong Luan harrumphed coldly.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he made a grabbing motion with one hand, and the long crimson saber appeared in his grasp.

Immediately thereafter, he began to slide rapidly toward Han Li like a wave, then raised the crimson saber in his hand, and all of the patterns on the blade of the saber began to radiate dazzling crimson light before the saber was swung down upon Han Li.

Chapter 305: Pulling Out All the Stops

Han Li clenched his fists tightly before raising them with all his might, but he couldn't raise them at all, as if there were a pair of mountains strapped to them.

The crimson saber projection reached him in the blink of an eye, but right when it was no more than 100 feet away and was about to strike his head, it suddenly slowed down to a snail's pace, as if it had sliced into layers of extremely resilient golden fabric.

At the same time, Han Li's Mantra Treasured Axis appeared behind him amid a flash of golden light, and it was slowly revolving while the 40 or so lit Time Dao Runes on its surface were releasing circles of golden ripples.

Several hundred feet away, Zhong Luan could sense the law fluctuations emanating from the Mantra Treasured Axis, and he discovered that no matter how much force he exerted, he was unable to force the crimson saber projection down any faster.

A thought immediately occurred to him, and his expression changed drastically as he exclaimed, "Could this be... the power of time laws? Burn him to death! Hurry!"

Upon realizing that Han Li was able to wield time law powers, he immediately decided against trying not to harm Han Li's soul, and he shifted his focus to taking down his opponent as quickly as possible.

The longer the battle wore on, the more he came to realize that Han Li wasn't someone that he could enforce his will over as he pleased.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a shrill cry rang out in the sky, and the giant black crane swooped down from the heavens while flapping its wings vigorously to send a sea of scorching black flames sweeping directly toward Han Li.

As soon as the black flames entered the golden ripples, the speed of their descent also slowed down to a crawl, rendering them unable to get close to Han Li for the time being.

Right at this moment, a tiny fiery silver figure appeared on Han Li's shoulder amid a flash of silver light, and it patted its own belly as it cast its gaze toward the oncoming sea of black flames, looking as if it were eager to embrace the feast being offered.

"Go on," Han Li instructed, and the fiery silver figure instantly sprang up into the air, then transformed into a giant silver fire raven that flew directly toward the sea of black flames.

At the same time, a vast expanse of silver flames emerged from its body as well to clash against the black flames, while the silver fire raven itself pounced at the giant black crane.

High up in the sky, a fierce battle ensued between the two huge birds, one silver and one black, as they released bursts of flames out of their wings.

At this point, Zhong Luan's expression had already become extremely grim. He continued to force his saber down with one hand while making a hand seal with the other before plunging it into the bloody sludge down below.

As soon as he did this, circles of runes instantly appeared out of thin air around his hand before spreading outward in all directions.

The bloody sludge on the surface of the sea instantly began to churn as massive waves were raised before sweeping toward Han Li, but they were also unable to escape the fate of being slowed down by Han Li's Mantra Treasured Axis.

The giant crimson waves around Han Li resembled a series of tall crimson walls that surrounded him from all directions, and it seemed that he was able to deal with all of the oncoming attacks with ease, but in reality, he was struggling immensely.

He had exhausted too much of his immortal spiritual power, and even though he had been able to replenish some of it using an Immortal Origin Stone, he still wasn't going to be able to support his Mantra Treasured Axis for long.

Han Li made a hand seal with one hand as he chanted an incantation, and a vast expanse of azure light instantly surged out of the bloody sludge down below.

Immediately thereafter, 72 Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords appeared before traversing arduously through the sludge, releasing countless streaks of azure swordlight that intertwined to form a huge ball of azure light beneath him.

Immediately thereafter, an earth-shattering draconic roar rang out, and the ball of azure light beneath Han Li exploded violently as an azure coiled dragon rushed out before ascending straight toward the heavens.

Han Li was standing atop the dragon's head, and thanks to the Azure Coil Sword Array, he was able to force his way out of the bloody sludge and rise up into the air.

He had only just steadied himself when the Mantra Treasured Axis behind him shrank down into a ball of golden light before flying back into his body.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged as he scrutinized Zhong Luan intently while flipping a hand over to produce an azure pill. After swallowing the pill, he summoned another Immortal Origin Stone, with which he began to replenish his immortal spiritual power while making a grabbing motion with his other hand.

The azure coiled dragon immediately split apart into 72 azure flying swords once again, then fused into a single azure longsword that flew into his grasp.

With the Mantra Treasured Axis gone, Zhong Luan was able to move at his normal speed again, and he slammed his hands down onto the bloody sludge below to raise an enormous wave that propelled him into the sky.

At the same time, he opened his mouth to release a translucent crimson thread that shot into the palm of his hand.

The flesh on his hand was instantly exposed before slowly squirming as it fused itself into one with the crimson saber in his hand, and a pained look appeared on his face as he gave an involuntary groan.

At the same time, the patterns on the surface of the crimson saber in his hand began to bulge like veins while pulsing incessantly, as if it really were a living creature with blood coursing through its veins.

Zhong Luan's body was still fused with the bloody sludge down below, and a series of cobweb-like golden patterns had lit up all over his body, extending all the way down into the crimson sea below.

As the veins on the crimson saber continued to pulse, the bloody sludge in the sea began to turn into pure baleful blood qi that flowed into the saber through these golden veins.

As a result, the saber swelled to around twice its original size, and it was giving off extremely formidable law fluctuations while the baleful blood qi emanating from it filled virtually the entire area of the sea.

By the time Zhong Lan was no more than 1,000 feet away from Han Li, all of the bloody sludge below him had completely flowed into his crimson saber, but the veins on the blade were still pulsing incessantly, as if it were yet to be satiated.

His muscles began to slowly atrophy, and his cheeks also became sunken, making it appear as if the crimson saber were sucking him dry.

"Die!" Zhong Luan roared as he swung his crimson saber through the air in a circle, causing the surrounding space to tremble violently while unleashing a vast expanse of saber projections that swept toward Han Li.

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face as he tightened his grip around his longsword, but instead of defending himself, he yelled, "Let heaven and earth be turned on their heads!"

The orientation of the sky and the sea was instantly flipped, with the boundless sea taking the place of the sky, while the cloudy sky appeared down below, presenting an extremely bizarre sight to behold.

This was naturally quite jarring to Zhong Luan, and it was very difficult for him to process exactly what had happened in a short time.

All he could see was that his all-out slash was suddenly being directed toward the sea, which was the complete opposite direction to where Han Li was.

He immediately gritted his teeth and forcibly changed the trajectory of his slash, wrenching his crimson saber upward so that his attack would be back on track.

The massive saber projection unleashed by the crimson saber was glowing with golden light and emanating formidable baleful blood qi as it tore Han Li's body in half down the middle.

More saber projections immediately followed in a relentless barrage, and only after unleashing over 300 slashes did Zhong Luan finally exhaust all of the baleful blood qi in his crimson saber.

A string of resounding booms rang out as crimson light exploded in the air, and the clouds churned violently, while the surrounding space also shuddered incessantly.

"There's no way you're not dead after that!" Zhong Luan chortled, and at this point, the saber in his hand had already reverted back to its original black color.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the sound of someone snapping their fingers rang out in the sky, and heaven and earth were immediately restored to their original orientation.

The sky was still filled with dark clouds, but a deep trench that was several hundred kilometers in length had appeared in the sea down below, within which crimson baleful qi was surging incessantly, parting the seawater like a miraculous act of the gods.

Zhong Luan's entire body instantly stiffened upon seeing this, and he slowly shifted his gaze upward with an incredulous expression, where Han Li was standing with a mocking sneer on his face, completely unscathed.

"How..." Zhong Luan murmured to himself.

Han Li's sneer grew even wider upon hearing this, and he eagerly rubbed some more salt into Zhong Luan's wounds. "Everything you saw just now was nothing more than an illusion."

The all-out attack that he had just unleashed had exhausted virtually all of his immortal origin stones and baleful blood qi, leaving him unfit for further battle. In contrast, Han Li had taken advantage of this opportunity to replenish a large chunk of his immortal spiritual power through the use of Immortal Origin Stones.

At this point, it seemed like the outcome of the battle was already decided.

"Don't think you've won just yet!"

A vicious look appeared in Zhong Luan's eyes as he raised an arm, and the black saber, which had already detached itself from his body, was sent hurtling rapidly toward Han Li.

In response, Han Li lashed out with his azure longsword to strike the black saber, but in the instant that the two blades clashed, a tiny crack suddenly appeared on the surface of the black saber amid a flash of crimson light.

Han Li immediately tried to stay his sword upon seeing this, but it was already too late.

A resounding boom rang out as a crimson sun that was over 10,000 feet in size rose up over the surface of the sea, radiating incredibly dazzling crimson light.

In the next instant, a burst of devastating shockwaves erupted in all directions, sweeping up enormous waves that swept over the surface of the sea down below.

Having just detonated his bonded treasure, Zhong Luan threw up a mouthful of blood, then crushed a black jade pendant that he was already holding in his hand.

A cloud of black mist surged out of the crushed jade pendant to envelop his body, and he vanished on the spot right before the waves arrived.

Chapter 306: Avoiding Trouble

Meanwhile, high up in the sky tens of thousand of kilometers away, Zhong Luan's giant black crane steed let loose a sharp cry, sending a wave of scorching black flames sweeping toward the giant silver fire raven situated over 10,000 feet away.

Immediately thereafter, it turned toward the direction where the crimson sun had just exploded with a hint of lingering fear in its eyes.

Thankfully, it had been chased all the way here by the silver fire raven. Otherwise, just the shockwaves from that explosion alone would've been almost too much for it to withstand.

In the face of the oncoming wave of black flames, the silver fire raven flapped its wings vigorously to release a series of balls of silver light, which exploded one after another into silver flames to destroy the approaching black flames.

A hint of wariness flashed through the black crane's eyes, and it jeered, "Cease your futile resistance, your master is already dead!"

The silver fire raven faltered slightly upon hearing this, then let loose a sharp cry as the silver flames around its body swelled up before forming a giant fireball that was launched through the air, absorbing all of the scorching black flames in its path.

The black crane had no intention of continuing this battle any longer, and it swooped down from the sky while the silver fire raven was obstructed by its black flames.

All of a sudden, it changed directions in its flight, and a cloud of black mist appeared in the air tens of thousands of feet away in that direction.

Zhong Luan then stumbled out of the black mist before landing on the black crane's back right as it was flying past.

"We have to get away from here! Hurry!" Zhong Luan yelled in an urgent voice as soon as he landed on the black crane's back.

The black crane didn't dare to delay, and it immediately flapped its wings vigorously to fly away.

However, right at this moment, countless arcs of golden lightning intertwined in the air up ahead over 10,000 feet away, immediately following which a golden lightning array that was several dozen feet in size appeared.

Han Li then emerged amid a tumbling thunderclap with an azure longsword that was crackling with arcs of golden lightning, which he swung down upon Zhong Luan.

A hint of despair appeared in Zhong Luan's eyes at the sight of Han Li. He had just detonated his bonded treasure, yet it hadn't managed to harm Han Li at all.

He made a grabbing motion in front of his own chest, and a translucent round shield instantly flew out before situating itself in front of him.

At the same time, what little remained of the baleful blood qi in his body surged forth to manifest a suit of crimson armor.

Before the spirit patterns on the suit of armor had a chance to completely take shape, the azure longsword had already arrived.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as several dozen bolts of golden lightning erupted from the surface of the crimson shield, dancing through the air like whips of the lightning gods.

A string of crackling rang out incessantly, and an acrid charred odor wafted through the air.

Immediately thereafter, a faint crack rang out, and the crimson shield in front of Zhong Luan was shattered, following which Han Li's longsword came slashing down.

All of a sudden, a burst of azure light appeared in front of Zhong Luan's forehead. The azure light was coming from his copper headgear, and it was able to stop Han Li's sword in its tracks.

Han Li let loose a loud roar as golden scales appeared over his arms, and he forced his azure longsword down with all his might.

At the same time, arcs of azure lightning erupted out of the runes on the sword to complement its attack.

"No!"

Zhong Luan let loose an indignant roar as the copper headgear on his head cracked open.

Without anything left to oppose it, Han Li's longsword came crashing down to slice Zhong Luan's head into two, and the black crane began to plummet toward the sea as if it had been dealt a heavy blow.

Right as it was about to land in the sea, it suddenly flapped its wings and increased its altitude before flying away into the distance.

Without even requiring an instruction from Han Li, the Essence Fire Raven immediately set off in pursuit.

Meanwhile, Han Li grabbed onto Zhong Luan's collar to catch his lifeless body, and after sweeping his spiritual sense over Zhong Luan's remains, his brows furrowed ever so slightly.

Right at this moment, the shockwaves from the explosion of the crimson sun arrived, and even they were less than a thousandth as powerful as they would've been at the epicenter of the explosion, they still swept past Han Li as gusts of fierce wind, evoking within him a sense of lingering fear.

He had only noticed that something was wrong in the instant that the black saber exploded, and it was already too late for him to defend himself. In that dire situation, all he could do was call upon his Mantra Treasured Axis again to delay the explosion of the crimson sun for a brief moment, and that window of opportunity allowed him to unleash his Reversal True Axis ability to escape.

After that, he used his spiritual sense to determine Zhong Luan's location, then chased him down with his lightning teleportation array.

All of a sudden, a burst of black light flashed in Zhong Luan's right sleeve, and a black nascent soul wearing a transparent cloak flew out from within, then instantly vanished from the spot with a flash of black light.

However, immediately thereafter, a loud explosion rang out, and the nascent soul stumbled out of thin air several thousand feet away amid a burst of violent spatial fluctuations.

It turned around with a horrified expression to find Han Li looking at it in an expressionless manner with a vertical black eye on his glabella.

"The Law Destruction Eye..."

Zhong Luan's heart was plunged into complete despair.

Before the nascent soul had a chance to get away again, Han Li slashed his sword through the air to unleash a streak of azure sword light, which swept up Zhong Luan's nascent soul and the transparent cloak that it was wearing before tearing both to shreds.

Even after Zhong Luan's nascent soul was completely vanquished, Han Li still made sure to inspect the surrounding area carefully with his Brightsight Spirit Eyes.

Only after verifying that not even the slightest hint of Zhong Luan's aura remained did he withdraw his Brightsight Spirit Eyes, following which he stowed Zhong Luan's storage bracelet away before setting off in pursuit of the black crane.

At this point, the silver fire raven had already caught up to the black crane, and it had formed a massive ring of silver flames to trap the black crane inside.

The black crane was struggling with all its might to escape, but to no avail.

Never could it have imagined that its master would be defeated by such an ordinary-looking young man, yet this was the undeniable reality, and it had no choice but to believe it.

With Han Li closing in at a rapid rate, the black crane hurriedly yelled in a panicked voice, "Spare me, Senior! I'm a primordial bird with an innate mastery over fire-attribute laws! If you spare my life, I'm willing to accept you as my master! Also, I know a lot of Zhong Luan's secrets!"

However, Han Li paid no heed to the black crane's desperate pleas for mercy, and he made a hand seal with one hand while plunging his azure longsword straight down with his other hand.

A massive sword projection that was over 1,000 feet in length erupted out of the tip of the sword, piercing through the black crane's head in an instant.

The black crane let loose an anguished howl before plummeting toward the sea, followed closely by Han Li, who reached down to pluck its nascent soul out of its head.

The nascent soul was a projection of a tiny black crane, and it was struggling with all its might in Han Li's grasp with a horrified look on its face.

The Essence Fire Raven swooped down and transformed into a fiery silver child that landed on Han Li's shoulder, and there was a clear look of yearning in its eyes as it gazed upon the black crane's nascent soul.

"You can have it soon," Han Li reassured with a smile, then closed his eyes as a burst of azure light emerged from his hand to envelop the nascent soul.

A short while later, Han Li slowly opened his eyes with a series of mixed emotions in his heart.

The black crane didn't have many memories that contained information on Fang Pan, but from what little memories pertaining to Fang Pan that it did have, Han Li could tell that Zhong Luan was telling the truth in that he didn't know who had instructed Fang Pan to come after him.

In the black crane's memories, Han Li also saw that earthy yellow palace situated in the vast desert, as well as the black chains that littered the entire floor of the palace, and he immediately thought of the Origin Separation Law Chains.

He saw the large black chair at the center of the palace and a figure dressed in the white cloak seated on the chair, but no matter how hard he tried, he was unable to make out the figure's facial features.

The black crane seemed to have been extremely fearful of this person, to the point that it didn't even dare to look directly at him.

After a brief moment of silence, Han Li tossed the black crane's nascent soul to the fiery silver child, then flew onto the black crane's back to recover Zhong Luan's storage bracelet, among other items.

The fiery silver child gleefully accepted the black crane's nascent soul, eagerly devouring it whole.

A burst of light then began to glow through its round little belly, as if there were a scorching flame burning in its stomach.

After extracting the black crane's demon core, Han Li turned back to the Essence Fire Raven to find that after devouring the black crane's nascent soul, it was beginning to stumble around as if it were drunk.

However, through their spiritual connection, he could sense that it was fine, and he made his way over to the fiery silver child before plucking it up with one hand and withdrawing it back into his body.

After that, he pulled out a pill and devoured it, then cast his gaze back toward the Holy Puppet Sect with a contemplative look on his face.

Given the situation that he had witnessed earlier, the Holy Puppet Sect was most likely beyond saving, so if he were to go back, he would've only been risking his own safety for no reason.

Furthermore, he had only been hired by the Holy Puppet Sect for protection, and he certainly wasn't going to risk his life for the sect.

On top of that, Zhong Luan had ventured into the Holy Puppet Sect's restricted area prior to his, and even though he didn't know what Zhong Luan's objective was, now that he had slain Zhong Luan, going back to the Holy Puppet Sect would've only spelled trouble.

As for the reward for this mission, he was happy to leave it. After all, he had reaped a great deal of spoils from killing several True Immortal cultivators on this mission, and those spoils were more than enough compensation.

With that in mind, he took one final glance in the direction of the Holy Puppet Sect before flying away as a streak of azure light.

Chapter 307: Immortal Puppet

The seasons passed, and over a year flew by in a flash.

On this day, a streak of azure light descended onto the Crimson Dawn Peak, then faded to reveal Han Li.

He hadn't made any effort to conceal himself, so it didn't take long before all of the servants in his cave abode were assembled to see him in the courtyard, but Meng Yungui and Sun Buzheng weren't among them.

"When did you get back, Qianqian?" Han Li asked as he swept his gaze over the eight servants.

"I only got back less than a month ago. Here are some spirit medicine seeds found by my brother and Brother Sun, they asked me to pass the seeds onto you," Meng Qianqian said as she handed Han Li a storage pouch.

Han Li accepted the storage pouch, then flipped a hand over to produce three more storage pouches that he offered to Meng Qianqian as he said, "Good. If you get the chance to meet them, pass these spirit stones and pills onto them. Also, you can distribute these pills among everyone in my stead."

Meng Qianqian accepted the storage pouches as she nodded in response. "Yes, Elder Li!"

"Has anything of note happened on our Crimson Dawn Peak or in the sect during the past few years I've been away?" Han Li asked.

"Everything has been fine on our Crimson Dawn Peak, and not much has happened in the sect, either. However, I've heard that a Golden Immortal Stage dao lord will be coming out of seclusion soon and will be preaching about the Great Dao, but the spots are very limited, and generally speaking, only direct disciples are entitled to attend," Meng Qianqian replied with a hint of longing in her eyes.

The same expression was mirrored on the faces of all of the other servants, but at the same time, they were also looking a little dejected. After all, they would've been sure to benefit immensely from hearing the preaching of a Golden Immortal, but they knew that True Immortal servants like them had no chance of being allowed to attend.

"While it's true that hearing the preaching of a powerful cultivator is a brilliant opportunity, everyone's cultivation path is different. You can listen to the experiences of others, but ultimately, you have to figure things out for yourself. In order to fulfill the Great Dao, you must forge a path of your own, do you understand?" Han Li asked.

Meng Qianqian faltered slightly upon hearing this before nodding in response, and the disappointment in the eyes of all of the servants immediately faded.

"Alright, if there's nothing else you have to report, then you can all go for now," Han Li said with a dismissive wave.

Meng Qianqian and the others extended a collective bow before departing.

Meanwhile, Han Li remained standing on the spot for a while before entering his cave abode, and after activating all of the restrictions, he made his way into his secret chamber before sitting down with his legs crossed.

With a sweep of his sleeve, he summoned a trio of storage treasures, which he had obtained from the three True Immortals that he had slain back at the Holy Puppet Sect.

Prior to this, he had been focused solely on making the return journey, so he didn't get the chance to examine his spoils. Now that he had finally returned to his cave abode, he was naturally eager to see what he had obtained.

With that in mind, Han Li picked up a storage bracelet before emptying all of its contents, which spilled out onto the floor.

However, after a quick inspection, his brows furrowed slightly in disappointment.

These were the belongings of the burly man who had attempted to fight Han Li on his own, and he was so impoverished that his belongings consisted only of a few materials and spirit medicines, as well as several ordinary spirit treasures. Aside from that, there were only around a dozen Immortal Origin Stones, a pile of spirit stones, and some other miscellaneous items.

Given how impoverished he was, it was no wonder that he was willing to risk his life for that Ubiquitous Pavilion mission.

Han Li could only lament his own ill-fortune, but nevertheless, he still patiently categorized everything before stowing them away into his own storage bracelet. After that, he picked up the thin old man's storage treasure before emptying its contents as well.

This time, he was much more pleased with what he saw.

The majority of the old man's belongings consisted of materials of a high caliber. In particular, there were several crimson crystals around the size of human heads, and they were giving off fiery red radiance, as if they were red-hot chunks of metal.

These crimson crystals were filled with extremely abundant spiritual qi, and there were fiery patterns on their surface that were giving off fire-attribute law fluctuations, indicating that it was a type of material that contained law powers.

Aside from that, there were also around a dozen treasures, most of which were spirit treasures, as well as several vials of pills, over 500 Immortal Origin Stones, and a large pile of spirit stones.

Han Li stowed these items away as well before turning to Zhong Luan's storage bracelet, which he had saved for the finale.

He had already anticipated that Zhong Luan was most likely going to be quite wealthy, but he was still astonished by what he saw after emptying out the storage bracelet's contents.

There were countless types of spirit materials and spirit medicines, some of which contained law powers, and setting aside the spirit treasures, pills, and scriptures for now, there were around 5,000 to 6,000 Immortal Origin Stones as well.

The spiritual light radiating from all of the Immortal Origin Stones illuminated the entire secret chamber, and with all of this, in addition to everything that he had saved up thus far, he would most likely have sufficient funds to support his own cultivation for the next few centuries.

Han Li immediately stowed the Immortal Origin Stones away before slowly sorting through the rest.

"Origin Separation Treasured Scripture?"

Han Li faltered slightly after injecting his spiritual sense into a white jade slip, and a thought immediately occurred to him, following which he hurriedly began to inspect the jade slip's contents.

By the time he removed the jade slip from his forehead, over two hours had already passed by.

The initial section of the jade slip contained a devilish True Immortal Stage cultivation art of a very high caliber by the name of the Origin Separation Yin Devil Arts. It was said that one could cultivate this cultivation art to the High Zenith Stage, and it was no lesser in rarity than his Mantra Axis Scripture.

However, no matter how formidable this cultivation art was, there was no way that Han Li would abandon the Mantra Axis Scripture for it. What he was more interested in were the secret techniques recorded in the latter section of the jade slip. In particular, there was a secret technique that allowed one to conceal their aura by sealing themselves, and that was very intriguing to Han Li.

However, these secret techniques were very difficult to grasp, and they weren't something that he could master anytime soon.

With that in mind, Han Li stowed the jade slip away before continuing to sort through everything else.

"Hmm? What's this?"

All of a sudden, Han Li spotted a strange-looking yellow ball among the treasures. It had a diameter of roughly half a foot, and there were numerous profound yellow patterns engraved onto its surface, giving it quite a mysterious appearance.

The ball had been buried under some materials earlier, so he hadn't noticed it initially. Furthermore, there were several white talismans adhered to the ball's surface, seemingly acting as a seal.

Han Li brought the ball closer to his eyes for inspection, but was still not able to see anything special about it.

Furthermore, it wasn't giving off any energy or aura fluctuations, and it didn't appear to have been a treasure.

After a moment of contemplation, he decided to try and examine the item using his spiritual sense.

However, as soon as his spiritual sense came into contact with the ball, the talismans adhered to its surface immediately began to emit dazzling white light that formed a covert array that was invisible to the naked eye, keeping his spiritual sense at bay.

Han Li was rather intrigued to see this, and he began to carefully examine these talismans.

While it was true that these talismans were quite remarkable, it was clear that someone had placed them down in a hurry, and given Han Li's mastery in talismans, it wasn't going to be difficult for him to remove them.

After a brief pause, he made a hand seal and cast a series of incantation seals into the talismans while opening his mouth to release a burst of azure flames that enveloped the golden ball.

Moments later, several dull thumps rang out in succession as all of the white talismans disintegrated into specks of white light that were devoured by the azure flames.

In the next instant, circles of spirit patterns appeared on the golden ball's surface, immediately following which beams of yellow light began to radiate from the yellow ball, making it appear as dazzling as the sun.

The restrictions in the secret chamber immediately reacted, and countless azure runes appeared on the walls, forming an azure light barrier that attempted to contain the yellow light, but it was able to quickly pierce through the light barrier.

Han Li was rather taken aback by this, and he made another hand seal to activate all of the restrictions around the cave abode, conjuring up light barriers of different colors to envelop the entire cave abode.

The dazzling yellow light continued to proliferate outward, and it was able to pierce through several more layers of restrictions, but was ultimately intercepted.

A faint crack rang out from the yellow ball, following which a series of bulges appeared on its surface, and it rapidly began to swell in size and transform.

In the span of just a few seconds, the ball transformed into a yellow-robed middle-aged man with an authoritative appearance who appeared to have been in his thirties.

This is... an immortal puppet!

The yellow-robed man had an earthy yellow complexion that was giving off a faint metallic gleam, it was giving off an immortal spiritual aura, much like a humanoid immortal treasure, much like Daoist Xie's past form.

Han Li suppressed the excitement in his heart as his gaze fell upon the yellow robe worn by the puppet.

Some of the designs on the yellow robe were ones that he had seen on many past occasions on other puppets in the Holy Puppet Sect, leading him to wonder if this puppet was also from the same sect.

With that in mind, he immediately thought back to when he first encountered Zhong Luan outside the Holy Puppet Sect's restricted area, and it occurred to him that this was most likely the very thing that Zhong Luan had ventured into the restricted area to obtain.

He had always been quite interested in puppets, and if this really were a True Immortal Stage puppet, then this would be a massive haul in itself.

Thus, Han Li immediately cast an incantation seal into the puppet's body, and two specks of light emerged in the puppet's eyes, while a layer of yellow light surfaced over its skin.

Immediately thereafter, a mountainous aura erupted forth, causing the surrounding space and the entire cave abode to tremble violently.

Chapter 308: Modifications

Han Li was watching all of this unfold with a calm expression, but internally, he was nowhere near as calm as he looked.

However, the disturbance only lasted less than a second before abruptly subsiding, and the light radiating from the puppet's body faded, as did the enormous aura it had displayed.

Han Li exhaled as a stunned look flashed through his eyes.

The enormous aura that had just erupted out of the puppet's body had been extremely formidable, and he was unable to gauge exactly how powerful it was, but he was certain that it was beyond the True Immortal Stage.

With that in mind, Han Li had to suppress his excitement once again as he made another hand seal.

However, this time, no matter what he tried, the puppet displayed no further reaction.

After some contemplation, Han Li closed his eyes and released his spiritual sense to inspect the puppet's internal makeup.

A short while later, he withdrew his spiritual sense out of the puppet's body, then opened his eyes with an uncertain look on his face.

He had never come into contact with an immortal puppet before, but given his expertise in the art of puppetry, he had already managed to track down the core area of the puppet, but to his surprise, the area was empty.

Aside from that, the entire puppet was missing an energy source, so the reaction it had just displayed was most likely only from a tiny amount of residual energy left in its body.

By his estimates, it was most likely going to require an enormous amount of Immortal Origin Stones to operate this puppet.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to Han Li, and he flipped a hand over to produce the golden ball that was Daoist Xie's core.

Han Li made a hand seal and cast an incantation seal into the ball, and it quickly transformed into a palm-sized golden crab amid a flash of golden light. The crab clutched at its own head with its pincers and shook it around a little, then stood up in a rather unsteady fashion.

The crab then cast its gaze toward Han Li as it asked in a slow voice, "What is it, Fellow Daoist Han? Why have you..."

It had been in a state of slumber ever since its return, and even now, it was still rather groggy and lethargic.

However, its voice suddenly trailed off as it turned around to stare intently at the yellow-robed puppet behind it.

"That's an immortal puppet, and a linked puppet, at that! This is truly a rare find!" Daoist Xie murmured to itself with golden light glowing in its eyes.

It flew up from Han Li's hand as it spoke and landed on the puppet, crawling joyfully up and down its body while touching the puppet with its pincers.

All the while, Han Li merely looked on in silence.

Only after a full 15 minutes had passed did Daoist Xie stop what it was doing before turning to Han Li as it asked, "Where did you obtain this immortal puppet from, Fellow Daoist Han? I can tell you that it's a puppet of a very high caliber."

There was a clear hint of excitement in its voice as it spoke.

"That's a long story, but this puppet should have some close ties with a sect known as the Holy Puppet Sect," Han Li replied in an ambiguous manner.

"Holy Puppet Sect... I've never heard of such a sect before," Daoist Xie murmured to itself before turning back to inspect the puppet again.

"By the way, what did you mean by linked puppet just now, Brother Xie?" Han Li asked.

"Linked puppets are a very rare type of puppet. Generally speaking, once a puppet is refined, its power will be set at a certain level, and there's very limited potential for growth. However, linked puppets are different in that their combat prowess depends on the power of the spiritual sense of its user, as well as its degree of affinity to the user. To put it in simpler terms, it functions much like a treasure," Daoist Xie explained.

"I see. It seems like you're very interested in this puppet. Is it something that you can use?" Han Li asked.

"I haven't had a chance to fully examine the puppet yet, but it's an earth-attribute puppet, so generally speaking, only someone who's using an earth-attribute cultivation art will be able to use it. If you can reach the peak level of affinity with it, it should be able to display mid-Golden Immortal Stage power," Daoist Xie replied.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing this. "You possess lightning-attribute powers, so..."

"That's right, I won't be able to use this linked puppet," Daoist Xie confirmed with a nod.

"I see," Han Li replied with a hint of disappointment in his eyes.

While he possessed sufficiently formidable spiritual sense to use the puppet, he wasn't very adept in any earth-attribute cultivation arts, so even if he were to use the puppet, he wouldn't be able to use it to its full power.

Daoist Xie was silent for a moment, then suddenly said, "Having said that, if you give me a suitable environment and sufficient resources, it may not be entirely impossible."

An elated look appeared on Han Li's face as he hurriedly asked, "What do you need, Brother Xie? I'll do my best to provide you with the right conditions."

If Daoist Xie could successfully control this puppet, then he would have a Golden Immortal Stage ally on his side.

"Firstly, I'll need a lightning array. The array isn't very complicated to set up, but it requires something that can continuously provide lightning power as its core, and that is the key that'll decide whether the modification will be successful. On top of that, I also require a large sum of Immortal Origin Stones and lightning-attribute top-grade spirit stones to ensure that the modification process isn't interrupted for even a single moment," Daoist Xie said.

It opened its mouth to spit out a small golden jade slip as it spoke, and the jade slip flew toward Han Li, who caught it before injecting his spiritual sense into it.

The jade slip contained the method required to set up a lightning array, and just as Daoist Xie said, it wasn't very complicated.

Aside from that, in order to maintain the array, close to 1,000 Immortal Origin Stones and a huge sum of lightning-attribute top-grade spirit stones were required. It seemed like a massive cost, but it was no problem with Han Li's current wealth.

"Alright, I'll be able to set up everything for you in seven days at the very most," Han Li said after a brief moment of contemplation.

Daoist Xie wasn't all that surprised to hear this, and it replied, "it looks like you've done quite well for yourself since your return to the Immortal Realm, Follow Daoist Han. In that case, I'll be counting on you."

……

Several days later.

Countless purple veins had been engraved onto the floor of the secret chamber, forminga large circular array. The yellow-robed puppet was laying flat on a certain point in the array, around which were standing eight lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood.

Array patterns had also been engraved onto the lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood, and there were arcs of purple lightning flashing occasionally over their surface.

At the very center of the lightning array was an indentation, within which was embedded a round purple crystal. This was none other than the clam jewel that he had obtained from that giant clam while crossing the Thunderstorm Sea.

At this moment, Han Li was standing at the entrance of his secret chamber with Daoist xie perched on his shoulder.

He made a hand seal with both hands to cast a string of incantation seals into the purple clam bead at the center of the array, and thunderclaps rang out one after another as all of the array patterns on the ground began to glow with dazzling radiance.

Countless arcs of purple lightning emerged from the array before springing up into the air to resemble a nest of wildly dancing lightning snakes.

In the blink of an eye, the entire secret chamber was transformed into a world of purple lightning.

"What do you think of this array, Brother Xie?" Han Li asked.

"You've done very well, Fellow Daoist Han. In particular, that crystal at the center of the array is very remarkable, and it seems to be holding an enormous amount of lightning power," Daoist Xie remarked as it pointed a pincer at the purple clam bead.

Han Li gave Daoist Xie a recount of how he had come into possession of the clam bead, and after hearing the story, Daoist Xie said, "Prior to this, I only had a 30% chance of success, but with this setup, the chance of success has increased to 50%."

After that, he crouched down before springing into the lightning array as a streak of golden light.

Countless arcs of lightning sprang out of all parts of the array before converging toward Daoist Xie, while dazzling golden lightning appeared over its body.

In the blink of an eye, it had been completely enveloped in a ball of golden lightning, following which it descended toward the yellow-robed puppet's chest.

The ball of golden lightning vanished into the puppet's chest in a flash, and the puppet's body shuddered as dazzling yellow light appeared over its skin, while arcs of lightning crackled around its chest.

The purple lightning in the array was drawn to the puppet's chest before fusing as one with it, and the lightning immediately began to spread toward other parts of the puppet's body.

The lightning immediately began to clash against the yellow light on the yellow-robed puppet's body, and explosions rang out occasionally, causing the entire secret chamber to shudder along with the lightning array.

Han Li was standing at the entrance, watching everything unfolding inside the secret chamber with a hint of anticipation in his eyes.

According to Daoist Xie, the fusion process could take several decades or even over a century. The clam bead contained more than enough lightning power to support this process, and Han Li had prepared a sufficient number of Immortal Origin Stones and lightning-attribute top-grade spirit stones as well when setting up the array.

"Hopefully everything goes well," Han Li murmured to himself, then left the secret chamber and closed the door before setting up a restriction.

Before long, he had already sat down with his legs crossed in another secret chamber.

Now that he had set up everything that Daoist Xie needed, it was time for him to consider his own situation.

With all of the Immortal Origin Stones he had accumulated thus far, there should've been enough to support his cultivation for the next few centuries, barring any mishaps.

However, that encounter with Zhong Luan on this trip to the Holy Puppet Sect was one that struck a great deal of wariness into his heart.

Even though he had managed to slay Zhong Luan in battle, it was clear from the black crane's memories that this was far from the end of the matter.

According to what Zhong Luan had said, even if their encounter hadn't taken place in the Holy Puppet Sect, Zhong Luan had been planning to search for him on the Ancient Cloud Continent anyway, so he wasn't necessarily safe just because he was in the Blaze Dragon Dao.

There was no guarantee that the enemy wouldn't pursue him to the Blaze Dragon Dao, and he had to consider what he was going to do if Fang Pan and Zhong Luan's master or some other formidable enemy came after him.

Chapter 309: Progressing to the Late-True Immortal Stage

With that in mind, Han Li swept a hand through the air, and the remaining lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood in his possession appeared on the ground before him, along with some other lightning-attribute spirit materials.

Around a month later.

Han Li was seated in the main hall in the courtyard outside the cave abode, sipping on a cup of spirit tea with a contemplative look in his eyes.

Moments later, Meng Qianqian made her way into the room.

"Elder Li."

"Qianqian, I called you here because I have something important I need you to do for me," Han Li said as he set down his teacup with a serious expression.

Meng Qianqian faltered slightly upon hearing this, then puffed out her chest as she replied, "Please go ahead, Elder Li."

"Don't be so tense, it's not that serious," Han Li said with a smile, then pulled out a storage tool that he handed to Meng Qianqian.

Meng Qianqian accepted the storage tool before injecting her spiritual sense into it, following which she looked up at Han Li with a hint of befuddlement in her eyes.

Han Li said something to her through voice transmission, and a grim look appeared on her face.

"Is that too difficult a task?" Han Li asked.

"Rest assured, Elder Li, I'll get it done even if it costs me my life!" Meng Qianqian assured with a serious expression.

"Good, but do be careful, and don't let anyone else know about this," Han Li instructed.

"Yes, Elder Li," Meng Qianqian replied with a respectful curtsey, then departed from the room, flying away as a streak of crimson light.

Han Li stood at the entrance of his cave abode, watching as the streak of crimson light vanished into the distance before also flying away himself as a streak of azure light.

Only after two months did he return to the Crimson Dawn Peak, and during this time, he had sold most of the materials, spirit medicines, and treasures that he had obtained from the Holy Puppet Sect in batches for Immortal Origin Stones.

He had also purchased a large supply of ingredients required for the pills that he was going to refine, and having completed all of these preparations, he returned to his cave abode, then activated all of the restrictions before making his way into the secret chamber.

On the way there, a thought suddenly occurred to him, and he made his way to his medicine garden instead, specifically to the corner where the primary bean had been planted.

To his surprise, he discovered that the seedling that had sprouted out of the primary bean had become several inches taller than before.

It had taken the primary a very long time to germinate, but ever since then, its rate of growth had become a lot faster.

As the seedling developed, the golden patterns on it had become a lot darker, but as for whether this supposed mutation was positive or negative, that was still yet to be seen.

In any case, after witnessing the Dao Warriors in action back at the Holy Puppet Sect, he was very much looking forward to acquiring his own Dao Warriors.

With that in mind, Han Li pulled out his Heaven Controlling Vial before handing it to the nearby giant ape puppet, then made his way back to his secret chamber.

Up to this point, all of the errands had been taken care of, and he exhaled as he flipped a hand over to produce a silver pill cauldron, which he set down at the center of the secret chamber.

After that, he summoned the Essence Fire Raven with a sweep of his sleeve, which descended near the cauldron as a fiery silver figure.

After devouring and absorbing the black crane's nascent soul, the Essence Fire Raven's aura had clearly become more powerful than before, and its facial features had also become a bit more exuberant and expressive.

It seemed to have been aware of why it had been summoned, and after quickly flying in a circle around the cauldron, its round cheeks bulged, following which it blasted a large plume of silver flames out of its mouth to envelop the underside of the cauldron.

Meanwhile, Han Li had already prepared all of the pill refinement ingredients that he had purchased into batches, and he sat down with his legs crossed.

……

Several years later.

The silver flames beneath the cauldron subsided, and the fiery silver figure jumped onto Han Li's shoulder, where it sat down in an obedient manner.

There was a rather weary look on Han Li's face as he cast an incantation seal through the air, and a faint pop rang out as the lid of the silver cauldron flew up, following which a rich medicinal aroma instantly filled the entire secret chamber.

After taking a whiff of the aroma, a pleased look appeared on Han Li's face, and he made a grabbing motion to draw around a dozen longan-sized white pills out of the cauldron. All of the pills were emanating faint wisps of white mist, giving them quite a profound and remarkable appearance.

The white pills fell into a white jade vial that had been prepared earlier, and at this point, there were already over 100 of these vials placed beside Han Li.

"That should be about enough," Han Li murmured to himself, then swept a sleeve through the air to stow the silver cauldron and the Essence Fire Raven away before closing his eyes to meditate.

He was going to prime himself into the best possible condition before going into seclusion.

Over 200 years flew by in the blink of an eye, and the Crimson Dawn Peak had been closed to the outside this entire time.

During this time, the Blaze Dragon Dao welcomed its largest bout of snowfall in the past 500 years, lasting several months.

Not only were all of the northern branches of the entire Bell Toll Mountain Range covered in a blanket of snow, the same applied to the majority of the mountain range's southern branches as well, and that included the Crimson Dawn Peak.

On this day, the snowfall finally subsided to reveal clear, blue skies, and Han Li's servants began to clear away the snow around the cave abode, led by Meng Xiong.

There were very few people on the Crimson Dawn Peak to begin with, and Meng Yungui and the others were yet to return from their outings. In particular, in the absence of Meng Qianqian, it was very quiet, and even the calls of the birds were particularly clear and audible.

After all of the snow in front of the entrance of the cave abode had been cleared away, everyone went to the spirit medicine fields, which were protected by restrictions and arrays, but the snow there still had to be cleared away. Otherwise, the melting snow would result in excessive water that would drown the plants.

All of a sudden, the entire Crimson Dawn Peak abruptly shuddered, and an enormous pillar of golden light erupted straight into the heavens from the cave abode. All of the world's origin qi in a radius of thousands of kilometers rippled violently, forming an enormous cloud that revolveD around the Crimson Dawn Peak.

Spiritual light of all types of different colors shone down upon the Crimson Dawn Peak, and the phenomenon only subsided after a long time had passed.

Everyone had stopped what they were doing to observe the phenomenon, and Meng Xiong hurriedly urged, "Alright, let's all get back to work. The sooner we get this done, the sooner we can go back to cultivate. Elder Li has provided us with an exceptional cultivation environment, so let's not squander it."

Everyone immediately returned to work upon hearing this.

They were already accustomed to all of the phenomena taking place on the mountain, and they knew that all of them resulted from Han Li's cultivation, but they still couldn't help but want to stop and watch whenever these phenomena took place.

After all, these phenomena were being triggered by the cultivation of a True Immortal!

Inside the secret chamber of his cave abode, Han Li's entire body was basked in golden light, and there were 24 specks of golden light on his chest and abdomen that were glowing as radiantly as stars in the night sky.

An enormous aura was emanating from his body, and it was as if he had been reborn anew.

He had progressed to the late-True Immortal Stage.

During the past two centuries, he had constantly been consuming earthly pills to enhance his own cultivation, and he had finally managed to open those four remaining immortal acupoints.

This rate of cultivation was naturally far faster than that of the average cultivator, but it was still significantly slower than before.

It had only taken him around a century to open up the previous three immortal acupoints, yet it had taken far longer than that just to open up this final one.

As the golden light gradually fused into Han Li's body, the phenomenon taking place within the secret chamber also subsided.

Han Li exhaled as he turned and cast his gaze toward the Mantra Treasured Axis hovering in mid-air behind him.

The Eye of Truth was shut, and at this point, all of the Time Dao Runes on the axis had already fully recovered.

However, there was a hint of disappointment in Han Li's eyes.

Even after his progression to the late-True Immortal Stage, the number of Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis still remained stagnant at 108.

This was clearly not just a matter of bad luck. According to the Mantra Axis Scripture, opening up the final four immortal acupoints should've earned him two more Time Dao Runes.

It was most likely the case that he had manifested too many Time Dao Runes by using the Eye of Truth to absorb the crystals created by the Heaven Controlling Vial, and the Mantra Treasured Axis had already reached its tolerance threshold.

Having said that, Han Li was already prepared for this outcome, so he wasn't overly disappointed.

A faint smile appeared on his face as he sensed the vast immortal spiritual power in his body, and instead of immediately rising to his feet, he continued to remain seated on the ground.

This breakthrough was naturally fantastic news, but there were more important things that he had to attend to right now.

He flipped a hand over to produce the eye of the Primordial Fei Beast, and at the same time, the sound of heavy footsteps rang out from outside as the giant ape puppet strode into the room.

It set down the Heaven Controlling Vial beside him, and there was already a drop of green spirit liquid inside it.

Han Li took a deep breath as he picked up the Heaven Controlling Vial, then consumed the drop of spirit liquid inside without any hesitation.

Once again, he was attempting to glean the laws of time.

His immortal spiritual power began to circulate in his body, while the Mantra Treasured Axis behind him lit up with dazzling golden radiance, and the 108 Time Dao Runes on its surface were also flashing incessantly.

A vast expanse of golden ripples appeared around him to envelop the entire secret chamber, and a burst of indescribably formidable energy fluctuations erupted in all directions.

To Han Li, it felt as if even the flow of air in the surrounding area had slowed down, and he was able to hear everything with exceptional clarity.

It seemed that everything around him had fallen into some type of profound tempo, and as time slowly passed, the golden light radiating from Han Li's body continued to flash, causing the level of brightness in the secret chamber to fluctuate incessantly.

At this point, his body was already drenched in blood, but he paid no heed to that at all, as if it weren't even happening to him.

Chapter 310: Two Flowers

All of a sudden, his eyelids fluttered slightly, and his eyes sprang open, following which two beams of golden light erupted out from within.

He began to make a rapid string of hand seals, bringing his palms together and linking them together before thrusting his joint index and middle fingers upward like a sword.

All 108 of the Time Dao Runes on the Mantra Treasured Axis behind him instantly lit up at once.

At the same time, golden light emerged between the palms of his hands before traveling to his fingertips, and a translucent golden thread that was as thin as a strand of human hair began to slowly extend out from his fingertips.

However, it had only protruded around an inch out from his fingertips before it exploded into specks of golden light with a dull thump.

The golden light in Han Li's eyes also slowly faded, and he looked down at his own bloodstained robes with a wry smile on his face.

He had made some progress compared with last time he had attempted this, but once again, he had ultimately fallen just short of manifesting a time law thread.

It looks like it'll be extremely difficult to glean the laws of time even by directly consuming the spirit liquid. Perhaps only by consuming a dao pill will I have a chance of succeeding in this endeavor.

It had now become apparent to him why dao pills were so sought after in the Immortal Realm.

The difference here was like that between directly consuming a spirit medicine and a pill refined with that spirit medicine as the main ingredient.

A pill would give the consumer the best chance of gleaning the law powers contained within the spirit medicine, and that was naturally far more effective than directly consuming the ingredient itself.

Thankfully, he had accumulated a substantial amount of wealth and was able to easily obtain spirit ingredients that contained the power of time laws. Otherwise, this wouldn't have been a feasible path for him to pursue.

After heaving a faint sigh, he took a pill, and a layer of golden light appeared over his entire body once again.

Around half a month later.

Han Li departed from his secret chamber, then made his way to the spirit medicine garden in his cave abode.

The medicine garden was filled with abundant spiritual qi and was thriving with vitality.

Inside the field, the giant ape puppet was holding an azure wooden bucket in one hand, out of which it was scooping pails of shimmering azure spirit liquid onto the garden.

This spirit liquid had been mixed using the recipe stipulated in the book on planting Dao Warriors given to Han Li by Daoist Hu Yan, but he had been using it to water his other spirit medicines rather than on the primary bean.

Han Li swept his gaze across the various spirit medicines in the garden, and his eyes lit up as his gaze fell upon one corner of the garden.

The seedling that had sprouted out of the primary bean was gone, and in its place was a massive golden plant that was around 10 feet tall.

Its trunk was an earthy yellow color, while its leaves had a golden hue.

The leaves were riddled with countless golden veins that were stacked on top of one another in layers, and these golden veins stretched all the way from the leaves to the branches and the main trunk of the plant.

Hanging below the layers of lush golden leaves were a series of azure bean pods, each of which was around a finger in length, and the bulges visible in the pods clearly indicated that they contained the beans that Han Li was aiming to grow.

Han Li was very elated to see this, and he hurried over to the tree before walking a lap around it like a proud farmer, carefully counting the number of bean pods on the tree as he did so.

In total, he counted 75 pods, and under the assumption that each pod contained seven beans, that would've amounted to a total of over 500 beans, which, barring any mishaps, would've developed into over 500 formidable Dao Warriors.

However, these beans clearly hadn't reached full maturity yet.

According to Daoist Hu Yan's book, once the Dao Warriors reached full maturity, the trunk, branches, and leaves of the tree would gradually begin to wilt, supplying all of their nutrition to the beans.

After that, the bean pods would break open on their own to release the beans inside.

Due to the fact that the beans hadn't yet matured, Han Li couldn't sense any special aura from them, so he didn't know whether the mutation was positive or negative.

However, Han Li wasn't overly concerned. There was a very good chance that the mutation had arisen as the primary bean had been watered using spirit liquid from the Heaven Controlling Vial, and anything that concerned the Heaven Controlling Vial generally wasn't a bad thing.

Only after inspecting the tree for a while longer did Han Li turn to depart, but right as he did so, he spotted out of the corner of his eye that there were two small yellow flowers on top of the tree.

He stopped to look at the flowers for a moment, and a perplexed look appeared on his face. He flipped a hand over to summon the book given to him by Daoist Hu Yan, then flipped it open to a certain page.

A short while later, he stowed the book away again, but the befuddlement on his face remained.

The book says that the flowering period of primary bean flowers is quite long, so they'll generally only bloom after the beans have reached maturity, and there's only supposed to be one of them, so why are there two here? Could this also be a result of the mutation?

If that were the case, then that would naturally be a good thing as the rate at which he could develop Dao Warriors would be significantly increased, but as a safety precaution, he decided that it was best to consult Daoist Hu Yan about this situation.

With that in mind, he turned and made his way elsewhere in the medicine garden.

This area of the medicine garden was filled with various different types of spirit medicines, and there weren't many of them, but they were all giving off their own unique auras.

These spirit medicines were all ingredients stipulated in the dao pill recipe that Han Li had obtained, and due to the fact that he had obtained them at different ages, the degree of growth that they were displaying were all different.

The oldest of these spirit medicines were several dozen blue plants that looked as if they had been carved out of ice. They resembled boneset herbs with glowing and translucent leaves, and he had acquired them from the floating mountain secret area.

At the time, he didn't know what they were, and only later did he discover that they were none other than the Hidden Mist Herb stated in the dao pill recipe.

Due to the fact that these spirit plans had been growing deep within the floating mountain secret area, they had been left completely untouched, and several of them had already exceeded 100,000 years of age, making them fit to serve as dao pill ingredients.

Not far away from the Hidden Mist Herbs, in a small area enshrouded within a small array, were around a dozen seedlings that looked as if they had only just sprouted.

These plants were known as Sandthrough Sunflowers, and they had been brought back by Meng Yungui over 100 years ago.

This spirit medicine appeared to have been growing very slowly, but its root systems underground were thriving, and if they weren't enshrouded within this array, they would've most likely stretched across the entire garden, making it impossible for the other spirit medicines to survive.

Aside from the main ingredients, the supplementary ingredients on the dao pill recipe were also quite difficult to gather. Meng Yungui had been very fortunate to have come across these spirit plants, and on the way back, he had almost been killed by someone aiming to take the spirit plants from him. Thankfully, he was able to survive thanks to the protective treasures bestowed upon him by Han Li.

After receiving a reward from Han Li for his efforts, Meng Yungui cultivated on the Crimson Dawn Peak for over 10 years before resuming his spirit medicine search.

In addition to Meng Yungui, both Meng Qianqian and Sun Buzheng had also returned to the Crimson Dawn Peak once each during the past two centuries, but Han Li had been in seclusion on both of those occasions, so he wasn't able to see them.

Meng Qianqian stayed on the Crimson Dawn Peak a little longer than Sun Buzheng as she wanted to see if Han Li would come out of seclusion, and also because Featheryearn didn't want to part with the Two-headed Griffin.

Neither Sun Buzheng nor Meng Qianqian had been as fortunate as Meng Yungui, and they were only able to find some seedlings or seeds of spirit medicines stipulated in Han Li's earthly pill recipes, but Han Li wasn't disheartened by this.

Up to this point, even he had only managed to secure several of the spirit medicines listed on the dao pill recipe, including that Thistle Spirit Flower, and no one had responded to the spirit medicine procurement missions that he had released in the Transient Guild.

After staying in the spirit medicine garden a while longer, Han Li made his way to another secret chamber.

Standing in front of the stone door, Han Li swept a hand through the air, and a series of runes instantly appeared on the door, following which it slid aside to reveal an opening that was as tall as a grown man.

The secret chamber was filled with purplish-golden light, and bursts of crackling were ringing out incessantly from within.

The lightning array inside was still operating, but the eight lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood situated around the array were looking a little dim, clearly having already been exhausted of much of their lightning power.

At this moment, the yellow-robed immortal puppet was seated with its legs crossed at the center of the array, and arcs of purple lightning were constantly flashing all over its body, particularly its chest.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he noticed that the indentation at the center of the lightning array was empty, and the purple crystalline ball that was originally embedded in there was nowhere to be seen.

"Brother Xie," Han Li called out to Daoist Xie through spiritual sense voice transmission, but the yellow-robed puppet displayed no reaction.

After a moment of contemplation, Han Li decided to remain patient and wait.

A long while later, the lightning surging over the yellow-robed puppet's chest began to converge toward the center before quickly disappearing entirely.

At the same time, all of the purple lightning across the entire array also vanished, and the spirit patterns on the lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood gradually faded, while the entire array ceased operating.

A burst of golden light appeared in the puppet's chest, and a palm-sized golden crab slowly emerged from within, then crouched down before springing toward Han Li, who spread a hand open to catch the crab.

"How did it go?" Han Li asked.

Compared with before, Daoist Xie's aura had become far more stable, and there were numerous extremely thin purple veins on its eight legs that could only have been noticed upon close inspection.

Chapter 311: Implanting a Bean Into a Puppet

"The construction of this immortal puppet is more complex than I anticipated. I thought that I would be able to forcibly alter its internal makeup with the assistance of the lightning array, but it didn't quite work out that way," Daoist Xie sighed.

"Don't worry about it, it was just an idea, and there's no need to try and force the issue. If the opportunity arises, I'll be sure to find you a suitable puppet in the future," Han Li replied with a shake of his head.

"I suppose we have no choice but to accept this outcome. Having said that, this was not an entirely fruitless endeavor. Even though I wasn't able to modify the puppet, I've examined every single part of it in meticulous detail during the past 200 years.

“If you so wish, you can spend 1,000 years or so cultivating a suitable earth-attribute cultivation art, and I'm confident that I can make it so that you can use 60% of the puppet's power. It won't be its full mid-Golden Immortal Stage power, but it'll definitely be more formidable than the average early-Golden Immortal cultivator," Daoist Xie said.

"You were a complete immortal puppet in the past, so I naturally trust your expertise in the art of puppetry, but let's discuss this matter another time," Han Li replied in an ambiguous manner.

While it was true that being able to control an early-Golden Immortal Stage puppet would've been a great asset, he didn't have time to consider this matter for the time being.

Even though he was in the Blaze Dragon Dao, his safety wasn't guaranteed, so he couldn't just go into seclusion for thousands of years at a time like other immortals. On top of that, the Mantra Axis Scripture and the Great Universe Origin Arts were more suitable cultivation arts for him to pursue, so he naturally had to prioritize them.

"Also, during this process, I discovered a hint of origin lightning power in the clam bead, so I attempted to refine it, and it replenished quite a bit of the energy in my core," Daoist Xie continued.

"That's fine, that thing wasn't very useful to me anyway. In that case, there's no longer any need for this array to continue to function, right?" Han Li asked as he cast his gaze toward the lightning array on the ground.

Daoist Xie shook his head in response, and Han Li swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of azure light that disassembled the entire array.

Meanwhile, Daoist Xie raised its pair of pincers before crossing them in front of itself, and a bolt of purple lightning instantly shot forth to strike the yellow-robed puppet.

A crisp crack rang out from the puppet, and it reverted back into a yellow ball amid a flash of dazzling yellow light. Immediately thereafter, Daoist Xie also reverted back into a golden ball, and both balls were promptly stowed away by Han Li.

……

Around two hours later.

A streak of azure light descended onto a white stone plaza on a mountain near the High Profound Palace, then faded to reveal none other than Han Li.

He made his way to the end of the plaza, and a large expanse of courtyards appeared before him. On the plaque that hung above the large red gate at the center were inscribed the words "Hundred Wine Cottage" in free-flowing characters, and he couldn't help but be amused whenever he saw the wobbly characters on the plaque.

No matter how he looked at them, they always resembled a bunch of drunkards leaning on one another for support.

Before he reached the entrance of the cottage, the gate was opened from the inside, and a pair of azure-robed servants emerged, carrying a large black urn between them.

The two of them were familiar with Han Li, and they immediately set down the large urn before extending a collective respectful salute to him.

Han Li could smell a faint sour odor coming from the black urn, and he asked, "What is it that you're carrying?"

"These are some distillers grains that have gone bad, and Elder Hu Yan instructed us to tip them into a creek in the mountains," one of the azure-robed servants replied.

Han Li nodded in response, then stepped around the pair of servants and made his way into the cottage.

He had only just passed through the corridor in the front yard and made his way into the main hall when he spotted Elder Hu Yan emerging from the inner courtyard.

To his surprise, Elder Hu Yan's hair was impeccably groomed, and his clothes were also in pristine condition. Even his stride lengths had increased slightly compared with before, and he couldn't help but wonder what could've happened in the past 200 years that had brought on these changes.

"You must have the nose of a dog! I only just finished brewing several jars of Hundred Flower Wine, and you've already sniffed it out! You came at just the right time," Daoist Hu Yan declared with a wide smile.

"Are you celebrating something, Senior?" Han Li asked.

Daoist Hu Yan faltered slightly upon hearing this, then scoffed, "Why do you think that? Are you thinking to yourself that there's no way someone as stingy as me would offer you wine unless there's something I'm celebrating?"

Han Li merely smiled and offered no response.

Daoist Hu Yan also smiled as he gestured for Han Li to come in. "Take a seat."

After both of them had sat down, Daoist Hu Yan swept a hand through the air, and a white jade flagon and a pair of peony cups appeared on the table.

He picked up the flagon and tipped it slightly to the side, and a stream of light azure wine instantly came flowing out of the spout and into the cup, while an intoxicating floral aroma began to waft through the air.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon catching a whiff of this aroma, and Daoist Hu Yan was very pleased to see this reaction.

"Give it a taste."

Han Li did as he was told, picking up his cup before taking a small sip, and his mouth was instantly filled with a sweet and aromatic flavor that wasn't harsh on the mouth in the slightest.

"This is exceptional wine!" Han Li praised after swallowing the wine in his mouth, and a proud smile appeared on Daoist Hu Yan's face upon hearing this.

"This is indeed a fine wine, but its flavor is lacking compared with the Red Mulberry Wine and the Fire Drop Wine, so it's rather unlike the wines that you normally enjoy," Han Li remarked.

"This wine was brewed for someone else, not for me to drink," Daoist Hu Yan explained with a smile.

"Oh? Is it for Dao Lord Yun?" Han Li asked in a seemingly casual voice.

Daoist Hu Yan's smile stiffened slightly upon hearing this, and he put on an angry façade as he stowed the flagon away. "Just keep your mouth shut and drink your wine!"

Han Li smiled and offered no response.

All of a sudden, Daoist Hu Yan's expression changed ever so slightly, and he remarked, "I didn't notice it earlier, but your aura has become a lot more powerful than before. It seems like you've been working hard!"

"I just so happened to encounter some strokes of fortune, and I went into seclusion for a while as well. I came to visit you as soon as I came out of seclusion," Han Li replied with a smile.

"It must've been quite a significant stroke of fortune for you to have made such significant progress in just a few centuries! Also, why have you come to visit me? You're not the type to do things that won't work to your benefit, so you must have something to ask of me, right?" Daoist Hu Yan asked.

"You know me very well, Senior. I came to you because for some reason, the primary bean that I planted produced two primary bean flowers, which is at odds with what's stated in the book that you gave me, so I decided to come and consult you about it," Han Li replied with a serious expression.

"Two primary bean flowers?" Daoist Hu Yan exclaimed with an incredulous expression.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly at the sight of his reaction, and he hurriedly asked, "Is there something wrong?"

"Wrong? Things couldn't be less wrong! Generally speaking, a Dao Warrior Tree will only have a 50% chance of sprouting a primary bean flower, but not only has yours sprouted a primary bean flower, it's sprouted two! It's not that this has never happened before, but it's extremely unlikely. How are you so lucky? I'm beginning to get a little envious of you," Daoist Hu Yan said as he picked up the red wine gourd strapped to his waist before taking a swig of its contents.

Han Li was quite relieved to hear this. He had already guessed that this was most likely a positive development, and he was completely reassured after receiving confirmation from Daoist Hu Yan.

He knew that this was most likely a result of the spirit liquid that had been used to water the primary bean rather than just a matter of dumb luck, but he naturally wasn't going to reveal that to Daoist Hu Yan.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to him, and he asked, "If a Dao Warrior Tree doesn't sprout a primary bean flower, doesn't that mean it won't be able to produce another Dao Warrior Tree?"

"That's right. Do you think primary beans are that easy to obtain? In the field of Dao Warrior planting, the continuation of primary beans has always been a major problem. Forget it, you wouldn't understand even if I explained this to you," Daoist Hu Yan harrumphed.

"In that case, it looks like I'm in luck," Han Li chuckled.

Daoist Hu Yan rolled his eyes at Han Li before taking another swig of wine.

Han Li paid no heed to Daoist Hu Yan as he mused in an excited voice, "If I plant both primary beans, after a couple of centuries, I'll be able to develop twice the number of Dao Warriors!"

"If I were you, I definitely wouldn't waste those primary beans by simply planting them," Daoist Hu Yan interjected.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then asked, "Why would that be a waste, Senior?"

"If you can maintain this streak of luck, then just a single primary bean would be enough for you to nurture more Dao Warriors. As for the other one, you may as well keep it, and if you ever come across a high-grade puppet, you can implant it into that puppet," Daoist Hu Yan explained in a meaningful voice.

"Primary beans can be implanted into puppets?" Han Li asked with a surprised expression.

"Some Dao Warriors are puppets to begin with. As long as the attributes are matching, a primary bean can be integrated into a puppet, and after that, the puppet will gain many characteristics of Dao Warriors, such as the ability to regenerate severed limbs.

“As long as the core remains intact, the puppet will be virtually indestructible, and due to the fact that these puppets will have runes inscribed upon them from the primary bean integration process, even if it they fall into the hands of others, no one else will be able to use them," Daoist Hu Yan explained.

Han Li immediately thought of the yellow-robed immortal puppet upon hearing this, and he said, "That sounds incredible! Would you be able to impart the integration method upon me, Senior?"

"Why? Could it be that you already have an immortal puppet in your possession?" Daoist Hu Yan asked as he raised an eyebrow.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged as he replied, "Of course not, but it can't hurt to be prepared. What if I am fortunate enough to come into possession of an immortal puppet in the future?"

"You sure do like to cover all of your bases. The integration method isn't exactly a secret, so I can bestow it upon you, but... I can't just let you have it for free," Daoist Hu Yan said as a sly gleam flashed through his eyes.

Chapter 312: Lightning Bean

"Of course. I just so happened to have obtained a certain item recently, let me know if it catches your interest, Senior."

Han Li flipped a hand over as he spoke to produce a thin golden page.

"A pill recipe, eh? Don't try to placate me with just any pill recipe. At the very least, it has to be an earthly pill recipe," Daoist Hu Yan chuckled.

He made a beckoning motion with one hand as he spoke, and the golden page rose up from Han Li's hand before landing in his grasp.

"Growth Bearing Pill? This is indeed an earthly pill, and one that's fit for consumption for mid-True Immortal cultivators, at that. I suppose this will suffice," Daoist Hu Yan mused, then stowed the golden page away before flipping his hand over to produce a white stone shard that he handed to Han Li.

Han Li accepted the stone shard before pressing it against his own forehead to inspect its contents.

"The array diagram and the materials required to set it up have already been clearly annotated, and it shouldn't be too difficult to set up, but you must make sure to prepare a sufficient number of spirit stones to support its operation. Otherwise, if it runs out of spirit power for even a single moment, then the entire process will fail. The puppet won't be harmed as a result, but the primary bean will be destroyed," Daoist Hu Yan cautioned.

"Thank you, Senior," Han Li replied with a nod as he removed the stone shard from his forehead.

"Alright, if that's all, then you can go. I still have other guests to attend to later," Daoist Hu Yan said in a direct and straightforward manner.

"In that case, I won't take up any more of your time, Senior."

Han Li rose to his feet and extended a parting salute, then flew out of the Hundred Wine Cottage as a streak of light.

He had only just flown to the edge of the mountain when he spotted another streak of light descending toward the Hundred Wine Cottage, and it was none other than Bai Suyuan's mistress, Yun Ni.

Back on the plaza in the Holy Puppet Sect, Bai Suyuan had referred to Qilin 3 as mistress, and Han Li was already aware of Bai Suyuan's identity, so he was naturally tipped off to the fact that Qilin 3 and Yun Ni were one and the same.

Even though he hadn't been present during the final stage of the battle at the Holy Puppet Sect, he had learned through some other avenues that the person who had saved the Holy Puppet Sect in the end was none other than Daoist Hu Yan, and that he was also one of the Blaze Dragon Dao's 13 dao lords.

Given what he already knew about Bai Fengyi, he had guessed that there were some ties between Daoist Hu Yan and Yun Ni, but seeing as Daoist Hu Yan hadn't mentioned this topic, he naturally pretended to have been oblivious.

Of course, he had gone out of his way to unearth all of this information not just to satisfy his own curiosity. Instead, he was trying to find out whether the Holy Puppet Sect had launched a search for its lost immortal puppet. However, it seemed that not long after the attack, the Holy Puppet Sect moved away from those islands and seemingly disappeared.

With these thoughts flashing through his mind, Han Li returned to the Crimson Dawn Peak.

After entering the secret chamber of his cave abode, he flipped a hand over to produce the stone shard given to him by Daoist Hu Yan, and an excited look appeared on his face as he closed his eyes and injected his spiritual sense into the stone shard.

The stone shard contained an array that was very similar to the one that Daoist Xie had requested, indicating that there were many fundamental similarities between them, but there were some differences in the finer details and in the materials required to set up the array.

After inspecting the array diagram for a moment, Han Li directed his attention to the materials and method required to set up the array. In doing so, he discovered five different sets of materials depending on the attribute of the primary bean.

Among them, he placed his focus on the earth-attribute materials. After all, he immortal puppet was an earth-attribute one, and his primary bean came from the Golden Dao Warrior, so there was a very good chance that it was also an earth-attribute one.

Some time later, Han Li opened his eyes as he murmured to himself, "Infinity Sand..."

He then flipped a hand over to produce a pair of azure masks, one cow and one tiger.

Han Li's gaze roamed back and forth over the two masks for a moment before he ultimately decided to put on the tiger mask.

At this point, Wyrm 15 had already become a little too renowned for comfort, so it was best for him to switch identities.

This was the first time that he was using the mask since obtaining it, and it gave him the identity of Raccoon 11.

After that, he released an Infinity Sand procurement mission, and after some contemplation, he decided to release the same procurement missions for the dao pill ingredients that he had already released using the cow mask.

Only after doing all of that did he stow the mask away before sitting down with his legs crossed to cultivate.

……

Over 10 years passed by in a flash.

On this day, Han Li was cultivating in his secret chamber when he suddenly heard a string of loud booms ringing out from within his cave abode.

His eyes immediately sprang open as he flew out of his secret chamber and traveled straight to his spirit medicine garden.

As soon as he entered the garden, the loud booms became even clearer.

A hint of elation appeared on Han Li's face as he quickly approached the Dao Warrior Tree to find that it had already completely wilted, and the bean pods hanging from it had also turned yellow and were exploding one after another, sending dark yellow beans raining down onto the ground.

Han Li caught one of the beans that had just erupted out of its pod, and he inspected it closely to find that its surface was riddled with golden lightning veins that would've been impossible to see had he not been looking at it so closely.

He then injected a burst of immortal spiritual power into the bean through his fingers, and the golden lightning veins on the bean instantly lit up before releasing a vast expanse of golden lightning.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon seeing this. As it turned out, the mutation that these Dao Warriors had undergone had granted them the lightning attribute.

Right at this moment, an explosion that was clearly louder than all of the previous ones rang out, and Han Li looked up to discover that the two large bean pods at the top of the Dao Warrior Tree had erupted open at once, sending a pair of pea-sized primary beans flying through the air.

He hurriedly reached out to catch the pair of primary beans before inspecting them closely as well.

Aside from their size, these primary beans were almost identical to the other beans, except the lightning veins on their surface were darker, and the lightning power that was imbued within them was slightly more pure.

At this point, all of the beans had already been ejected out of their pods, and the Dao Warrior Tree completely wilted away, rapidly turning from yellow to gray before disintegrating into dust, all in the span of just a few seconds.

Han Li flipped a hand over to produce a yellow gourd, then patted the underside of the gourd, and a burst of yellow light immediately appeared at its opening, releasing a burst of tremendous suction force that sucked in all of the beans that had spilled onto the ground.

Of course, not just any object could be used to store Dao Warriors, and this gourd was something that Han Li had refined according to the instructions enclosed in Daoist Hu Yan's book.

This gourd functioned very similarly to a storage pouch, but it was actually closer in nature to a spirit beast pouch, and while stored inside it, the Dao Warriors could continue to absorb the world's origin qi.

In fact, if he wanted to keep nurturing the Dao Warriors to elevate them to a higher caliber, he could even pour some premade spirit liquid into the gourd, and that was exactly what Daoist Hu Yan was doing with his Dao Warriors.

After collecting all of the beans, Han Li returned to his secret chamber in an excited manner.

Two days later.

A ring-shaped array that was around 10 feet in radius had been engraved onto the ground in Han Li's secret chamber.

There were numerous indentations distributed throughout the array, within which were placed various types of spirit materials and several Immortal Origin Stones.

At the center of the array was a golden platform of a moderate size that resembled a city, with four walls on top to create a cavity, where the hundreds of Dao Warrior beans were being stored.

This array was known as the Lightning Origin Locking Array, and it was a lightning-attribute array recorded in Daoist Hu Yan's book that could be used to refine Dao Warrior beans.

The golden platform at the center of the array was a small altar that Han Li had constructed using Lightning Restraining Wood, and it was the core of the entire array.

The refinement array for Dao Warrior beans had to be chosen based on the attribute displayed by the beans after they reached maturity, and Han Li had thought that these beans would most likely have taken after the golden giant and developed the earth attribute, but due to the mutation, these beans did still contain earth-attribute spiritual power, but it was far outmatched by the lightning-attribute spiritual power within them.

Hence, when choosing a refinement array, Han Li had decided on the Lightning Origin Locking Array.

After everything was set up in the secret chamber, he sat down with his legs crossed in front of the array, then flipped a hand over to produce a pill, which he promptly consumed.

Daoist Hu Yan had warned him that setting up this array was going to be very taxing on his immortal spiritual power, so he had to prime himself into the best possible condition before commencing the refinement process.

With that in mind, he sat down to meditate for a long time before opening his eyes and activating the array.

He made a hand seal with both hands, then pointed a finger at the golden platform at the center of the array, and an arc of golden lightning immediately shot out of his fingertip before springing into the platform like a spirit snake.

The sound of flowing electricity rang out as the entire golden platform instantly began to glow brightly, and countless arcs of lightning sprang forth in all directions, forming a spherical golden light barrier that encompassed the entire array.

At the same time, all of the top-grade spirit stones that had been embedded into the indentations on the ground also began to glow brightly before releasing bursts of pure spiritual power into the array patterns on the ground.

At the same time, the golden platform began to tremble violently, and the beans inside also began to bounce up and down as a result.

Han Li activated his Brightsight Spirit Eyes upon seeing this, then thrust both palms upward at once, and all of the beans were immediately raised upward by an invisible hand, emerging from the platform to hover in the air within the spherical light barrier.

The two primary beans were hanging at the center like a pair of full moons, while the other beans were distributed around them like glowing stars.

Chapter 313: Exploring an Alternative Path

All of a sudden, Han Li switched to a different hand seal, and the golden patterns on the golden platform instantly lit up as a pillar of golden lightning erupted directly upward, striking the light barrier up above before splitting up into countless arcs of golden lightning.

The two primary beans were situated at the very center of the pillar of lightning, while hundreds of arcs of lightning erupted in all directions to form a golden net that encompassed all of the surrounding beans.

Within the net of lightning, all of the beans were interconnected by strands of lightning that resembled thin branches, while the pillar of golden lightning beneath the primary beans resembled the main trunk, giving the entire setup the appearance of a small golden lightning tree.

The wisps of spiritual power released by the spirit stones on the ground flowed through the lightning tree's trunk and branches and into the beans, causing all of the lightning veins on their surfaces to glow with dazzling radiance.

Han Li felt as if he were looking at a golden tree that was laden with fruit, and a pleased look appeared on his face.

He took a deep breath before switching to yet another hand seal, and the entire array instantly shuddered as specks of black light began to appear on many of the nodes in the array, then connected together to form an extremely peculiar bestial design.

The beast resembled a cow, but it had the horns of a dragon. It appeared to have been quite massive in stature, and its round belly was riddled with antiquated runes that were giving off formidable lightning power fluctuations.

What was even more peculiar was that the beast only had a single leg, making it resemble a giant black hammer, and trailing behind it was a whip-like tail.

This was a Lightning Kui that was an extremely renowned spirit beast in the Immortal Realm, and it was born with the ability to control Nine Heavens True Lightning. It would often pound its belly with its own tail to produce rumbling thunderclaps that warded off all evil and malicious entities.

As soon as the bestial design took shape, Han Li took a deep breath, and he knew that the most important moment in the Dao Warrior refinement process was about to arrive.

He joined his palms in a new hand seal, then began to chant an incantation, and as he did so, the Lightning Kui diagram on the ground began to glow with black light before rising up into the air, passing through all of the beans to reach the light barrier up above.

The blue light in Han Li's eyes grew even brighter, and translucent threads formed by his spiritual sense began to fly out of his glabella before hurtling into the golden lightning tree, and at the same time, he was also sweeping his hand incessantly through the air.

As he did this, all of the beans hanging from the golden lightning tree began to tremble slightly, and specks of black light began to appear around the lightning veins on the beans, indicating that the rune inscription process had officially begun.

Outside the array, Han Li's hands were moving in a rapid blur, yet the black veins that were appearing on the beans inside the array were doing so at an extremely slow rate.

Inscribing runes was an extremely painstaking process that was very taxing on one's spiritual sense, and the average True Immortal would've most likely divided the beans up into batches for rune inscription to lessen the strain on their spiritual sense.

While this was a feasible option, the downside was that due to the fact that the beans were refined in batches, only the batch of beans that had refined with the primary bean would have a strong connection to the primary bean, while the same couldn't be said for all of the other beans.

Under most circumstances, this wouldn't have had much of a negative impact, and the Dao Warriors would've still been able to function as normal, but if the Dao Warriors were required to set up arrays, just as the Golden Dao Warriors had done, then their reactions would've been slightly slower.

Thanks to Han Li's enormous spiritual sense, he was able to refine all of the beans in a single batch.

Time slowly passed by, and a month flew by in the blink of an eye.

Han Li was still completely engrossed in his work, oblivious to the passage of time.

He brought his palms together in front of his chest, and the final inscriptions were made on all of the beans in the array, following which the inscribed runes began to radiate dazzling black light.

The blue light in Han Li's eyes faded upon seeing this, and there was a slightly weary look on his face, but he was elated to have finally completed this process.

The light glowing from the array in the secret chamber also gradually dimmed as all of the arcs of golden lightning began to converge toward the pair of primary beans, while the lightning light barrier vanished.

Shortly thereafter, the golden lightning also vanished, and all of the beans fell back into the golden platform.

Han Li pulled out the yellow gourd, then patted its underside, and a burst of yellow light immediately appeared at its opening, releasing a burst of suction force that sucked in all of the beans.

However, instead of allowing the pair of primary beans to be sucked into the gourd, he stowed them away into his chest pocket instead.

After that he exhaled deeply as he produced an azure pill, which he consumed before closing his eyes to meditate.

The next day.

In a certain snowy valley within the territory of the Crimson Dawn Peak, a streak of azure light descended out of the sky, then faded to reveal Han Li.

He swept his gaze across the valley, then flew over to a relatively flat and open area.

There, he removed the yellow gourd from his waist, then chanted an incantation, and the the opening of the gourd immediately lit up with yellow radiance, following which a string of yellow beans flew out in rapid succession before landing on the ground.

As soon as the beans landed in the surrounding area, each of them instantly transformed into an armored Dao Warrior that stood at around 10 feet in height.

They were rather similar to Golden Dao Warriors in appearance, but they were wearing suits of armor with lightning veins inscribed upon them, and all several hundred of them had arranged themselves into a uniform array, presenting a formidable sight to behold.

Han Li flicked a finger through the air, and a streak of azure sword qi swept through the air before striking one of the Dao Warriors on the chest.

The Dao Warrior was instantly sent flying with a resounding boom before landing heavily on the ground to create a huge indentation.

In the next instant, the Dao Warrior sprang out of the crater, and its armor had already pierced through, while a gash had also been sliced into its chest, but the gash wasn't very deep and didn't appear to have been affecting its movements at all.

Han Li gave a slight nod upon seeing this.

He had only used around one percent of his power to unleash that streak of sword qi, but it still would've been too much for the average Grand Ascension cultivator to withstand, and the fact that it was only able to slightly wound this Dao Warrior indicated that its defenses were even more formidable than he anticipated.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li decided to pit the Dao Warriors against each other. Arcs of golden lightning flashed over their suits of armor, and they rushed into the valley at his behest, displaying far superior speed to the Golden Dao Warriors that Han Li had faced in the past.

Upon entering the valley, the Dao Warriors immediately split up into groups of two to engage in battle, and bursts of loud rumbling akin to formidable thunderclaps instantly rang out.

The entire valley began to tremble violently, triggering avalanches on all of the nearby mountains.

After some observation, Han Li discovered that these Dao Warriors were very similar to the Golden Dao Warriors in their style of battle in that they were just as reckless and uncaring for their own safety.

However, these Dao Warriors were clearly displaying superior regenerative abilities, able to quickly recover from all injuries as long as they weren't completely destroyed, and that was a very encouraging sight for Han Li.

After that, Han Li controlled the Dao Warriors to set up a few arrays, but the results weren't that great. However, he knew that this was due to a lack of practice, so he didn't pay it much heed.

He was already very pleased with the power being displayed by the Dao Warriors, and he stowed them away before returning to his cave abode.

After entering his secret chamber, he flipped a hand over to produce a golden metal ball, then called out, "Brother Xie..."

Moments later, several rifts appeared on the golden ball, out of which a series of thin metallic limbs emerged, and the ball transformed into a palm-sized golden crab amid a string of metallic clicking.

"Why have you called upon me, Fellow Daoist Han?" Daoist Xie asked as it looked up at Han Li from the palm of his hand.

"I recently came across an array that can integrate a Dao Warrior primary bean with a puppet, and I wanted to discuss it with you," Han Li replied.

"Are you considering fusing a primary bean with that immortal puppet, Fellow Daoist Han? I'm afraid that's not going to work on an immortal puppet that's missing its core," Daoist Xie said.

Han Li remained unfazed, and he smiled as he urged, "Don't be in such a hurry to shut down the idea, Brother Xie. Why don't you take a look at this primary bean first?"

He then flipped his other hand over to produce one of the primary beans, which had a series of golden lightning veins over its surface, as well as an image of the Lightning Kui beast.

Han Li set the primary bean down beside Daoist Xie, and the latter was immediately intrigued.

It made a lap around the primary bean, inspecting it carefully, then looked up at Han Li as it mused, "This primary bean possesses both earth and lightning attributes. Are you thinking..."

"That's right," Han Li interjected. "You were unable to fuse with the puppet due to mismatching attributes, but with this primary bean acting as an intermediary, perhaps it'll work."

Daoist Xie was silent for a moment, then said, "That is indeed a potentially feasible method... Can you show me the integration array?"

Han Li offered the stone shard to Daoist Xie, who grabbed onto it with one of its pincers.

A short while later, it released the stone shard, then turned to Han Li as it said in a solemn voice, "The lightning array that I asked you to set up earlier is one that works in a slow and subtle fashion, yet this array is far more aggressive. If the process fails, this priceless primary bean will for sure be destroyed, and that immortal puppet and I will most likely be harmed as well. Are you sure you're willing to take this risk?"

Chapter 314: Fusion

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then said, "You'll be harmed as well if the process fails? That's something that I failed to consider. Having said that, risk and reward always come hand in hand. If you manage successfully fuse with that immortal puppet, you'll immediately attain Golden Immortal Stage power, so I think it's still worth a try. Are you willing to take a gamble, Brother Xie?"

After slaying Zhong Luan, Han Li had been able to spend the past 200 years in relative peace, but he had never been able to shake off this prevailing sense of apprehension. Hence, after accumulating sufficient resources, he had constantly been cultivating arduously in the hope that he would be able to manifest a time law thread after reaching the late-True Immortal Stage so that he would be better equipped to take on Golden Immortal cultivators, but that endeavor had proven to be unsuccessful up to this point.

Now that he had been presented with the opportunity to potentially gain a Golden Immortal Stage ally, he naturally didn't want to pass it up.

Daoist Xie fell into a hesitant silence.

"I won't force you to make any decision on this matter, Brother Xie. Also, there's one thing that I must make clear ahead of time: if the fusion is successful, you will be fused as one with the puppet and the primary bean, thereby strengthening your connection to me, and due to the involvement of the primary bean, you'll be more firmly under my control. This is unavoidable, and it's something for you to consider," Han Li said in a candid fashion.

Daoist Xie remained silent for a while longer, then looked up at Han Li as it said, "Alright, I'm willing to give it a try as long as you don't forget the promise you made to me back in the Spirit Realm."

"Alright. In that case, I'll begin setting up the array right away," Han Li replied with a nod.

A month passed by in a flash.

During that time, Han Li had opened up a larger secret chamber in his cave abode, within which was a complex array with eight lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood with runes inscribed all over them distributed throughout.

Various types of materials, including Infinity Sand, had been placed into the nodes of the array, and there were also Immortal Origin Stones embedded into several indentations around the array.

The yellow-robed immortal puppet was seated at the center of the array with its legs crossed, and Han Li was standing outside the array as he flipped a hand over to produce a golden metal ball.

A string of mechanical clicking rang out, and the golden ball quickly transformed into a golden crab.

"Everything is ready, Brother Xie. You can begin," Han Li said as he turned to the golden crab.

Daoist Xie offered no response, enveloping itself in a ball of golden lightning before flying toward the yellow-robed puppet's chest and vanishing into it in a flash.

Han Li immediately sat down with his legs crossed upon seeing this, then made a hand seal as he began to chant an incantation.

A burst of yellow light emerged within the secret chamber amid a burst of buzzing, and gusts of yellow wind began to sweep over the array, forming a yellow vortex that enveloped the immortal puppet while also sweeping up all of the materials laid out across the array.

Immediately thereafter, a series of antiquated runes flew out of the immortal puppet's robes before flying into the vortex.

As soon as the spirit materials in the vortex came into contact with these runes, they immediately disintegrated into powder before surging toward the immortal puppet.

At the same time, Han Li flipped a hand over to produce one of his two primary beans, then tossed it forward, and the primary bean fell into the array in a flash.

Upon entering the array, the primary bean hovered above the immortal puppet's head, and several runes immediately adhered themselves to it as well, but it didn't disintegrate. Instead, it abruptly lit up and produced a Dao Warrior Tree projection.

The projection was around 10 feet tall, and it was rooted to the array with the yellow-robed puppet enveloped within its trunk.

Han Li made a hand seal before leaning forward and laying a palm against the ground, and as soon as he did this, all of the Immortal Origin Stones in the array lit up in unison, releasing a stream of immortal spiritual power into the trunk of the Dao Warrior Tree projection through its roots.

The tree projection began to glow brightly, and all of the broken down spirit materials vanished into the immortal puppet's body, while the yellow vortex faded away.

The sound of flowing electricity rang out as the runes on the eight lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood situated around the array lit up, and arcs of golden electricity shot out like a nest of lightning snakes before converging toward the immortal puppet.

At the same time, a burst of purplish-golden lightning erupted from the puppet's chest, and it was as if it had been draped into a large cloak of lightning.

This was a clear sign that Daoist Xie had already begun attempting to fuse itself with the puppet, and Han Li immediately switched to a different hand seal upon seeing this.

Right at this moment, a rumbling thunderclap suddenly rang out, and a giant golden crab projection appeared behind the immortal puppet with lightning flashing all over its body.

Han Li's attention was focused fully on the array in front of him as he thrust his palms forward, and the immortal spiritual power in his body surged forth like a mighty river.

Bursts of rumbling rang out incessantly within the secret chamber, and the walls also began to tremble violently.

Fortunately, Han Li had already anticipated this, and he had set up stabilization and isolation arrays in advance. Otherwise, these tremors would've caused quite a disturbance over the entire Crimson Dawn Peak.

As the tremors grew more violent, the yellow and purplish-golden light in the secret chamber also began to flash more erratically.

Han Li continued to cycle through a string of hand seals to maintain the outflow of immortal spiritual power, and he had also released spiritual sense threads to connect the primary bean, the immortal puppet, and Daoist Xie in order to forcibly integrate them.

Inside the secret chamber, the golden crab projection and the Dao Warrior Tree projection shrank down in unison from around 10 feet tall to only six to seven feet, then to two to three feet, and the yellow light and lightning enveloping them also began to converge toward the center.

Only after a long while did all of the light completely condense into a fist-sized ball of golden light that was hovering in front of the immortal puppet's chest, and a tiny tree projection and a golden crab could be seen within the ball of light.

At this point, almost all of Han Li's immortal spiritual power had flowed into the array, and his spiritual sense had been severely depleted as well, resulting in a slightly pale complexion.

"Fuse!" he roared, and in the next instant, all that remained of the immortal spiritual power in his body surged toward the immortal puppet without any reservation.

A faint crack rang out from the ground, and the Immortal Origin Stones embedded into the array also released all of their immortal spiritual power before shattering into pieces.

A vortex of light abruptly appeared at the immortal puppet's chest to devour the ball of golden light, and a thick bolt of lightning erupted out of the puppet's body amid a rumbling thunderclap.

It resembled a pillar of purplish-golden lightning that erupted into the heavens, blasting straight through the ceiling of the secret chamber and causing the entire Crimson Dawn Peak to shudder violently.

Thankfully, the pillar of lightning faded after only a few seconds.

Inside the secret chamber, Han Li's immortal spiritual power had been completely exhausted, so he could only withstand the blast of lightning with his Profound Immortal body alone, and he was sent crashing heavily into the wall behind him before throwing up a mouthful of blood.

After steadying himself, he took a glance at the immortal puppet, which remained completely still. He sat down with his legs crossed once again, then swallowed a yellow pill before summoning an Immortal Origin Stone that he held in his hand before closing his eyes to meditate.

Only after around 15 minutes had passed did he reopen his eyes before spitting out the remaining mixture of blood and saliva in his mouth.

All of a sudden, the immortal puppet's eyelids fluttered, and it opened its eyes to reveal a pair of golden pupils.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged, but internally, he was extremely excited as he said, "Congratulations on attaining a new body, Brother Xie. I was concerned that something would go wrong with the fusion process, but it appears my concerns were unnecessary."

The aura emanating from the immortal puppet's body indicated that it already possessed early-Golden Immortal Stage power.

Perhaps it was due to the involvement of the primary bean, but a spiritual restriction had already been planted deep in the puppet, ensuring that it wouldn't be able to turn on Han Li.

"It's all thanks to your help, Fellow Daoist Han. However, even though the fusion process was successful, due to the integration of the primary bean, the power in my body is a little chaotic, so I'll have to go into seclusion for a while for everything to settle down," Daoist Xie continued.

"That's not a problem. If you require any spirit stones or resources, feel free to tell me," Han Li replied with a nod.

Daoist Xie nodded expressionlessly in response, then closed its eyes to meditate.

Only now did Han Li allow a hint of elation to creep into his eyes, and he didn't linger in the secret chamber any longer, getting up to depart.

With this matter settled, he had to turn his attention to something else that he had to do.

......

A streak of azure light descended from the heavens, landing in front of the golden palace on the Gourd Peak to reveal Han Li.

He took a glance up at the plaque above the palace's entrance, then made his way inside.

The Immortal Medicine Pavilion was filled with medicine cabinets and was quite lively and bustling. At the moment, Ye Nanfeng was attending to an elderly man in front of a cabinet near the entrance.

As soon as he spotted Han Li, Ye Nanfeng gave him a smile and a wave.

Han Li nodded in response, then began to browse through the medicine cabinets on his own.

Before long, the elderly man seemed to have found what he was looking for, and he promptly departed after paying for his purchase.

Ye Nanfeng then quickly approached Han Li with a smile as he greeted, "Long time no see, Elder Li."

"It seems like your Immortal Medicine Pavilion has added a great deal of medicinal ingredients to its catalog since my last visit, Elder Ye," Han Li remarked as he withdrew his gaze from one of the medicine cabinets.

"You have a keen eye, Elder Li. It's all thanks to Dao Lord Mu that we've gotten all of this new inventory," Ye Nanfeng replied with a smile.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then asked, "Dao Lord Mu of the Flying Feather Peak?"

"Is there another Dao Lord Mu in our sect?" Ye Nanfeng asked.

"That's not what I meant. It's just that I heard that Dao Lord Mu has already been in seclusion for close to 100,000 years, could it be that he recently came out of seclusion?" Han Li asked.

Chapter 315: Number One Dao Lord

"You must've been in seclusion for quite some time, Elder Li. No wonder your aura has become significantly more powerful. Around a century ago, Dao Lord Mu suddenly came out of seclusion, then took several of his direct disciples on a trip to the Upper Arr Continent, and a lot of the new spirit medicines we acquired came from that trip," Ye Nanhua explained with a smile.

Han Li nodded in response with a contemplative expression. "I see. Speaking of spirit medicines, I came here to purchase some today. Please take a look for me, Elder Ye."

"Every time you come here, you always bring me a lot of business, Elder Li. I don't mean to brag, but even on the entire Ancient Cloud Continent, our Immortal Medicine Pavilion is near unmatched when it comes to the spirit medicine variety that we offer..."

Ye Nanfeng's voice suddenly trailed off, and his smile also faded as he inspected the list of spirit medicines in the jade slip.

Han Li wasn't all that surprised to see this change in Ye Nanfeng's expression.

After a brief silence, Ye Nanfeng shook his head as he said, "As far as I'm aware, we don't have even a single one of the ingredients on your list."

"It's fine, these spirit medicines are indeed quite difficult to find. Having said that, I'm sure you have many sources and connections, so if you can supply me with any information regarding any of these ingredients, I'd be happy to pay for it," Han Li said.

A slightly awkward look appeared on Ye Nanfeng's face, but he still replied in a polite manner, "I'm afraid I won't be able to help you, Elder Li. All of the spirit medicines on your list are extremely rare, and there are some that I only vaguely recall reading about in some ancient scriptures. Of course, I'll be sure to keep an eye out for any information and inform you if I do come across some leads."

"You have my thanks, Elder Ye."

Han Li didn't waste any more time here as he cupped his fist in a parting salute.

He had been searching extensively for the final few ingredients on the dao pill recipe, exhausting virtually all of the avenues available to him, but to no avail.

All of a sudden, a thought occurred to Ye Nanfeng, and he said, "Don't be disheartened, Elder Li. Under normal circumstances, it would be next to impossible to find these ingredients, but there may be some better chances for you at the moment."

"Oh? What do you mean by that, Elder Ye?" Han Li hurriedly asked.

Ye Nanfeng drew a little closer to Han Li, then said in a quiet voice, "This hasn't yet been made public knowledge in the sect, but I've heard that in a few more years, Dao Lord Baili will be coming out of seclusion."

Han Li was rather taken aback to hear this.

Dao Lord Baili Yan was the number one dao lord of the Blaze Dragon Dao, and it was said that he had already reached the pinnacle of the Golden Immortal Stage, so he was only one step away from becoming a High Zenith Stage Jade Immortal.

However, he was always in seclusion, and very few people in the sect had ever seen him.

"You only joined the sect in the past 1,000 years, so it makes sense that you aren't aware of this. After all, the last time Dao Lord Baili came out of seclusion was tens of thousands of years ago. Traditionally, whenever he comes out of seclusion, Dao Lord Baili would always hold a preaching ceremony.

“When that time comes, not only will all of the sect's elders be in attendance, many fellow daoists from all over the Northern Glacial Immortal Region will travel from far and wide to attend as well. With such a massive influx of outsiders, there will generally always be some auctions and exchange events taking place in the leadup to the preaching ceremony, so perhaps you'll be able to find some of the spirit medicines that you're looking for there," Ye Nanfeng explained.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this. "I see. I was indeed unaware of all of this. Thank you for enlightening me, Elder Ye."

"There's no need to thank me, Elder Li. I'm sure news of this would spread throughout the sect soon anyway," Ye Nanfeng replied with a smile.

Han Li didn't dwell on this subject any longer as he flipped a hand over to produce a jade slip, then said, "Elder Ye, I have another list of ingredients here that I'm also trying to procure."

The jade slip contained the ingredients required to refine a pill called the Myriad Axis Pill.

The Myriad Axis Pill was suitable for late-True Immortal cultivators to consume, and he had obtained the recipe from Ping Yaozi.

Now that he had progressed to the late-True Immortal Stage, the pills that he had refined in the past were no longer effective, so he had to search for new pills.

All of the ingredients required to refine the Myriad Axis Pill were quite rare and exotic, indicating that it was no ordinary late-True Immortal Stage pill.

He had sent out Meng Yungui and the others several hundred years ago to search for the ingredients enclosed in the recipe, but they had only managed to find three or four of the supplementary ingredients, while the three main ingredients required to refine the pill remained elusive.

After inspecting the contents of the jade slip with his spiritual sense, a wry smile appeared on Ye Nanfeng's face as he said, "These ingredients are also quite rare, Elder Li. I'm assuming they were requested by that Earthly Pill Master friend of yours, right?

“In particular, the Myriad Axis Fruit, the Herofall Flower and the Blood Crystal Lotus Root are very uncommon. I can supply you with all of the supplementary ingredients, but out of the three main ingredients, we only have the Herofall Flower."

He had always taken pride in the comprehensive nature of the Immortal Medicine Pavilion's inventory, but this was already the second time that he had failed to fulfill an order.

"That's right. That friend of mine acquired an ancient pill recipe recently, but he's been unable to secure all of the required ingredients, and that's why he asked me for help. I'll take whatever you have here and find the rest elsewhere," Han Li replied.

……

Close to an hour later, Han Li emerged from the Immortal Medicine Pavilion with a slightly pained look on his face.

The ingredients for the Myriad Axis Pill were extremely expensive, and it had cost him a great deal of Immortal Origin Stones, even though he had only bought a few batches. Among them, the Herofall Flower was the most expensive, with a single 1,000-year-old specimen costing 15 Immortal Origin Stones.

Thankfully, he could mature and breed the flower with the spirit liquid from the Heaven Controlling Vial, so this wasn't a big problem.

After leaving the Immortal Medicine Pavilion, Han Li returned straight to the Crimson Dawn Peak.

According to Ye Nanfeng, there were still several years left until Dao Lord Baili was going to come out of seclusion, and it was very likely that he would be able to find more of the ingredients that he needed around that time, but it was most likely going to be very expensive.

He had already exhausted a great deal of funds in his prior pill refinement, and even though he still had a decent supply of Immortal Origin Stones, it was best that he earned more as a safety precaution.

After sitting down in his secret chamber, Han Li injected his spiritual sense into his storage pouch, then swept a sleeve through the air, and a bunch of objects emerged, including spirit treasures, cultivation arts, and materials.

These were all spoils that Han Li had reaped from the three True Immortal cultivators that he had slain at the Holy Puppet Sect, and he had already sold some of their belongings, but there was still quite a bit left. Given the circumstances, he didn't have time to complete any missions, so the only way to secure Immortal Origin Stones in a short time would be to sell everything here.

Han Li flipped a hand over to put on his tiger mask, then summoned the array plate and listed everything laid out before him in the exchange column, making sure to list everything at a slightly discounted price in order to sell them off quickly.

After that, he made his way to his medicine garden before pulling out a jade box, within which were several purplish-black spirit flowers that were giving off a peculiar aroma.

These were the Herofall Flowers that he had purchased. In order to secure more seeds, he had to wait for the flowers to bear fruit, and that was only going to happen once they reached 30,000 years of age, but that was naturally not a problem for him.

He cleared out a new area in his medicine garden, then carefully planted the Herofall Flowers.

After that, he returned to the entrance of the medicine garden, and a series of emotions welled up in his heart as he looked at all of the precious and exotic spirit plants thriving in the garden.

He had expended an enormous amount of time and effort to build up this medicine garden to its current state, and it was all thanks to this garden full of spirit plants that he was able to progress so quickly in his cultivation.

After lingering in the medicine garden for a moment longer, he returned to his secret chamber before sitting down with his legs crossed.

Without the support of pills, his rate of cultivation progression was going to be very slow, so instead of cultivating, he decided to continue appraising the eight-and-a-half-sentence mantra to see if he could reap any additional rewards.

Just as Ye Nanfeng anticipated, it didn't take long for news of Dao Lord Baili's imminent emergence from seclusion to begin spreading in the sect, and it was officially announced that the preaching ceremony would be held in seven years.

The entire Blaze Dragon Dao erupted into a frenzy with the emergence of this news.

According to sect records, Dao Lord Baili had held eight preaching ceremonies up to this point, and every single one of them had been an extremely prestigious event even in the context of the entire Northern Glacial Immortal Region.

What was special about this ceremony was that there were no restrictions on the people who could attend. In other words, even the outer sect disciples of the Blaze Dragon Dao were able to attend. As for how much they would be able to get out of it, that was up to them.

Apparently, this was a rule established by Dao Lord Baili himself, and it had always been upheld.

Some of the inner sect elders and direct disciples that were stuck at cultivation bottlenecks were extremely excited by this opportunity.

There was always a chance that some words of wisdom from Dao Lord Baili could address their cultivation problems and help them break through their bottlenecks. It was said that attending past preaching ceremonies was a major factor that contributed to many members of the sect ascending to the True Immortal Stage.

Some disciples who hadn't yet reached the Grand Ascension Stage were just as excited nonetheless. After all, Dao Lord Baili already had half a foot in the High Zenith Stage, and being able to hear him preach was an extraordinary opportunity.

Seven years flew by in the blink of an eye.

This was not a short time for a mortal, but for cultivators, perhaps it wasn't even as long as the duration of a session of meditation.

The gates of the cave abode on the Crimson Dawn Peak were opened, and Han Li emerged from within.

Even though he had been in seclusion these past few years, he had made sure to keep up to date on the sect's affairs.

Dao Lord Baili's preaching ceremony was going to take place in seven days, and he had originally intended to come out of seclusion earlier than this, but while appraising the eight-and-a-half-sentence mantra during his seclusion, he had inadvertently gained some insight into the aura concealment secret technique enclosed in the Origin Separation Yin Devil Arts.

Only on this day did he finally achieve initial mastery of the secret technique, and he began to chant an incantation as azure light surged over his body.

Several chain projections appeared within the azure light before abruptly vanishing into his body, and his aura was instantly completely concealed, yet it wasn't forced in the slightest, and there were no signs to indicate the aura concealment that had taken place.

Upon reaching the True Immortal Stage, unless one were to completely release their aura while in battle, it would generally be impossible for others to determine one's cultivation base and exactly how many immortal acupoints one had opened.

However, someone with sufficiently formidable spiritual sense would still be able to glean the cultivation bases of others, but with this secret technique up his sleeve, even the average Golden Immortal wouldn't have been able to detect his aura.

A pleased smile appeared on Han Li's face, and he flew away into the distance as a streak of azure light.

Chapter 316: Invitation from Qi Liang

Somewhere in the central region of the Bell Toll Mountain Range, all of the snow and ice within a radius of hundreds of thousands of kilometers had melted away, revealing the lush greenery underneath.

The sky was as clear and bright as a blue crystal, and white clouds were hanging between the mountains, while resplendent five-colored light shone through the heavens. Countless cranes were flying through the clouds while letting loose clear cries, and the entire place resembled an immortal paradise.

At the center of the area was a pristine white mountain that was very smooth and uniform, resembling an enormous white jade pillar.

The mountain severed halfway up with an extremely smooth cross-section, looking as if it had been sliced into two by a giant blade, creating an enormous plateau that served as a plaza.

Even though only half the mountain remained, the white plaza was still situated far above the clouds.

At the center of the plaza was a huge white jade platform that was close to 10,000 feet tall with countless runes engraved onto its surface.

A staircase led from the platform all the way down the plaza, and there were thousands of round cushions placed on the steps of the staircase.

The ground surrounding the plaza was also riddled with countless cushions that stretched all the way to the edges of the plaza, and this platform on the White Jade Peak was where the preaching ceremony was set to take place.

Prior to the commencement of the ceremony, the plaza was completely deserted.

No more than several hundred kilometers away from the White Jade Peak was a city that stretched for thousands of kilometers, complete with countless lavish pagodas and pavilions that were concealed within the cloud and mist.

In contrast with the deserted White Jade Peak, this city was extremely lively and bustling, and there were countless streaks of light flying through the air above the city.

Occasionally, people would fly out of the city in different directions, while others converged toward the city from afar.

Right at this moment, a streak of azure light arrived from the distance, then faded to reveal Han Li.

He cast his gaze toward the White Jade Peak in the distance, then quickly withdrew his gaze before descending toward the city down below.

The entire city was enshrouded within a huge azure light barrier with Blaze Dragon Dao disciples stationed all around it.

Upon his arrival, Han Li was immediately welcomed by a young Blaze Dragon Dao disciple, who extended a deep bow toward Han Li upon seeing his inner sect elder robes, then said, "Welcome, esteemed elder. Apologies for the delay, but according to the rules of the sect, anyone who enters White Jade City must first have their identity verified."

"That's fine," Han Li replied as he pulled out his elder badge.

The young disciple pulled out a white jade talisman that he waved at Han Li's badge, and a layer of white light emerged from the talisman to form a small screen of white light that displayed Han Li's image and information.

The disciple took a glance at the information on the light screen, then flipped a hand over to produce an azure badge as he said, "Thank you for your cooperation, Elder Li. I'll open the restriction for you right away."

With a wave of the badge, a streak of azure light shot out from within before vanishing into the light barrier that encompassed the city.

The light barrier then shuddered before an opening that was large enough to fit a person appeared on its surface, and Han Li stowed away his elder badge before flying into the city through the opening.

He made his way along a street, traveling deeper into the city while inspecting his surroundings, and a hint of surprise soon appeared in his eyes.

Only after entering through the light barrier did he discover just how beautiful and lavish the buildings in the city were. The wide streets extended throughout the city like a system of cobwebs, and they were lined with opulent shops, presenting a stunning sight that didn't lose to any of the large cities that he had seen before.

Outside of his cultivation, he had made frequent forays throughout the Bell Toll Mountain Range during the past years, but he had never visited this place before.

The shops that lined the streets were selling all types of wares, including materials, pills, and treasures, all of which were of quite a high caliber. The wares being sold weren't inferior in the slightest to those sold in the markets in the Blaze Dragon Dao, and there were some things that were very rarely seen even in those markets.

Many of the shop owners clearly weren't Blaze Dragon Dao disciples. Instead, they were most likely from subsidiary powers to the Blaze Dragon Dao, and they were aiming to sell some specialty local products during the leadup to the preaching ceremony.

After walking along the street for a while, Han Li stopped in front of a materials shop.

From the entrance, he could see dozens of shelves inside, all of which were laden with precious materials.

At this moment, the shop was filled with customers, and business appeared to have been booming.

After a brief pause, Han Li stepped into the shop, and he was immediately greeted by a young red-robed attendant.

"What materials are you looking for, Senior? We have a comprehensive inventory of all types of spirit materials at competitive prices..."

Before the young attendant had a chance to finish what he was saying, an elderly man who appeared to have been the shopkeeper hurriedly approached Han Li as he said, "Go see if the other customers need any help, I'll attend to this customer myself."

The young attendant faltered slightly upon hearing this, then promptly departed.

"Welcome, esteemed elder. What materials are you looking for today? I am from the Yi Clan in the west, and our clan has been selling spirit materials for generations. We are a reputable business, and I'm sure you won't be disappointed by our wares," the elderly man said in a respectful manner.

Han Li didn't waste any time with words as he flipped a hand over to produce a jade slip, which contained a list of the remaining ingredients listed in the dao pill recipe, as well as the other two primary ingredients for refining the Myriad Axis Pill.

The elderly man accepted the jade slip from Han Li, but after inspecting its contents, an apologetic look appeared on his face as he said, "These are all extremely precious items, and I'm afraid our shop does not have what you're looking for."

"Do you know where I'll be able to buy these things?" Han Li asked.

"I've only ever seen these materials in scriptures, and I've never heard of any being sold," the elderly man replied with a shake of his head.

Han Li nodded calmly in response, then took back his jade slip before turning to leave, and the elderly man hurriedly accompanied him out of the shop.

After emerging from the shop, Han Li continued to walk along the street, and a short while later, he made his way into another large materials shop.

A short while later, he emerged from the shop, once again without any luck, but he remained unfazed as he continued onward.

……

Close to a day later, Han Li emerged from a huge materials shop in the central area of the city, and his expression didn't betray much emotion, but internally, he was starting to feel quite frustrated.

Thus far, he had visited most of the materials shops in the city, yet not only had he not been able to find what he was looking for, he wasn't even able to gather any leads on where he could find the ingredients on his list.

There were still some shops left for him to visit, but seeing as the largest shops didn't have what he was looking for, the chances that he would find success in the remaining shops were quite slim.

With that in mind, he heaved a faint sigh and was just about to continue onward when a voice rang out from behind him.

"Brother Li!"

Han Li turned around to discover a white-robed man approaching him with a smile, and it was none other than Qi Liang.

"Long time no see, Brother Qi," Han Li greeted with a smile.

He had spent the majority of his time in seclusion, while the rest of his time was spent on completing various missions, so it had already been close to 300 years since he had last met Qi Liang.

Qi Liang was just about to say something when his eyes abruptly widened, and he was silent for a long while before finally finding his voice again. "Brother Li, your aura... Could it be that you've already reached the mid-True Immortal Stage?"

"Indeed. I encountered some strokes of fortune during the past few centuries, and I recently managed to make a breakthrough," Han Li replied in an ambiguous manner.

Qi Liang could tell that Han Li didn't want to speak much on this matter, so he refrained from prying any further. "I am truly envious, Brother Li."

"When did you get here, Brother Qi?" Han Li asked, promptly changing the subject.

"I got here a few days ago, and I've been exploring the city ever since, but I didn't see you before this. Could it be that you only just arrived? Why didn't you come a little earlier? This place has already been thriving for quite some time," Qi Liang said with a smile.

"Sounds like you've been busy, Brother Qi. My original intention was to come here a bit earlier, but I was delayed by some matters," Han Li explained with a smile.

"I suppose you haven't really missed much. Generally speaking, the most precious treasures will only appear much closer to the preaching ceremony. By the way, I just so happen to be on my way to an exchange event for True Immortal Stage fellow daoists. Would you be interested in tagging along?" Qi Liang asked.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly upon hearing this, and he immediately nodded in response. "Of course!"

"I knew you wouldn't pass up such a great opportunity. The event venue is just up ahead, and it should be starting soon," Qi Liang said with a smile as he led the way forward.

"I didn't know there was such a lavish city in the sect. Why is it that I've never heard anyone speak of it before?" Han Li asked.

"White Jade City and the White Jade Peak are very important locations in our sect, and under normal circumstances, this city is closed to the outside. Entry is only granted during important occasions like the preaching ceremony," Qi Liang explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod.

The two of them continued to chat, and after making their way down the street for a while, they turned onto another street, this one lined with buildings that were even more lavish and opulent, and many of them were enshrouded within light barriers of different colors.

Han Li noticed that whenever the cultivators walking down the street cast their eyes toward these buildings, they would always do so with awe and veneration on their faces.

"This is the place," Qi Liang declared as he stopped in front of a three-story pavilion.

This building was also enshrouded within a white light barrier that made it impossible to see into the building, giving it quite an aura of mystique.

Chapter 317: Heavenly Scorpion Badge

Qi Liang strode forward, then flipped a hand over to produce a white badge that was giving off a faint white glow with a scorpion design engraved onto its surface.

With a wave of the badge, a streak of white light was released, and it vanished into the white light barrier in a flash.

An opening immediately appeared in the light barrier, and it instantly closed after Han Li and Qi Liang had passed through.

Only then was Han Li able to see the pavilion enshrouded within the light barrier in its full glory. It was an intricately constructed three-story pavilion that was entirely a pristine white color and appeared to have been constructed from some type of special jade.

Hanging above the entrance of the pavilion was a white plaque that bore the words "Heavenly Scorpion Pavilion" in large characters, and some scorpion designs were engraved around the edge of the plaque, much like the badge that Qi Liang had pulled out earlier.

"This exchange event is being hosted by the Heavenly Scorpion Sect, which is a subsidiary sect to our Blaze Dragon Dao. The Heavenly Scorpion Sect isn't a particularly powerful sect, but it has a great deal of expertise in all types of restrictions and the refinement of Dao Warriors," Qi Liang informed in a low voice.

Han Li nodded in response with a contemplative expression.

Qi Liang stowed his badge away before entering the pavilion.

The furnishings inside the pavilion were quite lavish, with a lush red carpet on the ground and dragons and phoenixes engraved on the pristine white walls. The room was also surrounded by screens and immaculately pruned potted plants, resembling the interior of a wealthy family's estate.

Several maidservants dressed in red were situated around the room, and they immediately extended respectful curtseys toward Han Li and Qi Liang.

They appeared to have been no different from normal people, but in reality, they were merely Dao warriors, and all of them were giving off auras comparable to that of a Body Integration cultivator.

Han Li took a closer look at these maidservants to find that their movements were very natural, and their eyes were also just as bright and full of life as a normal person.

Having already refined a batch of Dao Warriors of his own, he had naturally gained a far better understanding of Dao Warriors, but even so, he was still unable to tell how the Heavenly Scorpion Sect had managed to refine these Dao Warrior maidservants.

His Dao Warriors were most likely far more formidable in battle than these Dao Warriors, but they were far lacking when it came to how life-like they were.

Right at this moment a young woman emerged from deeper in the building, and she extended a respectful curtsey to Han Li and Qi Liang.

"Take us to the exchange hall," Qi Liang instructed.

"Yes, please come with me, seniors," the young woman hurriedly replied, then led the two of them up a staircase to a hall on the third floor.

The hall was quite large, but it was completely empty with the exception of some furniture.

At the center of the room was a giant screen that bore an extremely life-like scenic painting, making one feel as if they were situated in the depicted scenic location.

Han Li inspected his surroundings momentarily, following which his brows furrowed slightly as he turned his gaze back to the screen.

Right at this moment, the young woman chanted an incantation before releasing a streak of white light into the screen, and a layer of translucent white light instantly appeared on its surface.

The scenery depicted on it instantly sprang to life in a flurry of movement, and it was also releasing black light that fused with the white light to form a black door.

A hint of intrigue flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this.

The young woman continued to chant her incantation while making hand seals, and the black door began to glow brighter and brighter with black light while also rapidly expanding.

A dull thump rang out as the black door flew out of the screen, hovering in front of it before opening to reveal a long passageway.

"Go ahead, seniors, the hall is just up ahead," the young woman informed.

Qi Liang nodded in response, then waved a dismissive hand, and the young woman quickly departed after extending a parting curtsey.

"Let's go," Qi Liang said as he led the way into the passageway.

Han Li strode through the passageway while inspecting it closely, and he could tell that the passageway had been created using an extremely advanced spatial restriction that resulted in a very stable space.

Qi Liang could see that Han Li had taken an interest in the passageway that they were walking through, and he explained, "The Heavenly Scorpion Sect is very adept in spatial restrictions, particularly ones that create independent areas. I've heard that many of the secret areas in our sect were created with the help of the Heavenly Scorpion Sect."

Han Li nodded in response, but his brows then furrowed slightly as he asked, "This is just an exchange event, not some shady, under-the-table deal, so why have they gone out of their way to hold the event in this separate space? Could it be that there are going to be so many people in attendance that they can't all fit in the hall outside?"

"There won't be many people in attendance, but the Heavenly Scorpion Sect has always had a habit of doing this, both to provide a private area for all of the event attendees, as well as to show off their expertise in spatial restrictions," Qi Liang explained with a smile.

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod.

"By the way, the exchange event here will be held once per day in the leadup to the preaching ceremony. If you're interested, I can get them to assign you a Heavenly Scorpion Badge as well so you can come to the next few exchange events as well," Qi Liang said.

"I hope that's not too much trouble," Han Li replied with a smile.

"Of course not! With your formidable cultivation base, the Heavenly Scorpion Sect would be scrambling to befriend you!" Qi Liang chuckled.

As they were chatting with one another, they reached the end of the passageway, where they arrived in a side hall and were greeted by an azure-robed elderly man with a warm smile on his face.

"Welcome, Fellow Daoist Qi. May I ask who this fellow daoist is?"

"This is Elder Li, a good friend of mine who's also from the Blaze Dragon Dao. He's always in seclusion, so very few people know of him. Brother Li, this is Fellow Daoist Changhe of the Heavenly Scorpion Sect, he'll be the one hosting the exchange event."

It seemed that Qi Liang and the elderly man were very familiar with one another.

"It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance, Fellow Daoist Changhe," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in a salute.

The elderly man responded in kind. "The pleasure is all mine, Fellow Daoist Li."

"Brother Li only just got here today, so he doesn't yet have a Heavenly Scorpion Badge. You wouldn't turn him away on that basis, would you, Fellow Daoist Changhe?" Qi Liang asked in a joking manner.

"Of course not, Fellow Daoist Qi. Fellow Daoist Li is more than welcome to attend our exchange events. Here's a Heavenly Scorpion Badge for you, Fellow Daoist Li. We'll be holding exchange events every day for the next few days, so feel free to come as you please," Daoist Changhe said as he offered a white badge to Han Li.

"You have my thanks," Han Li said as he accepted the badge.

"You're very much welcome, Fellow Daoist Li. Please follow me, the exchange event will be starting very soon."

With that, Daoist Changhe led Han Li's duo out of the side hall, and they passed through a corridor before arriving in a circular main hall.

The furnishings in this main hall were extremely lavish, and the ground was entirely paved with a type of premium material known as Green Pine Jade. There were also many bright gems embedded into the walls to fill the entire hall with dazzling radiance.

An antiquated little cauldron was placed in each of the hall's four corners, and there was a stick of burning yellow incense in each cauldron, giving off a refined and elegant aroma.

At the center of the hall was a large round table, around which were placed around two dozen chairs.

The table and the chairs were all crafted from some type of blue jade material that was giving off a cool and refreshing energy, clearly indicating that this was some type of precious material.

At this point, there were already around a dozen True Immortal cultivators seated around the table, and everyone immediately turned to look at Han Li's trio as they came in.

Some of them appeared to have been familiar with Qi Liang, and they only took a few glances at Han Li before averting their eyes.

Han Li made no eye contact with anyone, and only after taking seat did he begin to inspect the people around him.

Close to half of the people present were Blaze Dragon Dao elders, but Han Li only recalled two or three of them. As for those from outside of the Blaze Dragon Dao, he naturally didn't know any of them.

Qi Liang had a large social circle and began to chat with many of the other people present, and the atmosphere in the hall gradually began to liven up a little.

Han Li took no part in the conversations, merely sitting in silence as he casually swept his gaze around the table.

With this tremendous spiritual sense, he was able to instantly determine that most of the cultivators present were at the early-True Immortal Stage, while only two were at the mid-True Immortal Stage.

One of those two was a portly middle-aged man dressed in Blaze Dragon Dao elder robes. He had a thin mustache and a pair of eyes that were constantly darting around, making him resemble a fat yet shrewd rat.

The other mid-True Immortal cultivator was a white-robed elderly man from outside of the Blaze Dragon Dao, and he was seated with his eyes closed, paying no heed to the people around him.

The portly Blaze Dragon Dao elder seemed to have detected Han Li's gaze, and he looked back at Han Li before flashing him a smile, causing his mustache to wiggle a little in a rather comical sight.

Han Li was rather amused by this, but he naturally wasn't going to display his amusement. He gave the portly elder a slight nod, yet right as he was about to avert his gaze, a layer of black light suddenly appeared within the portly elder's eyes before quickly transforming into a pair of tiny vortexes.

A burst of peculiar power erupted out of the vortexes to ensnare Han Li's gaze, and all of a sudden, Han Li found himself situated in a world that was filled with white mist.

Several young women emerged from the mist, and their thin veil clothing didn't leave much to the imagination as they made all types of seductive gestures toward Han Li with their alluring bodies.

Han Li was able to instantly tell that this was an illusion, and he paid no heed to the women around him as he gently blew out a breath.

All of the women around him instantly faded, and countless cracks abruptly appeared in the surrounding world of white mist without any warning, following which it shattered to reveal the hall that Han Li was situated in once again.

The portly elder shuddered slightly, and the black light in his eyes was thrown into a state of disarray before fading away, revealing the stunned look in his eyes.

Han Li cast a cold gaze toward the portly elder, in response to which the elder offered up an apologetic smile.

This was only a very discreet clash between the two, but all of the other cultivators present were at the True Immortal Stage, so this naturally didn't escape their notice, and all of them were rather taken aback by this turn of events.

Chapter 318: Exchange Event

"That man is quite a renowned mid-True Immortal Stage elder of our sect. His name is Shu Tiansheng, and illusions are his forte. He's not a bad person, but he's very mischievous and often uses his illusions to play pranks on others. Rest assured, he has no ill intentions," Qi Liang explained to Han Li through voice transmission.

It was indeed true that the illusion just now hadn't tried to harm him in any way, so Han Li decided not to pursue the matter, merely withdrawing his gaze and paying no further heed to Shu Tiansheng.

Shu Tiansheng was quite relieved to see this, but he was still occasionally darting curious glances at Han Li.

An hour passed by, and during this time, two more True Immortals arrived.

Another 15 minutes passed without any further new arrivals, and the white-robed elderly man opened his eyes as he said in a cold voice, "It's about time we began, is it not, Fellow Daoist Changhe? I still have matters to attend to after this."

A hesitant look appeared on Daoist Changhe's face upon hearing this. There was still some time left until the scheduled start, but it didn't appear as if anyone else was going to show up.

"Alright, let's begin. There are 19 fellow daoists attending this exchange event. On behalf of our Heavenly Scorpion Sect, I would like to thank you for your patronage."

Daoist Changhe rose to his feet and cupped his fist in a salute to everyone present as he spoke.

"Let's skip all the formalities and begin, Fellow Daoist Changhe," a square-faced Blaze Dragon Dao elder said.

Despite being repeatedly rebuked, Daoist Changhe wasn't irked in the slightest as he declared, "It seems like everyone's in quite a hurry. The rules of this exchange event are the same as before. Everyone takes turns displaying the treasures that they prepared, then provide a short description of the treasure, as well as what you're looking for in exchange.

“If both sides agree to the deal, then it'll be finalized. On top of that, our Heavenly Scorpion Sect is only providing this venue, and we're doing so free of charge, so if any disputes arise after an exchange is made, we accept no responsibility. With that, let's begin."

As soon as his voice trailed off, a bald man seated next to him immediately rose to his feet.

The man patted the storage pouch strapped to his waist, and a blue jade box appeared in his hand.

The jade box was surrounded by a small cloud of blue mist, and it was giving off a bone-chilling aura.

It was clear that the box held something quite remarkable, and everyone's attention was immediately drawn to it.

A pleased look appeared on the bald man's face at the sight of everyone's reactions, and he opened the box in a slow and deliberate fashion to reveal a fist-sized blue crystal with liquid-like blue light flowing around it.

The crystal was giving off a glacial aura coupled with faint law power fluctuations, and as soon as it was revealed, the air temperature in the hall plummeted, causing all of the moisture in the air to freeze into ice crystals, presenting a beautiful spectacle to behold.

"This is a piece of Blue-veined Glacial Crystal. It‘s near-indestructible and contains extremely formidable glacial qi, making it an ideal material for refining frost-attribute immortal treasures," the bold man declared with a proud expression.

Many of the people present were clearly interested in the crystal, but Han Li only took a glance at it before withdrawing his gaze.

To the average True Immortal, materials that contained law powers were very precious, but he possessed many such items, so this one wasn't of particular interest to him.

"That's a very precious material, Fellow Daoist Xin. Have you considered what you would like in exchange for it?" Daoist Changhe asked.

"I would like a metal-attribute spirit material or demon beast core of the same caliber," the bald man replied.

Everyone remained silent, and the people that were interested in the crystal could only shake their heads with wry smiles.

The Blue-veined Glacial Crystal was indeed a precious material, but what he was asking for was just as precious and rare.

The bald man's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this.

"I don't have either of the two things that you stated, but I'm willing to purchase that crystal from you using Immortal Origin Stones," an elderly man wearing a round hat declared.

"I'm not short on Immortal Origin Stones at the moment. If no one can offer me what I asked for, then I'll be keeping this crystal for now," the bald man replied as he closed the jade box and sat back down.

The elderly man wearing the round hat could only heave a forlorn sigh in response.

After the bald man sat down, the young woman seated next to him rose to her feet, then swept a hand through the air to release four or five azure bones, all of which were giving off a faint azure glow. "These are some True Immortal demon beast bones, and in exchange, I would like some pills to assist me in my cultivation."

Demon beast materials generally weren't that precious, so the bones on display didn't attract much interest.

However, these were still the remains of True Immortal Stage demon beasts, so they were ultimately taken by a Blaze Dragon Dao in exchange for two vials of pills.

After the young woman came Shu Tiansheng.

"Fellow daoists, I've brought with me a set of 49 Lost Soul Flags, every single one of which is a spirit treasure in their own right, while the three primary flags are top-grade spirit treasures. When unleashed all at once, the 49 Lost Soul Flags are just as powerful as the average immortal treasure.

“In exchange for them, I would like one piece each of Profound Devilish Metal Essence and Heavenly Softwater Crystal," Shu Tiansheng declared as he swept a sleeve through the air, and 49 palm-sized black flags appeared in front of him one after another, with three of them clearly larger than the rest.

Shu Tiansheng made a hand seal, and a dark cloud that was as black as ink erupted out of the flags to instantly fill the entire hall. A burst of horrific howling also rang out from within the black cloud, causing the surrounding space to shudder.

Everyone was quite amazed to see this, and Han Li took an extra glance at the flags as well. Up to this point, these flags were the most precious item that had been presented, but he still wasn't interested.

However, many of the other cultivators present were very keen to get their hands on this set of flags, and after a fierce round of bidding, they were ultimately exchanged for a piece of Profound Devilish Metal Essence and 2,000 top-grade spirit stones, as well as several other treasures.

The items presented by the next few people after Shu Tiansheng were also quite remarkable, and the atmosphere in the exchange event was gradually beginning to heat up.

Up to this point, the most precious items presented had been three purple flowers called Purple Devil's Trumpets, and each one contained enough poison to kill a True Immortal. At the same time, they were an extremely precious type of spirit material for refining poison-attribute immortal treasures.

In exchange, the owner of the flowers was asking for the core of a True Immortal Stage demon beast known as the Crimson Crown Fire Crane, but no one had such a demon core in their possession.

As time passed, the atmosphere in the exchange event gradually peaked to a climax.

Qi Liang had his turn right before Han Li, and he was quite fortunate, exchanging a pair of spirit treasures for a 100,000-year-old spirit plant.

Finally, it was Han Li's turn, and he swept a sleeve over the table to produce two items, namely a black ball and a crimson crystal the size of a human head.

The black ball was the demon core of Zhong Luan's black crane steed, while the crimson crystal was the material that contained fire law powers that he had obtained from the thin elderly man.

Through some investigation, Han Li had discovered that this was a type of material known as Blush Cloud Fire Crystal, and while it did contain fire-attribute law powers, its natural limitations meant that it couldn't hold a large amount of fire-attribute spiritual power, thereby making it unfit for use as a tool refinement material.

However, it had an alternative use, which was to tame fire-attribute spiritual power.

Fire-attribute spiritual power was generally extremely violent, yet any fire-attribute spiritual power that was passed through a piece of Blush Cloud Fire Crystal would instantly become extremely mellow and mild.

It was exactly because of this that this crystal was one of the best materials for refining pill cauldrons or tool refinement cauldrons. Even if only a small amount of this crystal were added to a cauldron, its stability would be significantly enhanced. This chunk of Blush Cloud Fire Crystal was definitely large enough to refine an exceptional cauldron, so it would've definitely been able to fetch an astronomical price in a sect that was proficient in pill or tool refinement.

Compared with the Blush Cloud Fire Crystal, the black demon core was also very precious, but far less so.

Daoist Changhe initially faltered slightly at the sight of the Blush Cloud Fire Crystal, following which an intense look appeared in his eyes as he stared at the crystal with an unblinking gaze, and he was so excited that his cheeks had become slightly flushed.

Most of the people present weren't able to identify this crystal, but they could tell from Daoist Changhe's expression that it was an extremely precious item, and they began asking one another about it through voice transmission.

"I have here a True Immortal Stage demon beast core and a piece of Blush Cloud Fire Crystal. I'm looking to exchange the demon beast core for a Myriad Axis Fruit and a Blood Crystal Lotus Root, both of which must be over 50,000 years of age, and I'll accept anyone of a list of nine materials for the Blush Cloud Fire Crystal," Han Li declared, then rattled off the list of nine materials that he was searching for.

The excitement in everyone's eyes gradually faded upon hearing what Han Li had to say, and a long period of silence ensued.

Right at this moment, the white-robed elderly man broke the silence, and he was looking at the black demon beast core as he said, "I have a Myriad Axis Fruit, but no Blood Crystal Lotus Root. Would you accept something else as a substitute?"

"Let me take a look at your Myriad Axis Fruit first," Han Li said.

The white-robed elderly man pulled out an azure wooden box, but instead of immediately tossing it to Han Li, he asked, "Would I be able to take a closer look at that demon core as well, Fellow Daoist?"

"Of course," Han Li replied with a smile, then swept a hand through the air to release a burst of azure light that carried the demon core to the elderly man.

In return, the white-robed elderly man tossed his wooden box to Han Li as well.

There was a talisman adhered to the wooden box, and with a sweep of Han Li's hand, the talisman was removed amid a flash of azure light, while the lid flew off on its own

A golden fist-sized spirit fruit was laying inside the box, and there was a series of ring-shaped patterns on its surface. The fruit wasn't releasing any special aroma, but it was giving off an immense aura of vitality.

Han Li gently picked up the fruit for a closer inspection, then nodded with a pleased expression.

This was indeed a Myriad Axis Fruit, and it was at least 60,000 to 70,000 years old, so it was old enough for his pill refinement needs. Furthermore, the core of the fruit was also completely undamaged, so he would be able to plant it.

After inspecting the black demon core for a while, the white-robed elderly man was clearly also quite pleased with what he saw, and he swept a sleeve through the air to release four or five more jade boxes of different colors.

"Like I said, I don't have a Blood Crystal Lotus Root, but these items should be comparable in value."

The elderly man swept his sleeve through the air once again as he spoke, and all of the lids of the boxes were removed to reveal their contents.

Han Li took a glance at the items in the boxes, then said, "These are indeed all comparable in value to the Blood Crystal Lotus Root, but I'm afraid none of them fit my needs, so I'll take some Immortal Origin Stones instead."

After their exchange was complete, Daoist Changhe said, "Fellow Daoist Li, the nine materials that you're looking for are extremely rare, and it seems like no one has what you're looking for. May I ask if you're willing to exchange that Blush Cloud Fire Crystal for spirit stones as well?"

Chapter 319: News

As Daoist Changhe was speaking, Han Li noticed another pair of eyes being trained on him, and it was none other than Shu Tiansheng.

With Han Li looking his way, Shu Tiansheng immediately put on a fawning smile.

Han Li withdrew his gaze, then shook his head with a decisive expression. "My apologies, but I'm only going to exchange this Blush Cloud Fire Crystal for one of the nine aforementioned materials."

Daoist Changhe was quite disappointed to hear this, but he was still unwilling to give up. "Is there no room for negotiation at all, Fellow Daoist Li?"

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li said, "I won't exchange this piece of Blush Cloud Fire Crystal for anything else, but I do have some smaller pieces of the same material that I'm willing to exchange for any leads on where I can obtain one or more of the nine materials I mentioned earlier."

He swept a sleeve over the table once again as he spoke, and a pair of fist-sized Blush Cloud Fire Crystals appeared.

Daoist Changhe took a longing glance at the two pieces of Blush Cloud Fire Crystal, but ultimately sat back down with a defeated expression.

Shu Tiansheng also sat down in his chair with a sullen expression, while Han Li heaved an internal sigh before stowing the three Blush Cloud Fire Crystals on the table away again.

The exchange event continued, but in contrast with the Blush Cloud Fire Crystals, everything else that was presented was made to look completely mediocre, and the atmosphere gradually died down.

An hour later, the exchange event concluded, and Han Li immediately stood up to leave with Qi Liang.

Once again, Daoist Changhe asked Han Li whether he was willing to exchange one of the two smaller Blush Cloud Fire Crystals for something else, and he brought out an array of rare and exotic items for Han Li's consideration.

However, none of those items caught Han Li's interest, and much to Daoist Changhe's disappointment, he was turned down once again.

However, Han Li did leave a communication array plate to Daoist Changhe so that he could contact Han Li if he ever did come across one of the nine materials or news on any one of them.

A glimmer of hope was sparked in Daoist Changhe's heart, and he promised that he would do his best, while also imploring Han Li to save one or two of the Blush Cloud Fire Crystals for him.

Han Li was rather surprised by how urgent Daoist Changhe was in his pursuit for a Blush Cloud Fire Crystal, and he agreed to his request before departing with Qi Liang.

"Where are you going next, Brother Li?" Qi Liang asked.

"I'm going to go to some other places to search for some materials. It's not every day that I get this opportunity, so I have to make the most of it," Han Li replied.

Qi Liang nodded in response. "I have some matters to take care of as well, so I won't accompany you any further, Brother Li. Take Care."

"Alright, then I'll see you at the preaching ceremony," Han Li said with a smile, then promptly departed.

Qi Liang looked at Han Li's departing figure for a while, then heaved a faint sigh before departing in another direction.

Han Li made his way down the street for a while before suddenly stopping in his tracks, then turned around with a cold expression. "You've been following me for quite some time now. What business do you have with me?"

Standing not far away behind Han Li was none other than Shu Tiansheng.

"I am Shu Tiansheng of the Heavenly Sage Peak. Please accept my apologies for my rude actions during the exchange event, Fellow Daoist Li," Shu Tiansheng said in an earnest manner as he cupped his fist in an apologetic salute.

Han Li's expression eased slightly upon hearing this, and he said, "Don't worry about it, it's not a big deal. My question is why are you following me around?"

"Thank you for your understanding, Fellow Daoist Li. I came here to ask you if you were planning to continue searching for the materials that you mentioned during the exchange event just now," Shu Tiansheng explained.

"I don't like to talk in circles, so if you have something to say, then be more straightforward," Han Li said.

"Truth be told, I have information on where you can secure one of those materials, but I didn't want to say it in front of everyone back there," Shu Tiansheng replied as a serious look appeared on his face.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up slightly upon hearing this. "Which material do you have information on?"

Shu Tiansheng opened his mouth to reply, but then decided against it.

Han Li could see that Shu Tiansheng had some reservations, so he said, "Rest assured, the offer that I made earlier still stands. If you can provide me with information on one of the materials, then you can have one of my Blush Cloud Fire Crystals."

"Well... I do have information one of the materials, but instead of one of the nine, it's the Blood Crystal Lotus Root," Shu Tiansheng said.

Han Li faltered slightly upon hearing this, then nodded in response. "That's fine, that's also one of the things that I'm looking for. What would you like in exchange for this information?"

"I can see that you're a very straightforward man, so I'll cut straight to the chase. I want to exchange the information I have for a Blush Cloud Fire Crystal," Shu Tiansheng said with a smile.

Han Li offered no response to this.

Shu Tiansheng took a deep breath, then continued, "I know that the Blood Crystal Lotus Root is lesser in value than the other nine materials that you mentioned, so I'm willing to throw in some Immortal Origin Stones as well in exchange for a small piece of Blush Cloud Fire Crystal."

"There's no need for that. The Blood Crystal Lotus Root is one of the things that I'm looking for as well, so I won't ask for any extra Immortal Origin Stones," Han Li said with a shake of his head.

His expression remained unchanged, but he was actually quite excited. Compared with the nine ingredients required for dao pill refinement, he would actually rather acquire the Blood Crystal Lotus Root as that was the final ingredient he was missing for refining Myriad Axis Pills.

"Thank you for your generosity, Fellow Daoist Li. At the moment, there are many cultivators gathered in White Jade City, and there's no lack of True Immortals among them, so there are many more auctions and exchange events to come. There's a secret high-end auction that's going to take place in three days, and only those who are at or above the mid-True Immortal Stage can attend.

“I only learned about this auction by chance, and I've heard that the Blood Crystal Lotus Root will be one of the auction items," Shu Tiansheng informed through voice transmission.

An intrigued look appeared in Han Li's eyes upon hearing this.

The fact that only those at or above the mid-True Immortal Stage could attend the auction meant that most of the Blaze Dragon Dao's elders would not have been granted entry, so this was quite a prestigious event.

"Seeing as you were able to dispel my illusion so easily, I'm sure the cultivation base restriction won't be a problem for you," Shu Tiansheng said, having adopted his usual cheeky grin again.

Han Li paid no heed to this blatant attempt at probing out his cultivation base as he nodded in response. "Alright, I'll be sure to attend this auction, and I'll give you a Blush Cloud Fire Crystal if a Blood Crystal Lotus Root really does appear."

A hint of elation flashed through Shu Tiansheng's eyes upon hearing this, and he nodded as he said, "Great! I'll meet you back here at noon in three days."

After that, he promptly bade farewell to Han Li, and the two went their separate ways.

The day quickly flew by, and at night, a series of massive crescent-shaped gemstones appeared throughout White Jade City, releasing bright white radiance that made the city just as bright as it was during the day.

All of the buildings in the city also lit up, and with the night sky acting as a backdrop, the entire city appeared even more alluring and resplendent than it was in the day.

Right at this moment, Han Li emerged from one of the shops in the city.

He had visited all of the remaining materials shops in the city out of hope more than conviction, and sure enough, he hadn't found any of the materials that he was looking for.

He was already prepared for this outcome, but he still couldn't help but feel a little disappointment, and he had no choice but to place his hopes in the private auctions and exchange events.

However, his exploration of the city hadn't been entirely fruitless.

For example, he had learned from the owner of one of the shops that another exchange event was going to take place the next day.

This exchange event was likely going to be even smaller than the one held in the Heavenly Scorpion Pavilion, but Han Li wasn't going to miss it.

A short while later, Han Li arrived on a rather quiet street that was lined with inns.

Having explored the city for an entire day, he may not have exactly been tired, but it was still time to get some rest.

After looking around for a while, he chose one of the smaller inns and requested a peaceful room, upon which he was led by an inn employee to a room on the third floor.

"Have a good night, and if you need anything, just call for me,” the employee said.

Han Li took a glance around the room to find that it was to his liking, and he gave the employee a spirit stone as a tip before waving a dismissive hand, indicating for him to leave.

The employee was ecstatic and extended a grateful bow before quickly departing.

Han Li was just about to close the door when the sound of footsteps rang out nearby, and a woman in red passed by in front of his room.

The woman's face was obscured by a veil, but she seemed to have been quite young and possessed an exceptional figure.

White Jade City was quite a large city, but due to the excessive number of cultivators in the city, most of the inns were most likely quite full.

The woman in red took a glance at Han Li, then quickly made her way past him and disappeared down the corridor.

A hint of befuddlement emerged in Han Li's eyes as he looked on at her departing figure.

The woman had concealed her own aura, but with Han Li's immense spiritual sense, he was able to instantly detect that she was a True Immortal cultivator.

At the moment, True Immortals were a dime a dozen in White Jade City, but this woman struck Han Li with a sense of familiarity, as if he had seen her before somewhere.

However, he couldn't recall exactly where he had seen her before, so he could only set the train of thought aside.

After closing the door, Han Li set up a layer of restrictions in the room, then sat down with his legs crossed on the bed.

……

Three days passed by in a flash, and Han Li arrived at the rendezvous location at noon.

Shu Tiansheng was already waiting there, and he immediately greeted Han Li with a wide smile. "Welcome, Fellow Daoist Li."

Han Li merely nodded in response.

"The auction venue is quite obscure, so please come with me, Fellow Daoist Li," Shu Tiansheng communicated through voice transmission, then led the way ahead.

The two of them walked along the streets in silence, and only after walking for close to an hour did they arrive at a secluded little shop.

The shop didn't have any customers, and there was only an elderly shopkeeper resting on a reclining chair behind the counter, looking as if he were about to nod off at any moment.

Chapter 320: Underground Auction

Shu Tiansheng flashed Han Li a smile, then tapped the counter a few times as he yelled, "Rise and shine, Shopkeeper Gu."

The elderly man behind the counter opened his eyes and took a lazy glance at Shu Tiansheng and Han Li, then slowly sat up as he yawned and asked in a raspy voice, "What would you like to buy?"

"The best that your shop has to offer, of course," Shu Tiansheng was sliding his finger over the counter, and Han Li noticed that he was tracing out a strange pattern with his finger.

An alert look immediately appeared in the elderly man's eyes upon seeing this, and he nodded in response before rising to his feet and making his way deeper into the shop, followed closely by Han Li's duo.

Before long, the three of them arrived in a dilapidated wooden shack in the backyard of the shop.

The elderly man tapped one of the walls of the shack a couple of times, and a string of cracks rang out as a layer of azure light appeared over the wall, then transformed into a shimmering azure door, beyond which was a dark pathway that appeared to have been leading underground.

"The auction venue is down there," the elderly man said as he pulled out a pair of white masks for Han Li's duo.

Some star and moon designs were engraved onto the masks, and they were giving off rippling waves of blue and white light, giving the masks quite a profound appearance.

Shu Tiansheng accepted the masks, then handed one to Han Li before leading the way into the passageway.

Han Li took a glance at the mask in his hand, then gave the elderly shopkeeper a nod before stepping into the passageway as well.

The stone gated behind him swung shut amid a burst of dull rumbling, and the interior of the passageway was plunged into complete darkness.

However, this degree of darkness naturally wasn't going to trouble Han Li.

The blue and white light on Shu Tiansheng's mask swelled to form a light barrier that enveloped his entire body.

Han Li was rather intrigued to see this. The blue and white light barrier was able to keep out even his spiritual sense, and it also concealed the majority of Shu Tiansheng's aura.

If it weren't for the fact that the two of them had been standing together this entire time, Han Li would've been unsure of whether this person actually was Shu Tiansheng.

The aura concealment effect of these masks was very similar to that of the masks of the Transient Guild, but they were far lacking compared to the Transient Guild masks when it came to their ability to alter auras.

Han Li also put on his mask before injecting some immortal spiritual power into it, but to his surprise, it displayed no reaction at all.

Han Li faltered slightly upon seeing this, then increased his immortal spiritual power output.

However, the mask was like a bottomless pit, and its surface had lit up slightly, but it was nowhere to the same extent as Shu Tiansheng's mask.

Han Li continued to increase his immortal spiritual power output until he was drawing upon most of the immortal spiritual power in his body, and only then did he manage to achieve the same effect as Shu Tiansheng's mask.

Only then did Han Li realize that this mask was a device that verified one's cultivation base, and that those below the mid-True Immortal Stage would've been unable to use it.

The two of them made their way down the dark passageway for a while before turning a corner and arriving in a stone chamber, at the end of which was a white door of light that was giving off a gentle glow in the darkness.

"The auction venue is just inside."

Shu Tiansheng seemed to have been quite familiar with this place, and he strode through the door of light.

The blue and white light barrier around him resonated momentarily with the door of light, and he abruptly vanished.

Han Li also stepped through the door of light, following which he found himself situated in a hall with Shu Tiansheng standing not far away.

Han Li cast his gaze into the hall to find that it was ovular in shape and around 3,000 to 4,000 feet in size.

The furnishings in the hall were quite luxurious, and the ground was paved with beautiful dark red bricks, while several massive and intricately crafted palace lanterns were hanging from the ceiling.

There were also many gemstones embedded into the walls, but even with the palace lanterns and gemstones acting as light sources, the area was still rather dim.

There were several dozen large chairs crafted from precious wooden materials in the hall, and many of them were already occupied, but all of the people seated on the chairs were also enshrouded in blue and white light barriers, making it impossible to glean their true appearance.

In front of these chairs was a short stone platform, upon which was placed a rectangular table, and behind the table were three empty chairs.

The arrival of Han Li's duo didn't draw much attention, attracting only a few fleeting glances.

"Looks like the auction isn't starting quiet yet. Let's find some seats first," Shu Tiansheng said in a low voice.

Han Li nodded in response, and he and Shu Tiansheng sat down on a pair of neighboring chairs near the back of the hall.

From there, Han Li looked around the hall, and a peculiar look flashed through his eyes.

There was a faint yellow light barrier over all of the walls of the hall, and it didn't appear to have been all that remarkable, but Han Li could sense that the restriction was extremely thick and dense.

The restriction was clearly an earth-attribute one, and it seemed to have been drawing power from the vast earth, which meant that attacking the restriction would've been equivalent to attacking the entire earth itself.

Such an advanced restriction was extremely uncommon, and by Han Li's estimates, even if he were to go all-out, he most likely wouldn't have been able to break the restriction.

The fact that there was such a formidable restriction in the auction venue indicated that this was truly a very prestigious event.

Everyone in the hall was seated with their eyes closed, and the entire hall was completely silent and filled with a tense and heavy atmosphere.

Two hours passed by in a flash, and during this time, two more cultivators arrived in the hall, both of which also sat down in silence.

Right at this moment, a wooden door swung open on the side of the hall, and three figures, two tall and one short, emerged from within.

These three figures were also completely enshrouded in blue and white light barriers that concealed their appearance, and they made their way over to the long table on the stone platform before sitting down behind it, with the shorter figure situated at the center.

"Sorry to keep you all waiting, fellow daoists. Before we begin the auction, allow me to lay out what's going to happen today," the short figure declared.

His voice was extremely clear and penetrative, and everyone below the platform immediately sat up straighter to listen.

"This auction will be split up into two parts. During the first half, the three of us will conduct the auction as normal, and after the auction, all of you will be welcome to come up to the stage to display any valuable items that you're looking to sell or exchange, and you can negotiate your own terms without any intervention from the three of us. Alright, without further ado, let's begin."

As soon as his voice trailed off, the tall figure to his left swept a hand through the air to produce a rectangular wooden box with several talismans adhered to it.

The short figure accepted the wooden box, then removed the talismans before opening it.

Inside the box was an antiquated-looking blue longsword that was giving off dazzling blue light that was flowing over the blade of the sword like water while producing a faint splashing sound.

Tiny blue runes could be seen drifting throughout the blue light, and the entire sword was giving off power law power fluctuations.

"That's an immortal treasure!" someone exclaimed before the short figure even had a chance to say anything.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly upon seeing this. The fact that the first auction item was an immortal treasure of a decent caliber certainly boded well for things to come.

"Indeed, Fellow Daoist. Our first auction item is this Sea Splitting Immortal Slaying Sword, and it's a bona fide immortal treasure that contains immense water law powers, far more so than the average immortal treasure..."

The short figure began to give a description of the sword, and he was an extremely eloquent speaker, sparing no praise in his description of the sword and making it out to be an unmatched weapon that would grant the wielder invincibility.

Many of the auction-goers were tempted by what they were hearing, and they were eager for the bidding to begin.

"The starting price for the Sea Splitting Immortal Slaying Sword will be 60 Immortal Origin Stones, and each bid must go up by an increment of at least two Immortal Origin Stones," the short figure declared.

"60!"

"65!"

"70!"

As soon as the short figure's voice trailed off, a string of bids immediately began flooding in, quickly elevating the bidding price to 130 Immortal Origin Stones.

At this point, there were only a handful of people left participating in the bidding, and ultimately, the sword was purchased for 160 Immortal Origin Stones.

Han Li chose not to place any bids.

While it was true that the Sea Splitting Immortal Slaying Sword contained immense law powers, he could sense that the law powers within it were a little chaotic, indicating that something had gone wrong during the refinement process, so this was above its deserved selling price.

The atmosphere had already livened up quite a bit, and the short figure was clearly very pleased to see this as he declared, "Our second auction item is a 100,000-year-old Soulbirth Flower. I'm sure I don't need to tell you all how valuable such a spirit plant is. It's the ideal supplementary material for refining avatars..."

The tall figure next to him pulled out a jade box, then opened it to reveal a golden spirit flower.

Many of the auction-goers erupted into chatter upon seeing this. The flower wasn't comparable in value to an immortal treasure, but it was certainly far rarer.

After praising the Soulbirth Flower for a while, the short figure declared, "The starting price will be 30 Immortal Origin Stones, and each bid must go up by an increment of at least one Immortal Origin Stone."

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes, and he clearly wasn't expecting to see a Soulbirth Flower of such an advanced age here.

He still had some Soulbirth Flower seeds, so he naturally had no intention of bidding for the flower, but it seemed that Shu Tiansheng was very eager to obtain the flower, and he was participating in the bidding war.

However, after a few rounds of bidding, the price was quickly raised to over 80 Immortal Origin Stones, and Shu Tiansheng could only drop out of the bidding war. In the end, the flower was sold for 95 Immortal Origin Stones, much to Han Li's intrigue.

He wasn't expecting Soulbirth Flowers to be able to fetch such a high price even on the Ancient Cloud Continent. With the Heaven Controlling Vial in his possession, he could mature some Soulbirth Flowers at anytime, but all spirit plants watered with the Heaven Controlling Vial's spirit liquid were imbued with traces of time law powers, which made selling such spirit plants quite risky and only something that he could turn to as a last resort.

With that in mind, Han Li could only heave an internal sigh.

The auction continued, and around 20 to 30 items were auctioned off in a flash.

All of the auction items had been extremely precious, with not a single one of them selling for below 50 Immortal Origin Stones, but the Blood Crystal Lotus Root still hadn't appeared.

Han Li was starting to grow a little concerned, and Shu Tiansheng was also getting slightly agitated.

"Are you sure your sources are correct, Fellow Daoist Shu?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

"I'm certain. I have some ties with the powers behind this auction, and there's no way they would lie to me," Shu Tiansheng hurriedly replied.

Chapter 321: Kindred Mark

Han Li offered no response to Shu Tiansheng, but his mind was racing.

At this point in the auction, the value of the auction items was gradually beginning to increase, with the exception of a few items that bucked this trend.

The Blood Crystal Lotus Root was quite a precious spirit plant, but it was already slightly lacking in value compared with the past few auction items, so it seemed increasingly unlikely that it was going to appear.

The same thought seemed to have occurred to Shu Tiansheng as well, and he was becoming more and more agitated. After all, if the Blood Crystal Lotus Root didn't appear in the auction, then he wouldn't be able to obtain a Blush Cloud Fire Crystal from Han Li, and he would most likely lose some trust from Han Li as well.

At this moment, an item had just been auctioned off, and a new item was brought out to replace it. The new item was a fist-sized fire-attribute True Immortal Stage demon beast core that was giving off a fiery red glow, within which were circles of tiny crimson runes.

"This is the demon core of a Golden Scale Red Wyrm at the pinnacle of the late-True Immortal Stage, meaning it was one step away from the Golden Immortal Stage at the time that it was slain. Its core is imbued with tremendous fire attribute law powers, making this an object of immeasurable value for those using fire-attribute cultivation arts. The starting price is 60 Immortal Origin Stones," the short figure declared.

Han Li nodded slightly to himself upon seeing this.

According to the provided description, the demon beast that the core had been procured from had been at an extremely lofty cultivation base, and the law power fluctuations emanating from its core was far superior to that of the demon core of Zhong Luan's black crane steed. With that in mind, even Han Li was feeling a little tempted to participate in the bidding.

However, such a precious demon core was undoubtedly going to be quite expensive. He had already saved up quite a large number of Immortal Origin Stones, but after the past 200 years of cultivation and pill refinement, he only had just over 1,000 left, so he couldn't afford to make unnecessary purchases.

"60!"

Shu Tiansheng had made the first bid.

"80!"

A female voice rang out, this time from Han Li's other side.

Han Li turned in that direction to find a petite figure seated on a chair to his left near the edge of the venue, and judging from her voice, she seemed to have been quite young.

Han Li had some recollection of her as she was the last person to arrive at the auction venue, and she was giving off a cold and unapproachable aura.

"90!"

This bid had come from a tall cultivator seated to the right side of the venue.

"100!" Shu Tiansheng called out.

"120!"

The female cultivator seemed to have been insistent on placing bids in increments of 20 Immortal Origin Stones.

Shu Tiansheng hesitated momentarily, then decided to drop out of the bidding war. This was already a very high price, and it wasn't worth making any further bids.

"130!"

The tall cultivator raised the price once again.

"140!"

The female cultivator was completely unfazed.

Han Li shook his head slightly upon seeing this.

140 Immortal Origin Stones was quite a large sum, even for a mid-True Immortal cultivator, and it was already far too much to pay for a late-True Immortal Stage demon beast core.

The tall cultivator was silent for a moment, then placed another bid. "145!"

"150!"

A hint of disdain had crept into the female cultivator's voice, and she seemed to have been losing her patience.

This time, the tall cultivator finally fell silent and didn't place any further bids.

Everyone present immediately turned to the female cultivator while shaking their heads, but she merely ignored them.

The short figure on the auction platform was naturally extremely pleased, and he quickly announced the sale of the demon core.

"A True Immortal Stage demon beast core is quite a precious object, but the next auction item is even more valuable, so be sure not to pass up on it," the short auctioneer declared as he swept a hand through the air, and a large crimson jade box appeared on the stage.

The entire box was giving off a layer of translucent crimson light, as well as a faint sweet fragrance that was wafting through the air in all directions.

The short auctioneer made a hand seal, and the lid of the jade box flew off on its own amid a flash of light.

Inside the box was a length of crimson lotus root that was around the same thickness as a human arm. It was preserved extremely well, and even the whiskers on the roots hadn't been damaged in the slightest.

Furthermore, the lotus root was glittering and translucent, looking as if it had been carved out of blood jade.

The lotus root was giving off a gentle crimson glow that formed a band of crimson light several inches above it, and the rich aroma of sweetness that it was giving off was quite reinvigorating even to all of the formidable mid-True Immortal cultivators present.

Shu Tiansheng was both ecstatic and relieved to see this, as was Han Li.

It seemed that he had made a misjudgment. The Blood Crystal Lotus Root was indeed very hard to find, but as long as it wasn't over 50,000 years of age, it would've been lacking in value compared with the previous few auction items. However, this one was definitely no less than 100,000 years of age.

However, in the next instant, his brows suddenly furrowed slightly.

He had noticed a subtle detail, which was that there was a gray area on the Blood Crystal Lotus Root that was around the size of a fingernail, and it seemed that the area had been contaminated.

"This is a Blood Crystal Lotus Root. Normally, a Blood Crystal Lotus Root wouldn't have made an appearance this late in the auction, but this one is already 150,000 years of age, making it an extremely rare specimen. I'm sure some of you have already noticed this gray spot on the lotus root. This is not a result of the lotus root being damaged. Instead, it's a rare kindred mark," the short auctioneer declared.

Many of the auction-goers erupted into chatter upon hearing this.

"Some of you may not be aware of what a kindred mark is. Essentially, if two spirit medicines are growing too close to one another, their spiritual power will impact each other, thereby resulting in the emergence of kindred marks," the short auctioneer continued.

"According to my knowledge, kindred marks can be both good or bad, and in bad cases, the energy in the spirit medicine will become very chaotic and weak, making it completely unusable," one of the auction-goers declared.

Even though his body was concealed within a blue and white light barrier, just like everyone else, it appeared that this was quite a portly individual.

"That is indeed true, Fellow Daoist. Kindred marks can have different effects on spirit medicines, but we've already had this lotus root appraised by masters in spirit plant agriculture, and they've determined that this kindred mark has a positive influence. Not only is the energy in the Blood Crystal Lotus Root not chaotic in the slightest, it's abnormally pure and dense, so all of you can rest assured," the short auctioneer replied.

This declaration was followed by another smattering of chatter.

"The starting price for this item will be 80 Immortal Origin Stones, and each successive bid must go up by increments of at least five Immortal Origin Stones," the short auctioneer declared.

"85!"

"90!"

"100!"

……

The purported special characteristics of the Blood Crystal Lotus Root made it an even more desirable item to everyone. Not only was it an exceptional spirit plant for bodily nourishment, it was an extremely prized treasure for anyone using body refinement cultivation arts, and even before Han Li had placed a single bid, the price had already exceeded triple figures.

Han Li merely sat still in his chair, seemingly contemplating something.

He was determined to acquire this Blood Crystal Lotus Root, but instead of being in a hurry to make a bid for it now, he was going to enter the bidding war at the end.

He turned to Shu Tiansheng as he said, "Looks like your sources were correct, after all. This is for you."

He flipped a hand over to produce a fist-sized Blush Cloud Fire Crystal as he spoke, then offered it to Shu Tiansheng.

They were seated near the back of the venue, and there weren't many people around them, so they didn't have to hide what they were doing.

The female cultivator who had purchased the fire-attribute demon core just so happened to look over at them at this moment, and she immediately sat up noticeably straighter at the sight of the Blush Cloud Fire Crystal.

Shu Tiansheng was ecstatic, and he hurriedly accepted the crystal. "Thank you, Fellow Daoist!"

Han Li offered no response as he turned his attention back to the ongoing auction.

After a few rounds of bidding, the price had climbed all the way to 150 Immortal Origin Stones, and that bid had been made by none other than the portly figure from before.

In the wake of this bid, all of the other bidders fell silent.

"160!"

Han Li had finally made his first bid.

The portly man turned to take a glance at him, then harrumphed coldly as he called out, "170!"

"190!"

Han Li's voice remained calm and level, and it seemed that had absolute confidence.

The portly man hesitated momentarily, then placed another bid.

"200!"

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he didn't want this to drag on any longer, so he decided to put his foot down once and for all.

"250!"

Shu Tiansheng turned to Han Li with a stunned expression, as did many of the other auction-goers.

A 150,000-year-old Blood Crystal Lotus Root was indeed extremely precious, but this was far too heavy a price to pay.

Han Li paid no heed to everyone else, and even though he was looking directly at the Blood Crystal Lotus Root on the stage, he was also keeping tabs on the portly figure out of the corner of his eye.

This time, the portly figure hesitated once again before deciding to concede.

The short auctioneer was already very pleased with this price, and with no further bids coming in, he declared the Blood Crystal Lotus Root as having been sold to Han Li.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh of relief as an excited look appeared in his eyes.

He had finally gathered all of the materials required to refine the Myriad Axis Pill, and all he needed was a piece of the Blood Crystal Lotus Root to grow more.

As these thoughts were running through his mind, the next auction item was brought out.

It was a piece of artwork that depicted a mountain, a river, and a palace.

The scroll that contained the artwork was blue in color, and it was giving off a glacial aura. It was clearly a formidable treasure, and the glacial qi that it was giving off was also interspersed with law fluctuations, indicating that it was an immortal treasure.

However, one corner of the scroll was slightly damaged, and that was the only imperfection.

"This is an immortal treasure by the name of the Infernal Frost Scenic Painting. It contains extremely formidable profound glacial qi and can unleash several types of glacial attacks. Unfortunately, it's a little damaged. The starting price will be 65 Immortal Origin Stones," the short auctioneer declared.

Han Li's eyes lit up slightly at the sight of the blue scroll.

This was indeed quite a formidable treasure that didn't contain any less law powers than the blue immortal sword from before, and the fact that it was a scroll indicated that it definitely had to have been more versatile than the sword and much more difficult to refine.

Even though it was slightly damaged, it was still quite a powerful treasure, and at this point, the bidding had already begun, with the price quickly rising to 90 Immortal Origin Stones.

"95!"

Han Li had also placed a bid.

He was quite interested in this immortal treasure, so he would be willing to purchase it as long as the price wasn't too high.

"100!"

This bid was placed by the female cultivator who had purchased the fire-attribute demon core.

Han Li took a glance at the female cultivator, and right as he was considering whether he would continue to participate in the bidding, another voice rang out from the front row of the venue.

"150!"

Han Li immediately shook his head and decided to drop out of the bidding war. This was already higher than the price that the immortal sword had been purchased for, and all of the other bidders fell silent as well.

Chapter 322: Astronomical Bidding War

"200!"

To everyone's surprise, the female cultivator who had purchased the demon core didn't give up, and she had raised the price by 50 more Immortal Origin Stones in a single bid.

Everyone faltered slightly upon hearing this before turning to her with peculiar looks in their eyes.

200 Immortal Origin Stones wasn't exactly a massive sum. All of the auction-goers present were at least at the mid-True Immortal Stage, and they had come to participate in this auction, so they could naturally afford this sum.

However, Immortal Origin Stones were extremely useful. Not only could they speed up one's immortal spiritual power replenishment, they could also assist one in opening up immortal acupoints. Hence, True Immortal cultivators were perpetually in need of more Immortal Origin Stones, and they were very prudent with their spending of this resource. With that in mind, it simply wasn't worth spending 200 Immortal Origin Stones for a damaged immortal treasure.

However, this still wasn't the end of the bidding war.

"230!" the owner of the sharp voice retorted.

"250! The female cultivator wasn't backing down, either"

"300!"

"350!"

……

Both of them seemed to have been determined to acquire the scroll, and in the blink of an eye, the price had been raised to an incredible level.

Many of the auction-goers present were astonished by this turn of events. There was no way that a damaged immortal treasure would've been worth this much unless it was harboring some type of secret.

With that in mind, some other people began to throw in bids as well, and the price was quickly pushed above 800 Immortal Origin Stones.

At this point, everyone else dropped out of the bidding war, and it reverted back to a two-horse race.

Blue light was flashing in Han Li's eyes as he carefully inspected the blue scroll with slightly furrowed brows, but no matter how he scrutinized it, he wasn't able to identify anything special about it aside from the profound glacial qi that it contained.

On the surface, his glacial qi didn't appear to have been special in any way, but he noticed there seemed to have been more to it than met the eye after he inspected it with his spiritual sense a few times.

This was a feeling that Han Li couldn't really describe, and if he had to compare it to something, then it was a little like the Essence Fire Raven.

After inspecting the scroll for a while longer, he withdrew his gaze.

There was no way that he was going to spend so much money to acquire the scroll, so what was the point in thinking about all of this?

"1,000!"

At this point, the owner of the sharp voice had already lost their composure, and it was clear that they were approaching their limit.

"1,200!"

The female cultivator's voice remained as steady as ever.

This time, the owner of the sharp voice was silent for a long while, yet right before the short auctioneer declared the scroll as sold, they made one final last-ditch effort.

"1,500!"

"2,000!"

The female cultivator seemed to have finally run out of patience and placed an astonishing bid.

Everyone was stunned beyond belief. This was a sufficient sum of Immortal Origin Stones to purchase more than 10 immortal treasures!

The owner of the sharp voice fell silent once again, and only after a long while did they give a cold harrumph. "Your determination is truly impressive. In that case, I'll relinquish the scroll to you."

After that, they stood up and departed from the auction venue.

Han Li looked on at their departing figure, and he was speculating whether they were leaving early as they were preparing to take the scroll from the female cultivator by force after the auction.

With that in mind, he took a glance at the female cultivator, only to find that she appeared to have been completely unconcerned.

The short auctioneer seemed to have been a little stunned as well, and it took him some time before he finally declared the sale of the Infernal Frost Scenic Painting.

Even though the scroll could only go to one person, everyone else felt as if they had been treated to a good show, so they weren't all that disappointed.

The auction continued, and the items were becoming more and more expensive, with many of the precious and exotic treasures being presented posing a great deal of temptation even to Han Li.

Unfortunately, none of the dao pill ingredients were among them, and as for the other treasures, he did have a decent wealth of Immortal Origin Stones, but he had to save up for his future pill refinement, so he could only let those treasures slip away right under his nose.

After close to two more hours, the final auction item was sold, and the auction reached its conclusion.

"Alright, that will be the end of the auction. It's now time for the free exchange event. Any fellow daoists wishing to sell or exchange any treasures can feel free to step onto the stage in turns," the short auctioneer declared, then made his way down from the auction platform the two taller figures accompanying him.

As soon as his voice trailed off, a streak of white light immediately flew onto the stage at an astonishing speed.

There were several other cultivators who wanted to go first, but they could only stop in their tracks upon seeing this.

In an exchange event like this, it was naturally best to go as early as possible. Otherwise, one risked having the treasures that they desired slipping away right before their eyes, and that was certainly not going to be a good feeling.

"Looks like I'll be going first, fellow daoists," the man on the stage chuckled as he cupped his fist in a salute toward the cultivators that he had beaten to the stage, and judging from the sound of his voice, he seemed to have been an elderly man.

The ones who were beaten to the stage could only return to their seats, but there was one thin and tall figure who remained on the spot as he chuckled, "With your Bright Yang Light Wave Arts, your speed is unmatched, Brother Qiu. Whenever I participate in any exchange events with you, you always beat me to the punch."

"Fancy meeting you here, Brother Fu. My sincerest apologies, but I truly am in urgent need of a certain treasure," the elderly man on the stage replied with a smile.

The thin and tall figure merely shook his head in response before returning to his seat as well.

"Fellow daoists, I've brought two things with me today," the elderly man said as he flipped a hand over to produce a pair of jade boxes, one large and one small.

With a sweep of his sleeve, the lids of the boxes were removed to reveal their contents.

Inside the larger jade box was a spirit plant that was around a foot in height and resembled a bamboo sapling with only 12 leaves, but what was remarkable was that every single leaf was a different color, and they were also all glowing slightly.

"This is a Heavenly Spirit Bamboo that grows a leaf once every 10,000 years, so this is a 120,000-year-old specimen. As for what it can be used for, I'm sure everyone already knows, so I won't waste everyone's time with an explanation."

Immediately thereafter, the elderly opened the other jade box to reveal some fine golden sand that was giving off such dazzling golden radiance that it was too bright to look directly at.

"This is Profound Golden Sand, an exceptional material for refining metal-attribute flying swords, and it can also be mixed into other immortal treasures to significantly enhance their resilience and sharpness," the elderly introduced.

These two items immediately created a stir among the auction-goers, and it was clear that they had generated much interest.

"For this Heavenly Spirit Bamboo, I would like a Meridian Opening Herb above 100,000 years of age. As for this box of Profound Golden Sand, I would like a spirit material that contains earth-attribute law powers in exchange," the elderly man declared.

Han Li was very much interested in the Heavenly Spirit Bamboo plant.

This was a type of spirit plant that contained a hint of poison law powers, and theoretically speaking, it could be used as an ingredient to refine pills that could cure all poisons. There were some antidotal spirit plants in his medicine garden, but none that could compare with this one.

Unfortunately, he hadn't even heard of this Meridian Opening Herb, and it was clear that the elderly man wouldn't have been willing to sell such a precious spirit plant for Immortal Origin Stones.

As for that box of Profound Golden Sand, that wasn't of any interest to him.

Right at this moment, a thin cultivator rose to his feet, then swept a hand through the air to release a burst of red light, enveloped within which was a rectangular jade box, which flew onto the auction platform.

"Will this Meridian Opening Herb suffice, Fellow Daoist?"

The elderly man picked up the jade box and opened it ever so slightly, then immediately shut the lid again as he replied in a concise manner, "Deal."

After that, he swept a sleeve through the air to release a burst of white light that carried the Heavenly Spirit Bamboo to the thin cultivator, and Han Li could only heave an internal sigh upon seeing this.

However, there were no takers for the box of Profound Golden Sand, and in the end, the elderly man could only step down from the stage.

As soon as he left, a streak of green light immediately flew onto the stage like lightning, and it was none other than the man with the Fu surname from before.

"I've brought with me a stick of Seven Spirit Incense that can assist True Immortal cultivators greatly when it comes to opening immortal acupoints. If you light this incense while attempting to open an immortal acupoint, your chances of success will be raised by about 10%."

The man pulled out a sandalwood box as he spoke, then opened it to reveal a stick of red and black incense, which was already giving off an indescribable aroma even though it hadn't been lit.

Almost all of the auction-goers immediately had their attention drawn to the stick of incense.

Treasures that could help one make breakthroughs were naturally the most welcome items in these exchange events.

The man with the Fu surname seemed to have been quite pleased with everyone's reactions, and he declared, "In exchange for this stick of incense, I would like a Heavenly Musk Fruit."

Unlike everyone else, Han Li wasn't very interested in this stick of incense. He was able to rely on the large number of pills he had refined to assist him in opening immortal acupoints, so this wasn't something that he was all that keen to get his hands on, and even if he did acquire it, he couldn't make more like he could with spirit medicines.

The stick of Seven Spirit Incense was indeed quite rare and precious, but Heavenly Musk Fruits weren't easy to come by, either, and in the end, no one was able to provide one.

Many of the auction-goers offered to exchange the stick of incense for other spirit items or to directly purchase it using Immortal Origin Stones, but all of them were turned down.

The exchange even continued, and one cultivator after another flew onto the stage to display their treasures. Some were fortunate enough to have been able to successfully find what they were looking for, but the vast majority of the items displayed weren't successfully exchanged.

This wasn't much of a surprise. After all, this wasn't a very large event, and most of the cultivators present weren't itinerant cultivators. Hence, they were generally all figures of rather lofty status, and the things that they were looking for definitely weren't easy to obtain. Otherwise, they wouldn't have come to participate in this exchange event.

Han Li merely sat in his chair rather than competing with others to fly onto the stage. He watched as a procession of treasures was presented, and it was quite an eye-opening opportunity, one that rarely presented itself.

As the exchange event neared its conclusion, there was gradually less and less competition between the people flying onto the stage, and there were even some instances of delays between one cultivator to the next.

It was during one of those delays that Han Li decided to fly onto the stage, but right as he was about to do so, a streak of black light flew onto the stage ahead of him.

Even though the blue and white light barrier, it could be seen that the figure was enshrouded in a cloud of black qi that was giving off a formidable baleful aura.

Han Li sat back down without saying anything, and just like everyone else, his gaze fell upon the figure on stage, wanting to see what it was that he was going to present.

Chapter 323: Those Who Know the True Value

The figure enshrouded in black qi remained silent as he pulled out a pair of stone boxes that he placed down onto the auction platform, and with a sweep of his sleeve, the lids of both of the boxes flew off at once to reveal a semi-transparent purple crystal and a rather strange-looking ball of black mud.

The crystal was around the size of a human fist, and its surface was riddled with pits and bums, as well as overlapping purple lightning veins.

These lightning veins were constantly flashing with purple lightning, as if they were lightning captured in solid form, and they were giving off a violent lightning aura.

As for the ball of black mud, it appeared to have been rather unremarkable at first glance, but upon closer inspection, one would notice that it was giving off a layer of extremely faint black light that seemed to be able to devour all surrounding light, giving it a very mysterious appearance.

"I'm exchanging this Lightning Soul Crystal for a lightning-attribute immortal treasure or 300 Immortal Origin Stones, and this ball of High Zenith Yin Mud for a 100,000-year-old Yin Dragon Ginseng," the figure declared.

A wry smile appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

He had thought that he had become far more knowledgeable about the spirit materials of the Immortal Realm since joining the Blaze Dragon Dao, but it seemed that this was still very much a work in progress as he hadn't heard of either of those two types of materials.

His gaze settled on the ball of black mud for a moment before quickly moving onto the purple crystal.

The ball of black mud was clearly some type of yin-attribute material, so he didn't have any use for it at the moment, but the purple crystal was giving him a sense of familiarity.

The lightning power imbued within it was very similar to the purple lightning in the clam bead he had obtained from the Thunderstorm Sea, and he couldn't help but wonder if this crystal had come from the same place.

The purple crystal wasn't very large, but it contained a truly formidable amount of lightning power, far more so than even that purple clam bead.

There were also faint spiritual fluctuations emanating from the deepest part of the crystal, indicating that the lightning power contained within it was so dense and abundant that it had developed some sentience.

Han Li was carefully inspecting the crystal with a thoughtful look in his eyes when a voice suddenly rang out in his mind.

Daoist Xie had woken up, and he communicated to Han Li through their psychic connection, "Fellow Daoist Han, please purchase this Lightning Soul Crystal. It will be of great use to me."

Ever since fusing with the Golden Immortal puppet, Daoist Xie had been in a state of hibernation, and Han Li had attempted to contact it a few times to no avail.

"What is this Lightning Soul Crystal and how will it be useful to you, Fellow Daoist Xie?" Han Li asked.

"The Lightning Soul Crystal is a type of special crystal that will only arise in places with extremely abundant lightning power, and not only does it contain immense lightning power, there's a type of special spiritual power interspersed within it as well. Not only is it very beneficial to those using lightning-attribute cultivation arts, it can also be worn to nourish the soul and avoid the negative influence of inner demons.

“I've been striving to completely fuse with the Golden Immortal puppet this entire time, but progress has been very slow. With this crystal, I'll be able to gain complete control over the puppet in a very short time," Daoist Xie explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a contemplative expression.

As their communication was taking place, the other cultivators present were also appraising the two items on display, but no one was saying anything, and it seemed like there weren't going to be any takers.

The black figure remained standing still on the stage in silence, seemingly unfazed by the lack of response.

A short while later, a slightly raspy voice rang out to break the silence. "Are you not going to introduce these two types of materials? Pardon my ignorance, but I've never heard of this Lightning Soul Crystal or this High Zenith Yin Mud before."

"I'm only offering these two things to those who know their true value," the black figure replied in an indifferent voice.

The one who had raised the question fell silent upon hearing this.

Right at this moment, a streak of light flew onto the stage, and it was none other than Han Li.

"I'll take the Lightning Soul Crystal, here are 300 Immortal Origin Stones."

He pulled out a storage pouch and tossed it at the black figure as he spoke.

Right at this moment, another portly cultivator also flew onto the stage, then pulled out a flying bident that was flashing with dazzling lightning as he declared, "Hold on, I have a lightning-attribute immortal treasure refined using Lightning Raise Steel that I'm willing to exchange for this Lightning Soul Crystal."

The black figure faltered slightly as he took a glance at Han Li's storage pouch and the flying bident, then accepted Han Li's storage pouch in silence before handing the Lightning Soul Crystal to him.

"Hold on a second. If I'm not mistaken, surely you want a lightning-attribute immortal treasure more than those Immortal Origin Stones," the portly cultivator hurriedly said.

"That's true, but you're a little too late," the black figure replied in an indifferent voice.

The portly cultivator faltered slightly upon hearing this, clearly not anticipating such a response. In the end, he could only stow his flying bident away again before flying back to his seat. "I hope you won't regret this!"

Han Li was also rather surprised by the black figure's decision, and his surprise was also tinged with a hint of admiration. It was very rare to see someone who could abide by their word so strictly, particularly in the often deceitful and immoral world of cultivators.

For a mid-True Immortal cultivator, it was only a matter of time and energy for them to accumulate 300 Immortal Origin Stones, but the same certainly didn't apply when it came to acquiring a suitable immortal treasure, particularly a lightning-attribute one.

Perhaps the portly cultivator was also aware of the value of the Lightning Soul Crystal, just like Daoist Xie, but he was slightly unwilling to part with his lightning-attribute immortal treasure, and that had allowed Han Li to seize the initiative.

With that in mind, he gave the black figure a nod, then returned to his chair.

"Give me the Lightning Soul Crystal!" Daoist Xie urged as soon as Han Li sat down.

Han Li duly obliged, sending the Lightning Soul Crystal in his storage bracelet to Daoist Xie.

The Lightning Soul Crystal instantly vanished into Daoist Xie's body amid a flash of golden lightning, and only then did Han Li notice that Shu Tiansheng's seat was vacant.

He took a glance at his surroundings, but failed to discover Shu Tiansheng anywhere in the venue, and it seemed that he really had left.

His brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but he didn't think much of it.

On the auction platform, the black figure waited for a while longer, but there were no takers for his High Zenith Yin Mud, so he could only fly back down from the stage in the end.

Han Li rose to his feet upon seeing this, yet right as he was about to fly onto the stage, a female voice suddenly rang out from beside him. "You must be Fellow Daoist Li, right?"

Immediately thereafter, the female cultivator who had purchased the Infernal Frost Scenic Painting earlier appeared in Shu Tiansheng's seat.

"Who're you?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

The female cultivator dodged the question as she asked, "Would I be able to take up some of your time?"

Han Li hesitated momentarily, then sat back down as he nodded in response.

"Just now, I happened to notice you trading a Blush Cloud Fire Crystal with the fellow daoist that was sitting here before me. Do you have any more of these crystals in your possession, and if so, would you be willing to trade them? I'll be sure to offer you a satisfactory price. For a fist-sized crystal like the one from before, I'm willing to offer you 100 Immortal Origin Stones, and the more you have to sell, the better," the female cultivator said in an earnest voice.

"You seem to already be aware that I have more Blush Cloud Fire Crystals in my possession, and you also know my surname. I'm assuming Shu Tiansheng must've told you those things, right?" Han Li asked in a calm voice.

The female cultivator nodded in response. "I did indeed learn these things from the fellow daoist from before."

Han Li's expression remained unchanged, but he was contemplating how to proceed.

Blush Cloud Fire Crystals were extremely precious, but he had quite a few of them, and he didn't really need them at the moment, so he was certainly open to selling them for Immortal Origin Stones.

However, he wasn't sure if he was going to have a use for them in the future, and if he were to sell them now, he could be left regretting his decision at some later point.

"Agree to her offer, Fellow Daoist Han."

Daoist Xie's voice had suddenly rung out again.

"Why?" Han Li asked through their spiritual connection.

"I'll tell you why once I've completely fused with the Golden Immortal puppet. For now, just agree to her offer," Daoist Xie said, then fell silent again.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon hearing Daoist Xie's ambiguous response, but after a brief hesitation, he nodded as he replied, "Alright, I can sell my crystals to you."

"You've definitely made a wise decision, Fellow Daoist. I can assure you that no one else would be willing to offer such a high price for these crystals."

The female cultivator's voice was a little cold, but there was an unmistakable hint of elation as she spoke.

Han Li offered no response as he swept a hand over his storage pouch, and a new storage pouch appeared in his grasp with a flash of azure light.

He handed the storage pouch to the female cultivator, who accepted it before inspecting its contents with her spiritual sense, then immediately flipped a hand over to produce a storage pouch of her own that she handed to Han Li.

Han Li accepted the storage pouch and merely took a glance at it before giving the female cultivator a nod.

The female cultivator cupped her fist in a salute, then returned to her original seat.

Han Li looked on at her departing figure, and his brows furrowed ever so slightly.

Thanks to his immense spiritual sense, he was able to see through the blue and white light barrier to make out a blurry outline of the woman's figure, and he felt as if he had seen her from somewhere before.

All of a sudden, he recalled who she was.

She's the woman in red staying at the same inn as me!

Not only that, but the woman had struck him with a sense of familiarity back when he first saw her in the inn, and during their second meeting here, that sense of familiarity had only grown more pronounced.

Right at this moment, another cultivator just so happened to have stepped down from the stage, and Han Li immediately flew onto the auction platform, then displayed some of the precious materials in his possession while laying out the dao pill ingredients that he wanted.

Unfortunately, none of the auction-goers had any of those materials, and he was ultimately disappointed once again.

Close to an hour later, the final cultivator stepped down from the stage, and the exchange event drew to a conclusion.

Han Li issued the Immortal Origin Stones required to purchase the Blood Crystal Lotus Root, then examined it briefly before carefully storing it into a jade box. After that, he adhered a few talismans to the box before stowing it away in his storage bracelet.

Chapter 324: Refinement

A short while later, Han Li appeared on a quiet street in White Jade City.

"Fellow Daoist Han, I require an array to help me refine this Lightning Soul Crystal," Daoist Xie requested.

"What do you need me to prepare?" Han Li asked as he continued to walk down the street without pause.

A stream of information was immediately transmitted into his mind, laying out the method and materials required to set up an array.

"Alright, I'll get everything prepared as soon as possible, then arrange a secret chamber for you back on the Crimson Dawn Peak," Han Li said.

There were quite a few materials on the list, some of which weren't that easy to find, and it would've most likely taken him quite some time and effort to gather these materials under normal circumstances, but with all of these powers gathered in White Jade City and his membership in the Transient Guild, he was sure that it wouldn't have been very difficult to gather everything as long as he was willing to do some spending.

Furthermore, the array did appear to have been rather complex, but that wasn't an issue for him.

"There's no need for that, we can just get it done in the inn's secret chamber. With the help of the array, I should be able to completely fuse with the puppet in the next few days," Daoist Xie said.

Han Li nodded in response, then flew toward the nearest materials shop.

Only after night had fallen did he return to the inn where he was staying, and after entering the secret chamber, he flipped a hand over to produce a stack of array flags, then casually tossed them through the air, distributing them around the room in a rather peculiar array.

Immediately thereafter, he began to chant an incantation, and five light barriers of different thicknesses appeared to encompass the entire room.

After that, Han Li swept a hand through the air to release a burst of azure light, which carried all of the furniture into the room to one corner to vacate a large space, then summoned a bunch of different objects, including some lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood.

All of a sudden, Han Li's expression changed ever so slightly as he pulled a purple talisman that was riddled with silver patterns out of his storage bracelet. It was that Azure Wind Lock Immortal Talisman, and he had spotted it in a corner of his storage bracelet while summoning all of the other items required for the array.

All of a sudden, it occurred to him that the woman in red was none other than the woman who had given him this Azure Wind Lock Immortal Talisman, Gan Jiuzhen.

Her aura was slightly different from Gan Jiuzhen's, perhaps because she had intentionally altered it, and that was why he had only just made this realization.

"I didn't think that she would be here in White Jade City as well," Han Li murmured to himself, then shook his head to rid himself of that train of thought before stowing the Azure Wind Lock Immortal Talisman away again.

He wasn't particularly close with Gan Jiuzhen, and he didn't care to know the reason behind why she had come to the Blaze Dragon Dao. Presumably, it didn't have anything to do with him.

After taking a moment to settle his thoughts, he began to make some inscriptions on the ground.

After several hours of toil, day had transitioned into night, and a circular array that was around 100 feet in diameter had appeared on the ground in the room. The center of the array was riddled with spirit patterns that were surrounded by lengths of Lightning Restraining Wood, which were crackling with lightning.

Han Li exhaled as he patted his storage pouch, and a streak of golden light flew out before landing at the center of the array to reveal Daoist Xie.

Daoist Xie inspected its surroundings momentarily, then gave Han Li a nod before sitting down with its legs crossed.

"Do you need me to look out for you during the process, Brother Xie?" Han Li asked.

"There's no need for that, I'll be fine on my own," Daoist Xie replied.

"In that case, I'll leave you to it," Han Li replied with a nod.

There were still a few days left until the preaching ceremony, and he wanted to take advantage of this window of opportunity to search for some more dao pill ingredients, so he didn't want to waste any time here unless his presence was necessary.

Meanwhile, Daoist Xie quickly sprang into action, making a hand seal as it began to chant an incantation, and thick arcs of golden lightning emerged from its chest before spreading all over its entire body.

Arcs of golden lightning also emerged from the array on the ground before forming a series of profound lightning runes that resonated with the golden lightning flashing over Daoist Xie's body, quickly intertwining with one another before slowly revolving on the spot.

In the blink of an eye, a flashing ball of golden lightning had appeared around Daoist Xie,and arcs of lightning were surging over its surface, while the occasional bolt of stray lightning would spring forth in a random direction.

Thankfully, five layers of restrictions had already been set up in the room to contain the bolts of stray lightning.

Instead of immediately departing, Han Li remained in one corner of the room to observe the process.

A loud thunderclap rang out from Daoist Xie's head, and arcs of dazzling purple lightning emerged to envelop the entirety of its head.

A crystalline object could be seen within the purple lightning, and it was none other than that Lightning Soul Crystal.

Compared with the lightning released by the clam pearl, this purple lightning was brighter and more translucent.

The purple lightning continued to flash as it rapidly spread over Daoist Xie's body, and the light radiating from the puppet's body became even brighter, as if some important points had been opened up.

Han Li gave a slight nod upon seeing this, and he was just about to depart when the purple lightning erupting out of the Lightning Soul Crystal abruptly swelled.

At the same time, it began to spread over Daoist Xie's body faster than before, and it quickly fused with the golden ball of lightning around it.

The ball of golden lightning instantly began to ripple, and a huge bulge appeared on its surface.

A resounding boom rang out as the bulge exploded, and arcs of purple and golden lightning erupted in all directions to strike the first azure restriction in the room.

The restriction only lasted a second or two before being violently torn apart, and the remaining lightning continued onward to strike the second yellow restriction, which quickly dimmed and appeared to have been on the verge of breaking as well.

Not only that, but a second bulge had exploded on the ball of golden lightning, sending even thicker bolts of lightning erupting everywhere.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and four true spirit projections emerged around him, namely that of the Xuanwu, the Lightning Bird, the Giant Mountain Ape, and the Divine Dragon.

The four beast projections opened their mouths in unison to release bursts of black, silver, yellow, and red light, respectively into the remaining four restrictions.

As a result, the four restrictions were instantly significantly bolstered, becoming several times thicker than before, and the yellow light barrier abruptly brightened as a giant ape projection appeared on its surface.

Thick bolts of lightning struck the yellow light barrier, producing loud clangs that resembled the sound of metal striking against metal, and the light barrier began to flash erratically.

The giant ape projection on its surface quickly began to dim, and it was also rapidly thinning at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye.

Han Li immediately began to chant an incantation while making a rapid string of hand seals, and a series of four-colored halos instantly swept out of the four light barriers before proliferating outward in all directions.

The four light barriers then fused into a single four-colored light barrier that was several feet thick and was giving off a metallic sheen.

As soon as it took shape, it was immediately struck by bolts of golden and purple lightning, only for the bolts of lightning to instantly vanish into the light barrier without a trace.

The four-colored light barrier shuddered a few times, but displayed no signs of breaking.

Han Li's expression eased slightly upon seeing this, but he still maintained his hand seal.

As time passed, the four true spirit projections around him became clearer and clearer, and they were continuously releasing pillars of light into the four-colored light barrier to bolster it.

This entire time, Daoist Xie remained seated at the center of the array with its eyes tightly shut, and it seemed to have been completely oblivious to its surroundings.

Han Li was left feeling a little speechless upon seeing this. If he hadn't intervened in a timely fashion, all five of the light barriers would've been torn apart, and the entire inn would've been destroyed, thereby revealing the Golden Immortal puppet.

After a moment of hesitation, Han Li decided to ask Daoist Xie what was happening through voice transmission, yet he received no response, and it was as if Daoist Xie hadn't heard him at all.

Han Li didn't say anything further, but his plans to leave were naturally foiled, and he decided to stay and observe the unfolding situation.

Several hours quickly passed by, and not only had the purple lightning erupting out of Daoist Xie's head not abated in the slightest, it was only becoming brighter and more powerful.

The ball of golden lightning was becoming more and more unstable as it churned violently, while even thicker bolts of purple and golden lightning were erupting in all directions without displaying any signs of stopping.

Han Li continued to support the four-colored light barrier while standing in the corner of the room, and there was a slightly dark look on his face.

Given this current situation, it was clear that he wouldn't be able to leave anytime soon.

Three days later.

Han Li was seated on the ground with his legs crossed, continuing to maintain the four-colored light barrier.

At the center of the array, Daoist Xie's entire body was enveloped in purple lightning, making it appear as if it were wearing a suit of purple lightning armor.

The ball of golden lightning formed by the array had also swelled significantly in size, taking up close to half the entire room, and it didn't seem as if it were going to fade away anytime soon.

Han Li's expression had darkened even further.

The preaching ceremony was going to begin on this day, and he didn't know when this process was going to conclude. If he were delayed any longer, then he would have to miss the preaching ceremony altogether.

If he had known that this would happen, then he would've taken Daoist Xie back to the Crimson Dawn Peak. The restrictions in the cave abode there had been set up by him over the course of many years, and they were far more formidable than the ones here, so even without his support, they should've been able to contain the lightning that was constantly erupting in all directions.

However, it was too late to think about that now. At this point, there was no way that he could leave. Otherwise, it was very likely that all of the prior efforts that he had made would go to waste.

Right at this moment, the lightning array began to glow with dazzling radiance while countless lightning runes emerged everywhere.

Han Li hurriedly focused his attention on the array right as a string of crackling rang out.

The purple lightning around Daoist Xie's body swelled drastically before being absorbed into its body in a flash, while the surrounding ball of golden lightning also fluctuated violently before also surging into Daoist Xie's body in a frenzy.